Tonari no Totoro
arukou  arukou  watashi wa genki
あるこうあるこうわたしはげんき
Let's walk, let's walk, I feel fine.
aruku no  daisuki  don-don ikou
あるくのだいすきどんどんいこう
I love to walk, let's go quickly.
sakamichi TONNERU kusappara
さかみちトンネルくさっぱら
An uphill road, a tunnel, a meadow,
ipponbashi ni dekoboko jari-michi
いっぽんばしにでこぼこじゃりみち
At a long bridge, a bumpy gravel path.
kumo no su kugutte kudari-michi
くものすくぐってくだりみち
Passing under a spiderweb, a downhill path.
arukou arukou watashi wa genki
あるこうあるこうわたしはげんき
Let's walk, let's walk, I feel fine.
aruku no daisuki don-don ikou
あるくのだいすきどんどんいこう
I love to walk, let's go quickly.
kitsune mo tanuki mo dete oide
きつねもたぬきもでておいで
Foxes and badgers too, come out!
tanken-shiyou hayashi no oku made
たんけんしようはやしのおくまで
Let's go exploring deep into the woods.
tomodachi takusan ureshii na
ともだちたくさんうれしいな
I have lots of friends, I'm so happy.
tomodachi takusan ureshii na
ともだちたくさんうれしいな
I have lots of friends, I'm so happy.
Hey, Dad, want some caramel?
Thanks.
How are you doing back there?
I'm fine.
We're almost there.
Mei, hide!
l thought that was a policeman.
Hello there. Are your parents around?
Great. Thanks.
Hello! We're the Kusakabes!
We're moving in down the street.
A pleasure to meet you!
Welcome!
Thank you.
Here we are!
Wait!
Mei, there's a bridge!
A bridge?
There's a fish!
Look! There's another one!
So, how do you like the new place?
Dad, it's perfect!
Look at this. A tunnel of trees!
Is that our house?
Come on!
It's a wreck!
Wreck!
It looks like it could be haunted.
Haunted?
And it's all rotten!
It's gonna fall down!
Fall down!
Look, Mei!
See?
It's huge.
Dad, there's a huge tree!
It's a camphor tree.
Camphor tree...
Oops!
An acorn!
Show me.
Another one!
One for me!
Out of the way.
I can't open the screens.
Acorns!
There are acorns in the house.
They dropped from up there!
Maybe there are squirrels in here.
Squirrels, really?
Or rats that like acorns.
I'd rather have squirrels!
Where shall I put this?
Here, I'll open the door for you.
Satsuki, open up the kitchen.
-Okay!
It's just around the back.
Okay!
Mei, come on!
Wait for me!
Hurry!
Ready?
Yeah.
Bathtubs.
There's nothing here.
That's the bathroom.
Dad, there's something in here.
A squirrel?
I dunno.
They're not bugs or mice.
They were black and they were all over the place!
Really?
Can you see 'em?
I think they were... dust bunnies.
"Dust bunnies"?
Like in my picture book?
That's right.
Ghosts don't come out on days like this.
When you walk into a dark room from outside,
your eyes dim and so the dust bunnies come out.
Oh, I see.
Come here, dust bunnies.
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Let's get to work!
See if you can find a way to get upstairs.
Get up there and open all the windows.
Sure!
I'm coming, too!
Toilet!
Not here!
Not here.
Nothing here!
Nothing!
Mei, it's here!
It's pitch black!
Dust bunnies...
Another acorn.
Come out, dust bunnies!
Are you there, Dustbunny-san?
Dad, there's definitely something here!
That's exciting!
I've always wanted to live in a
haunted house ever since I was a little boy.
I'm coming!
I got it. Satsuki!
Mei?
You're full of energy!
This is our new neighbour.
She takes care of this house.
I'm Satsuki and this is my sister, Mei.
Nice to meet you.
Well, it's nice to meet you too.
I'm sorry l didn't have time
to clean up a bit more before you got here.
No, you've done plenty.
We've been very busy in the rice fields,
...but l did manage to keep
the place well dusted, as you can see.
Mei, what have you done to your hands?
The dust bunny got away...
Your feet, too!
Mine are black, too!
That must be the "soot sprites".
Soot sprites?
The black puff balls?
About this big?
They scurry everywhere when you enter a room?
That's right.
They live in old, empty houses,
and run all over the place,
covering everything with dirt.
l used to be able to see them when l was your age.
So you've seen them too.
Are they like ghosts or something?
Don't worry, dear. They're nothing to be afraid of.
If they decide that you're nice people,
they won't harm you,
and after a while, they'll just go away.
Right now they're probably deciding where to go next.
Mei, they're going away.
That's no fun.
What happens if a huge one comes out, like this?
I wouldn't be scared.
Okay then. I won't walk you to the bathroom at night.
Okay, cleaning time.
Could you get some water from the stream?
From the stream?
I'm coming, too!
Mei, wait there.
Did you get a fish?
Granny, it's coming out!
Good, keep pumping 'til the water gets cold.
Okay!
May I help you?
Huh... my Mum... for Granny.
What?
Wait, what is it?
Is that you, Kanta?
Hey! You live in a haunted house!
Kanta!
I did the same when I was his age.
I hate boys.
But I really love Granny's rice cakes!
Eat as much as you want.
Thank you!
Thank you very much for your help.
Good bye!
Dad, the house is going to fall down.
I hope not. We've only just moved in.
Everybody, try laughing.
Then whatever scares you will go away.
I'm not scared.
I mean it. I'm not scared!
One-two, one-two, one-two...
Come on, keep up the good work...
Okay! Washing... finished!
Here we go!
Granny!
Hello!
Hard at work?
Where are you all heading?
To visit Mummy in the hospital!
That's nice.
Give her my regards!
Okay!
This way.
Hello.
Hello there.
Mummy!
So glad you came, my dear.
Daddy took the wrong road.
Really? Hello, Satsuki.
It's a school holiday, today.
How nice.
Daddy is talking to the doctor.
It's so good to see you all.
Have you settled into the new house?
A haunted house?
Mum, do you like ghosts?
Of course I do!
I can't wait to see them.
See, I told you Mei.
Yeah!
Mei was worried that you wouldn't like ghosts.
What about you two?
I love them!
I'm not scared of them!
Are you fixing Mei's hair, Satsuki?
Yeah!
It's really good.
Lucky girl, Mei.
But she always gets mad at me.
That's 'cause you won't stay still.
Come here, Satsuki.
Isn't yours too short?
No, I like it like this.
Do mine, Mummy! Mine, too!
Wait your turn!
Wavy hair, just like mine when I was your age.
Will it be like yours when I grow up?
Probably. You take after your Mum.
Mum looked really well.
You're right.
The doctor says she'll be home soon.
Soon? Like tomorrow?
You always say this.
Tomorrow is a little too soon.
Mum said she'll sleep with me in my bed.
Weren't you saying you're big enough to sleep alone?
Mum is special!
Dad, time to get up!
Wake up!
Sorry, I overslept again...
I've got to bring a box lunch today.
I totally forgot about it.
It's all right.
I've made something for all of us.
It's burning!
I'm coming.
Here, this is yours, Mei.
It's for me?
Mei, sit down and eat!
Here!
Wrap it up.
Satsuki-chan!
Uh-oh.
I'm coming!
You made a friend already?
She's calling you!
Yup, that's Michiko.
Gotta go!
See ya!
See you later!
Morning!
Hi, let's go.
Yeah.
Daddy!
Do I look all grown up?
Yes, dear.
And where might you be going?
I'm just going out.
Daddy, is it lunch yet?
What, already?
You will be the flower shop, Daddy.
Tadpoles!
Got no bottom.
Gotcha!
Who are you?
A big dust bunny?
To-to-ro? You're Totoro!
I bet you're Totoro.
Totoro!
See you!
Okay, catch you later!
I'm home!
Hey there. Is it that late already?
Where's Mei?
I'm off to Michiko's.
We haven't eaten yet.
Is Mei in the garden?
Mei!
Mei?
Dad, I found her hat!
Mei!
Wake up, Mei!
You shouldn't sleep here!
Where's Totoro?
Totoro?
Where?
Were you dreaming?
Totoro was here.
You mean that troll in your picture book?
Yeah.
He was all hairy with a big mouth like this.
There's a tiny one and a little one and a huge one like this.
There you are.
Wow, this is amazing.
A great hiding place!
Dad, Mei said she met a Totoro here.
A Totoro?
-Yeah!
It's this way.
Hey, wait for me!
Huh?!
Here?
No.
It went to a big tree.
But there wasn't any other path.
Mei!
Come back!
Come back, Mei!
But it's true! Totoro was here.
I'm not lying.
Mei!
I didn't lie.
Sure. Neither of us think you're lying.
You probably met the king of this forest.
You were very lucky.
He doesn't come out very often.
We should pay our respects at the shrine.
Pay our respects?
To this forest.
Mei, you're getting heavy.
Daddy, look! That camphor tree!
What a big tree.
It's here!
Is that the tree?
Yup!
Dad, hurry up.
The hole has gone.
Are you sure it was here?
Yes.
The hole disappeared.
I told you he doesn't come to see us often.
But will he come again?
I want to meet him, too.
If you're lucky, sure.
What a beautiful tree.
This tree must have stood here for years and years.
Trees and people used to be good friends.
I saw that tree and fell in love with the house.
I hope that Mum likes it, too.
Okay, let's pay our respects and then get home for lunch.
Yes, I promised to go see Michiko.
I want to go, too!
Attention!
Thank you for looking after Mei.
Please take care of us.
Let's race home!
That's not fair! Dad!
Wait!
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Dear Mother, something amazing happened today.
Mei met a giant Totoro.
And I'm hoping to see him myself soon, too.
Kanta, hurry up! You'll be late!
Yeah.
Back to work!
Mei?
Excuse me!
Yes, Satsuki?
It's my sister...
What happened, Granny?
I'm sorry.
She insisted to be with you.
It's Dad's day at the university.
You promised to be a good girl at Granny's.
I still have two more classes
and Granny's too busy for this...
She was good up 'til now, weren't you?
I'll go and talk to my teacher.
Since Satsuki-san's mother is in the hospital,
I want you all to be nice to her.
Okay!
What's that?
It's Totoro.
Mei, you should keep quiet.
Okay.
Bye bye, Mei-chan!
I can't stay after class today.
Okay. We'll let the teacher know.
See you!
Bye bye!
Hurry up, it's going to rain!
Okay.
Here it comes!
Come on!
I won't cry.
Aren't I good?
Yeah.
But, it's getting worse...
Dear Guardian Spirit, let us stay until the rain stops.
But...
That was lucky.
Yeah.
It's got holes in it.
I better give Daddy's his umbrella.
I'm going, too.
I said I forgot it!
What idiot forgets his umbrella on a rainy day?
Ouch!
You broke it, I bet.
I did not!
Excuse me.
Hello Satsuki-san. Hi, Mei-chan.
Grandma!
I'm sorry about Mei today.
Not at all. Sorry we couldn't do more.
Kanta lent us this umbrella.
What? He lent you this?
A broken old thing like that!
Mei was with me, so I was glad.
But I'm so sorry that Kanta got wet.
Not at all.
It probably cleaned him up a little.
Are you off to meet your father?
Yes.
What good girls you are.
Bye bye, Mei-chan.
Bye bye.
Who was that?
I don't know.
Just in time!
Getting on?
All right, drive on.
Daddy wasn't on it.
He'll be on the next one.
Why don't you wait at Granny's?
Are you okay?
Mei...
Are you sleepy?
l knew this would happen.
Don't you want to wait at Granny's?
It won't be much longer.
Hang in there.
That bus sure is late, huh?
Come on.
Are you Totoro?
Ah, wait a minute.
You can use this.
Take it. Mei's slipping off.
Hold it like this.
Here's the bus!
Totoro took Daddy's umbrella...
I'm sorry.
All right, drive on.
My train was delayed,
so l had to wait for the next bus.
Were you worried?
We met him, Dad!
He was here!
And the cat bus!
What?
It was huge!
With big eyes like these!
-Scary!
We met him!
We met Totoro!
How wonderful!
Come on.
Dear Mother, I can't tell you how excited I was today.
It was the scariest, funniest day I've ever had.
Totoro gave us a lovely present...
...wrapped in bamboo leaves
and tied with dragon whiskers.
When we opened it,
it was full of magic nuts and seeds!
"We decided to plant them in the
garden to make a lovely forest. But..."
...they haven't sprouted yet.
Mei sits there all day, waiting for them.
She looks like a little crab.
It's nearly summer vacation.
Mother, get well soon. Love, Satsuki.
Come on. Bed time.
Lights off!
Wait, Dad.
Daddy, do you think they will sprout tomorrow?
Well, I'm sure Totoro would know.
Goodnight.
Mei!
That's where we planted the seeds.
Wow, we did it!
Mei, we're the wind!
There are no trees!
Yes!
It was a dream.
But it wasn't a dream.
We did it!
Kusakabe-san! Telegram!
Kusakabe-san!
Telegram!
Anyone home?
Granny.
I'm here.
This one is ripe.
What about this one?
That's good, too.
Your garden's a treasure house.
Let's take a little break.
These should be cold now.
Thanks for the food.
So good.
Yes. The sun blessed these
so they're really good for you.
Would they help my Mum, too?
Of course.
If she eats my vegetables, she'll get better right away.
She's supposed to be back on saturday.
She'll sleep in my bed!
Good. At last. That's wonderful.
But it's only for a couple of days.
To get used to the new house.
She will go back on monday.
I see.
We'll give her lots of vegetables, then.
I'll give her this corn I picked.
I'm sure she'll be very pleased.
Yes!
There was a telegram for you.
For us?
Dad won't be back till late. What shall I do?
Open it, it might be important.
Please contact, hospital...
It's from Mom's hospital!
Something's happened to her!
Granny!
What shall I do?
Calm down.
Do you know where your Dad is?
I know his office number,
but we don't have a telephone.
Kanta, take her to use the phone in the main house!
Okay.
Mei, stay here with me!
Stay with Granny, Mei!
Hello. I'd like to make a long-distance call, please.
It's Tokyo 31 -1 382.
Yes.
A cute girl, Kanta.
Hello?
Yes.
Hello, may I speak to Dad... er... Mr. Kusakabe?
It's his daughter, Satsuki.
Yes.
Daddy?
It's me, Satsuki!
Hello, what's wrong?
From the hospital?
Okay, I'll call them right away.
Is there anything wrong with Mum? What should I do?
Don't worry.
I'll check and call you right back.
Just wait by the phone.
Yes.
I'm hanging up now. Stay there.
May I stay here until he calls back?
Stay as long as you like.
Satsuki!
No, this corn is for my Mummy!
No, it's my Mom's!
Mei.
Mom's not well so she's not coming home this time.
No!
There's nothing we can do.
You don't want her to get worse, do you?
No!
It's just for a few more days.
So you don't care if she dies, do you?
No!
Stop being silly!
I'm going.
Let's go.
I hate you, Satsuki!
We should bring the washing in...
Don't worry too much, Satsuki.
Granny's here to help, so cheer up.
Your Dad said that he'll stop
by the hospital to check on her.
Besides, it's just a cold. She'll be back next week.
They said it was just a cold...
when she went into the hospital.
But what if she dies!
Don't be silly, Satsuki.
Maybe Mum will...
Stop it. Nobody would leave two pretty little girls like you.
There, there. Don't cry.
I'll be here until Daddy comes back, okay?
Mei-chan!
Mei!
Did she come back?
Wasn't she at the bus stop?
That's strange.
Where has she gone?
I yelled at her, because she was being silly...
Maybe she's heading for the hospital!
The hospital?
It would take a grown-up 3 hours!
I'll go look!
Kanta, hurry!
Tell your dad that Mei-chan is missing!
Stupid Mei.
Always getting lost.
Mei!
Excuse me, mister.
Have you seen a little girl pass by?
She's my sister.
No, I don't think so.
I'm sure I would've noticed...
Maybe she wasn't here.
Are you sure she came this way?
I don't know.
Mei!
Please, stop!
Idiot! What are you doing?!
I'm looking for my sister.
Have you seen a little girl?
Your little sister?
I think she's heading to the hospital. She's only 4.
Did you see anyone?
No. We just came from there...
...but we didn't see anyone.
Thanks anyway.
Where are you from?
From Matsugo.
Matsugo?
Really? It's very far away.
Good luck.
Satsuki!
Kanta!
Did you find her?
No. And you?
Dad and the others are looking for her.
I'll go to the hospital. You should go back home.
I guess she got lost on the way to the hospital.
They found a sandal by the pond.
We're not sure if it's hers or not!
Did you find her?
Dear Lord, please protect her and...
It's too deep here, better search further away!
Hey, are there any poles left?
Grandma, Satsuki's here!
Granny!
Look, is it hers?
No, it isn't.
Thank goodness. I was sure it was hers.
Hey, Granny was jumping to conclusions.
Hey! It's not hers!
Where's she gone then?
Let's start from scratch.
We better hurry. It'll be dark soon.
I really appreciate your help, everyone.
Don't worry. Could have been any of us.
Please, help me Totoro!
Mei is lost.
It'll be dark soon.
I'm sure she's scared somewhere...
Totoro!
Totoro, Mei is lost and we can't find her!
She must be scared. Please help me find her.
I don't know what to do...
Other people can't see the bus!
FOREST-SWAMP
CEMETERY-SHRINE
Mei
Mei-chan!
The trees are moving out of the way!
Mei!
Sister!
You silly girl.
I'm sorry.
You wanted to take the corn to Mum?
Hospital
Will you take us to the hospital?
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry.
They didn't need to send a telegram just for a cold.
The girls must be worried.
I'm sorry to upset them.
They'll be fine. As long as you're okay.
We've all learned to cope.
This'll just postpone the enjoyment.
They've put up with it so well.
I'm especially sorry for Satsuki. She's been so patient.
You're right.
I'm going to spoil them for a while when I come home.
Oh no!
She's laughing!
Looks like she's fine.
Yeah!
I can't wait to get back on my feet.
Yeah.
Where did that come from?
What is it?
l thought l saw Satsuki and Mei
smiling at us from up in that tree.
It sounds crazy, but maybe you did. Look at this.
For Mother
TOTORO TOTORO TOTORO TOTORO
トトロトトロトトロトトロ
Totoro, Totoro, Totoro, Totoro.
dareka ga kossori
だれかがこっそり
Someone stealthily
komichi ni konomi uzumete
小路に木の実うずめて
buries nuts in the path.
chissana me haetara
ちっさな芽生えたら
When a tiny sprout grows,
himitsu no angou
秘密の暗号
you'll find a secret password-
mori e no PASUPOOTO
森へのパスポート
the passport to the forest.
suteki-na bouken hajimaru
すてきな冒険はじまる
A wonderful adventure begins.
tonari no
となりの
My neighbour
TOTORO TOTORO TOTORO TOTORO
トトロトトロトトロトトロ
Totoro, Totoro, Totoro, Totoro,
mori no naka ni
森の中に
who has lived in the forest
mukashi kara sunderu
むかしから住んでる
since ancient times.
tonari no TOTORO TOTORO
となりのトトロトトロ
My neighbour Totoro, Totoro,
TOTORO TOTORO
トトロトトロ
Totoro, Totoro,
kodomo no toki ni dake
子供のときにだけ
only in your childhood age,
anata ni otozureru
あなたに訪れる
can one visit you-
fushigi-na deai
不思議な出会い
a wonderous meeting.
ame furi BASU tei
雨ふりバス停
The rain falls at the bus stop,
ZUBUNURE OBAKE ga itara
ズブヌレオバケがいたら
if the spirit is drenched,
anata no amaGASA sashite agemasho
あなたの雨ガサさしてあげましょ
open your umbrella for it.
mori e no PASUPOOTO
森へのパスポート
The passport to the forest
mahou no tobira akimasu
魔法の扉あきます
opens the magic door.
tonari no TOTORO TOTORO
となりのトトロトトロ
My neighbour Totoro, Totoro,
TOTORO TOTORO
トトロトトロ
Totoro, Totoro,
tsukiyo no ban ni OKARINA fuiteru
月夜の晩にオカリナ吹いてる
plays an ocarina on moonlit nights.
tonari no TOTORO TOTORO
となりのトトロトトロ
My neighbour Totoro, Totoro,
TOTORO TOTORO
トトロトトロ
Totoro, Totoro,
moshi mo aeta nara
もしも会えたなら
if you should ever meet,
suteki-na shiawase ga
すてきなしあわせが
wonderful fortune
anata ni kuru wa
あなたに来るわ
will come to you.
The End