(Totoro-Totoro-Totoro)
MY NEIGHBOR TOTORO
Let’s walk, let’s walk
I’m fine
I like to walk
so let’s go on...
Hills, tunnels, grass...
bridges and bumpy gravel roads
crawling under spider webs
and downhill.
Let’s walk, let’s walk
I’m fine
I like to walk
so let’s go on...
Foxes and raccoons,
come out !
Let’s explore deep into the woods.
Happiness with many friends !
Father, caramel.
Oh, thanks.
Are you tired ?
Uh - uh.
It’s just a little farther.
Oh !
Mei ! Hide !
It wasn’t a policeman.
HI-I-I !
Is someone there from this house ?
Oh, thanks.
I’m Kusakabe,
we’ve arrived.
Yoroshiku Onegai Shimasu
(Thanks for your future kindness !)
Welcome !
Thanks a lot.
Well, we’ve arrived.
Wait !
Mei, there’s a bridge.
Bridge ?
Fish !
See, it flashed again.
Well, do you like it ?
Father,
it’s beautiful !
A tunnel of trees !
Ahhh..
that house ?
Hurry !
It’s pretty old.
Old !
It’s like a haunted house !
Ghosts ?
It’s rotten.
It’ll fall down,
it’ll fall down !
Mei,
- Look.. !
- Huh ?
There...
Isn’t it big ?
Achoo !...
Father,
a huge tree !
Right, it’s a camphor tree.
- A camphor tree !
An acorn !
Let me see !
Ah, another one !
I have one !
Hey, hey.
We’ve got to open up
the storm shutters.
Acorns !
There are acorns in the room.
They fell from above.
I wonder
if there are squirrels here ?
- Squirrels ?
Or maybe acorn-mice ?
What ?
No, squirrels are better.
Where do you want this ?
Ah, just a minute.
I’ll open up over here.
Satsuki,
would you open the back door ?
Okay.
-You should be able to find it.
- Mm-hm
Come on !
Wait !
Hurry up !
AHHHHHH !
- I’m going in
- Mm-hm
- The bath...
Nothing there...
That’s the bath.
Father, there’s something in here.
Squirrels ?
I don’t know.
Not cockroaches, not mice...
...black.
There were a whole bunch !
Well ?
It must be "Mak-kuro Kurosuke".
(Blackie All-Black)
Mak-kuro Kurosuke ?
Like the ones in
the picture book ?
It must be...
Ghosts wouldn’t be out
on a beautiful day like this.
When you suddenly enter a dark place
from bright sunlight...
black spots appear
in front of your eyes.
So that’s it !
MAK-KURO KUROSUKE !
COME ON OUT !
IF YOU DON’T, WE’LL PULL YOU OUT
BY YOUR EYEBALLS ! ! !
Okay, back to work.
Where are the stairs
to the second floor ?
Let’s find the stairs and
open the upstairs windows.
Okay !
Mei too !
Toilet !
Over there !
Not here !
Mei, I found it !
It’s pitch black.
Mak-Kuro Kurosuke !
An acorn !
MAK-KURO KUROSUKE,
COME OUT !
- AAAHH !
- AAAahhhh...
Mister Mak-Kuro Kurosuke,
are you here ?
Father !
There’s something in this house
after all !
That’s great !
Since Father was a boy,
I’ve wanted to live
in a haunted house !
Ooops !
Oh no !
I got one ! !  Sis ! !
Mei !
What energy !
Say hello to the neighbor-lady
who watches over this house.
She came to help us move in.
I’m Satsuki and this is
my sister, Mei.
How do you do ?
Yes, how do you do ?
What nice children.
If there had been time,
I could have cleaned up the house.
You’ve done plenty.
We’re so busy in the fields right now,
but I cleaned a little, every so often.
Mei, your hands are black !
What happened ?
Mak-kuro Kurosuke escaped !
Oh, Mei, your feet...
Oh, mine are black too !
Oh, ho...
It looks like the ‘susu-atari’
have come out.
Susu-atari ?
(Moving Soot)
Are susu-atari like this,
and move like this ?
Yes indeed...
They breed in very old
empty houses,
and make soot and dust here and there.
I could see them too, when I was young.
So, you also saw them....
Are they ghosts ?
Nothing that scary.
If you’re good, they
won’t do anything bad.
Then before you know it,
they’re gone.
They’re probably up
in the ceiling right now,
discussing whether to move out.
Mei, they’re all going to leave.
I don’t like that.
But what would you do
if they all came out at once ?
Mei not scared.
Okay then...
I won’t go with you
to the toilet at night.
Say,
would you go to the creek
and bring up some water ?
The creek ?
Mei go too.
Mei, you wait there.
Catch any fish ?
Granny, it works !
Keep pumping,
until the water runs cold.
Okay.
Oh,
it’s you.
What can I do for you ?
From Mother,
for Granny.
What is it ?
Wait ! What is this ?
Is that Kanta ?
YAH-H-H ! !
YOUR HOUSE IS HAUNTED ! ! !
KANTA !
Reminds me of when
I was a boy.
I hate boys !
But I love Granny’s o-hagi
(sweet rice cake).
Eat all you like.
Thank you for all your help.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye !
Father, this old house
will fall down.
What a problem, since we just moved in.
Everyone laugh !
So your fears will all run away.
Mei not scared.
Mei not scared !
One, two,
Keep it up,
Keep it up !
Okay, laundry is finished !
Off we go !
Granny !
Good day !
Don’t work too hard !
Where are you going ?
To the hospital to visit mother !
That’s nice !
Say hello for me !
Okay !
Oh, this way, this way !
Good day.
Welcome.
MOTHER !
Mei,
it’s good to see you !
Father took the wrong road.
Really ?
Welcome.
Today is the Harvest Holiday.
Oh, so that’s it.
Father’s talking with the doctor.
I’m so happy you all came.
How’s the new house ?
Are you settled in ?
What ?
- A haunted house ?
- Mm-hm.
Mother, do you like
haunted houses ?
Of course.
I’d like to meet a ghost.
- That’s good. Right, Mei ?
- Mm-hm
We were worried. If Mother were scared,
we wouldn’t know what to do.
And Satsuki and Mei ?
I like it !
Mei not scared !
Is Satsuki doing Mei’s hair ?
Uh-huh.
You’re good at it.
Isn’t that nice, Mei ?
Uh-huh, but Sis gets really mad.
That’s because Mei never keeps still.
Satsuki,
come here.
Isn’t it too short ?
I like it this way.
- Mei too, Mei too !
- Wait your turn.
Unruly as always, isn’t it.
Exactly like mine
when I was your age.
When I grow up, will my hair
be just like Mother’s ?
Probably,
since you’re just like
I used to be.
Mother’s looking good, isn’t she ?
Yes. The doctor was saying she’ll be
able to leave the hospital soon.
Soon ? Tomorrow ?
There she goes again with ’tomorrow’.
Tomorrow is probably too soon, though.
Mother says she wants to
sleep together with Mei again.
But you’re a big girl now.
Weren’t you going to
sleep by yourself ?
With mother is okay.
Father,
it’s morning !
Hey,
WAKE UP ! !
Sorry, I overslept again.
Today, I’m making the bento
(lunch boxes).
Darn, I completely forgot.
It’s okay. I’ll make everyone’s.
It’s burning !
Hold on !
This one is Mei’s.
Mei’s -- ?
Mei, sit quietly and eat.
-- Yep.
Here. Wrap it yourself, okay ?
Satsuki-chan !
Oh, no !
OKAYYYY ! !
You made a friend already ?
She called you ’Satsuki-chan’.
Her name is Mit-chan.
( Michiko )
Gochiso-sama.
("That was delicious -- Thank you")
I’ll be going.
Have a nice day.
’Morning.
Hurry, let’s go.
Mm-hm.
Father !
Does Mei look like Sis ?
Mm-hm. Where are you going
with your lunch ?
Just over there.
Father, is it time for lunch ?
What, already ?
Father is a florist, okay ?
Tadpoles !
Ah, bottom’s gone.
Found one !
Who are you ?
Mak-Kuro Kurosuke ?
To -
To - Ro -
To - Ro - Ro
(Troll)
To -
To - ro -
To - ro - ro
Totoro !
Your name is Totoro, right ?
So...it’s Totoro, after all...
Totoro...
- ’Bye.
- See you later.
I’m home.
Welcome.
Oh, is it that time already ?
Where’s Mei ?
I’m going over to Mit-chan’s house.
We haven’t had lunch yet.
Isn’t she playing in the garden ?
Mei !
MEI ! ! !
Father !
I found Mei’s hat.
Mei -- Mei ! !
MEI ! Wake up !
You can’t sleep
in a place like this !
- Where’s Totoro ?
- Totoro ?
But...but...
Were you dreaming ?
- Totoro was here.
You mean ’Tororo’ that was
in the picture book ?
Uh-huh.
He said he was Totoro.
With fur...
and a mouth like this.
One like this...
and one about like this...
and a B-I-G-G-G one
like this, sleeping !
There you are.
Hey, how great !
Just like a secret hideaway.
Father ! Mei says she met Totoro here.
- Totoro ?
- Mm-hm.
Over here !
Hey, wait !
Here ?
Nuh-uh.
Before he was by a big tree.
But there was only one pathway...
Mei -- let’s go home.
I said... Mei !
It’s true !
There really was Totoro !
Not a lie.
Mei...
It not lie.
Uh...
Father and Satsuki don’t
think you’re a liar.
Mei must have met the
keeper of the forest.
That means good fortune is with you.
But you can’t see him all the time.
Say, we haven’t offered a proper greeting yet.
Greeting ?
Let’s go to Tsukamori !
(Shrine of Forest Gods)
Mei’s gotten so heavy.
Father, that camphor tree.
Isn’t it huge ?
There it is !
- That tree ?
-Yeah !
Father, hurry. Hurry !
The hole is gone.
- Was this really the place ?
- Yeah
She says the hole is gone.
Well, you can’t see him
all the time.
We’ll see him again ?
I want to meet him too.
Well, if good fortune is with you.
Isn’t this a beautiful tree ?
Since long, long ago it’s been here...
Back then, mankind and trees were friends.
Father saw this tree and
fell in love with that house.
I’m sure Mother will like it too.
Well, let’s get back home.
We have to eat our lunch.
Oh yeah. I was supposed
to go to Mit-chan’s.
Mei go too.
Attention !
Thank you for taking care of Mei.
From this moment on, ’Onegai itashimasu’
(We humbly beg your favor)
Onegai itashimasu.
(Humbly wishing for future goodwill)
A race to the house !
- Cheater !
- Yeah !
Wait !
Hurry !
Wait ! !
Today I have wonderful news.
Mei met the spirit, Totoro.
I’m thinking it would be wonderful
to meet him too.
Kanta !
If you don’t hurry,
you’ll be late !
Uh-huh...
There !
Mei... ?
- Teacher ?
- Yes, Satsuki ?
Um...My younger sister...
Granny.. Mei... ?
Well, she says she wants
to go where you are,
and she won’t listen.
But -- Mei !
Today is Father’s day
at the university
and you promised to be a good girl
and stay with Granny.
I have two more hours,
and Granny’s busy too.
She was a good girl
all day, right ?
Granny, I’ll go and speak
with the teacher.
Satsuki’s mother is in the hospital
and it’s rather difficult right now.
Class, we’ll do all we can
to help, right ?
Right !
What’s that ?
It’s Totoro !
Shhhhh. You have to be quiet.
Mm-hm.
Tell them I’m going to
skip the club today.
Okay, I’ll tell the teacher.
See you later.
- See you later.
- Bye, Bye.
Mei, let’s hurry ! It looks like rain.
Mm-hm !
Ah, here it comes !
Mei won’t cry. Is she a big girl ?
Mm-hm...
...but what a problem !
Jizo-san,
Please let us share your roof
for a little while.
But...
- Good thing. Right, Sis ?
- Mm-hm
It’s got holes.
Father didn’t take an umbrella.
Mei go to meet him too.
...and that’s why I forgot it !
What dummy would forget his umbrella
when it’s raining ?
That hurts !
You were probably swinging it around
and broke it.
I didn’t !
Excuse me.
Oh, Satsuki. And Mei-chan, too.
Granny !
Thank you for today.
You’re welcome; it wasn’t much.
Um, Kanta lent us his umbrella.
Really ? That kid !
It’s such a beat up old umbrella.
Mei was with me, so it really saved us.
But Kanta got all wet...
Thank you very much.
That’s all right.
He’s always so dirty anyway --
he must have gotten a little bit cleaner.
Are you going to meet your father ?
Yes.
How thoughtful.
- Mei-chan, bye bye.
- Bye, bye.
Who came ?
I don’t know.
Here it comes.
Are you getting on ?
All right, driver.
Father wasn’t on it.
It’ll be the next bus for sure.
Does Mei want to wait
at Granny’s house ?
(A Shinto shrine
to Inari-san, the fox-god)
What’s wrong ?
Mei...
Are you sleepy ?
That’s why I told you...
Want to go to Granny’s house now ?
Hold on, it’s just a little longer...
The bus is sure late...
Here...
Totoro ?...
Ah, just a minute.
I’ll lend you this.
Hurry, Mei will fall.
Use it like this.
The bus is coming.
Totoro... took father’s umbrella.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
Departure. All right.
The train was late and
I missed the bus.
Were you worried ?
It came !
Father, it came ! It came !
A cat, a cat bus !
Really huge !
With eyes like this !
It was wonderful !
We met him, we met him !
We met Totoro !
It was fantastic !
Mother, it feels like
my heart is still racing.
It was a fantastic, strange, wonderful day.
And the gift Totoro gave us
was wonderful too.
It was a bamboo-leaf package,
tied with a dragon’s whisker.
When we got home, we opened it...
and inside were nuts.
If our garden became a forest,
it would be beautiful,
so we planted them.
But... they just won’t grow.
Every day, Mei says ’Still nothing,
there’s still nothing’.
She’s just like the crab
of the monkey-crab fable.
It will soon be summer vacation.
Please hurry up and get well, Mother.
-- Satsuki.
Okay, okay.
- I’m going to turn it off.
- Wait --
Father, I wonder if they’ll
come up tomorrow ?
I wonder. Totoro would probably know.
Good night.
Mei !
- That's where we planted the seeds.
- Mm-hm.
Hooray! We did it, we did it!
Mei, we’re the wind !
There’s no tree.
We did it !
It was a dream
-- but it wasn’t a dream !
It was a dream--
We did it !
Mr. Kusakabe, telegram.
Mr. Kusakabe,
It’s a telegram.
Nobody home ?
Granny !
Over here.
This one’s ready to eat.
Granny, this one ?
It’s ripe.
Granny’s garden is like
a treasure-hill.
Say, let’s take a little rest.
They’re nice and cold.
Itadakimasu.
(Blessing: ‘I will receive’)
It’s delicious !
Is it ?
They’ve gotten a lot of Mr. Sun,
so they’re also good for you.
For Mother’s sickness, too ?
Of course.
If you eat Granny’s vegetables,
you’ll get really healthy fast.
Mother’s coming home this Saturday.
She will sleep with Mei.
So she’s finally leaving the hospital.
Uh-uh. It’s not for good.
She’ll return to the hospital on Monday.
It seems they’re going to
release her gradually.
Is that right ?
Then we’re going to have to
get her to eat more and more.
The corn Mei picked,
Mei will give to Mother.
- That will make her so happy.
- Mm-hm !
A telegram. Nobody was home,
so we accepted it for you.
For our house ?
Granny, Father won’t be home until evening.
Open it. It might be an emergency.
Mm-hm.
P-l-e-a-s-e re-ply, shi-chi-koku-yama...
Shichikokuyama Hospital !
It’s from Mother’s Hospital !
Something’s happened to Mother !
Granny, what shall I do ?
We have to answer !
Calm down, calm down.
Do you know where your father is ?
I know the telephone number of
the research department,
but we don’t have a phone.
Kanta, take her to your uncle’s.
- Let her use the phone.
- Mm-hm
Mei, you stay with me.
Mei, you stay with Granny !
Hello, long distance please.
Tokyo 31-1382.
Yes.
Isn’t she cute, Kanta ?
Hello... Yes.
Hello, is this the
Archaeology Research Department ?
Father, uh, Mr. Kusakabe please.
This is Satsuki Kusakabe... All right.
Oh Father, it’s Satsuki.
Yes, what is it ?
Uh-huh...
From the hospital ?
I’ll call the hospital right away.
Did something happen with Mother ?
What shall I do, Father ?
Don’t worry.
As soon as I find out what it’s all about,
I’ll call you.
Ask them to let you wait there.
Mm-hm.
I’m going to hang up now.
Granny, may I wait here ?
Father will call back.
Of course. Rest awhile.
Sis !
No way ! This corn is for Mother.
I said, no way ! I’m giving this to Mother.
Mei, It seems Mother’s not feeling well...
so they’re delaying her home visit.
No !
It can’t be helped.
If she rushes it and gets worse,
what’ll we do ?
No !
Mei, it’s just a short postponement.
Then it’s okay if Mother dies,
is that right ?
NO !
Mei, you dummy ! I’m not
talking to you anymore !
Let’s go.
Sis is a dummy !
Let’s put away the laundry.
Don’t be so sad, eh ?
Granny’s come to help, so cheer up.
Your father’s at the hospital...
They say your mother just has a cold...
She’ll be home next Saturday.
It was just like this last time.
Just a short stay at the hospital.
A little cold.
What will we do if Mother dies ?
But, Satsuki-chan...
Maybe Mother’ll...
It’s okay, it’s okay.
Who would die and leave such nice children ?
Don’t cry, don’t cry.
Granny will be here till
your father comes home, okay ?
Mei-chan !
Mei !
Did Mei come home ?
You didn’t see her at the bus stop ?
No.
Funny...
...where could she have gone ?
A little while ago, we had a fight.
Because Mei’s a...
That kid !
I wonder if she went to Mother’s hospital ?
The Shichikokuyama Hospital ?
Why, it would take even an adult
at least three hours to walk there.
I’m going to look.
Kanta !
Hurry and call your father !
Mei-chan has disappeared !
Darn Mei ! She’s always getting lost.
MEI !
Excuse me, Mister.  Uhh...
Good day. Did a little girl pass by
on this road ? My little sister.
Hmmmm... a little girl ?
I would remember if I saw someone...
I wonder if it was another road ?
Are you sure she came this way ?
I don’t know.
MEI !
Stop, please !
You fool ! That’s dangerous !
I’m looking for my little sister.
Did you see a little girl ?
Your little sister ?
I think she’s on her way
to the Shichikokuyama Hospital.
Four years old, a little girl.
Ryoko, did you see anyone ?
Uh-uh...
We came from Shichikokuyama,
but we didn’t see anyone like that.
Well... thank you.
Where did you come from ?
From Matsu-go.
Matsu-go ?
Isn’t there some mistake ?
Well, bye.
Satsuki !
Kan-chan !
Find her ?
No. How about you ?
Right now Dad and the others are searching.
I’ll go to Shichikokuyama for you.
You go home.
Mei tried to get to the hospital
and got lost on the way, I’m sure.
Satsuki, a while ago, they
found a sandal in the pond.
We don’t know for sure whether
it belongs to Mei !
Did you find her ?
Namo Amida Buddha, Namo Amida Buddha...
(I place my faith in Amida Buddha)
The mud’s deeper over there !
Try there first !
Hey, got another pole ?
Granny, Satsuki-chan’s coming !
Granny !
This...this is it.
It’s not Mei’s.
Thank heaven...
I thought for sure it was Mei-chan’s.
What, Granny jumped to conclusions ?
Hey, it was a mistake !
Where could she have gone ?
We’ll have to start over again.
We’ll have to hurry.
It’ll be dark soon.
Thanks, everyone.
Let’s split up and search some more.
Please... !
Let me through to Totoro’s den.
Mei’s lost.
It’ll be dark soon -- and that kid,
she’s lost somewhere.
Totoro !
Totoro, Mei’s lost !
I’ve searched all over, but I can’t find her.
Please -- find Mei.
I’m sure she’s crying somewhere right now.
I don’t know what to do !
Everyone can’t see it !
’MEI’
Mei-chaaannnnn....
The trees are leaning out of the way !
(Statues of Jizo, Protector of Travelers
and Savior of Children)
Mei !
Sis !
You dummy !
I’m sorry !
You wanted to bring that corn
to Mother ?
’SHICHIKOKUYAMA HOSPITAL’
You’ll take us to the hospital ?
Thank you !
I’m sorry.
It’s just a little cold, and the hospital
had to go and send a telegram.
The kids are sure to be worried.
They shouldn’t have done it.
Nah, the kids will be relieved
when they hear.
We’ve all come this far....
Our good times are just put off
for a little while, that’s all.
Those kids have to put up with so much.
Satsuki’s such a sensitive child,
I feel sorry for her.
You’re right.
When I get home I plan to really spoil them.
Hey, hey...
Mother’s laughing.
- She looks okay.
- Uh-huh.
Ah, I’ve got to hurry and get well.
Yes...
...what ?
Who could it be ?
What’s the matter ?
Just now, in the pine tree,
I thought I spied Mei and Satsuki, laughing.
It could be. Look !
‘ TO MOTHER ’
Someone secretly buries
a nut in the path...
...and when a little sprout grows,
the secret message is
the passport to the forest.
A wonderful journey will begin !
My neighbor To-to-ro Totoro
To-to-ro Totoro
living in the forest
since long ago,
My neighbor To-to-ro Totoro
To-to-ro Totoro...
...only in childhood can one visit you...
...a magical, mysterious meeting.
Raining at the bus stop,
if there’s a sopping-wet spirit,
let it under your umbrella.
The passport to the forest...
...the magical door will open.
My neighbor To-to-ro Totoro
To-to-ro Totoro...
...blows upon its ocarina
on the night of the moon.
My neighbor To-to-ro Totoro
To-to-ro Totoro...
if you ever meet it,
wonderful fortune will come to you.
The End