Do you want subtitles for any video?-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Whoa whoawhoa whoa!
Stop dumping.Stop dumping.
- What is matter?- Lower your bed.
You can't dump here no more.You need to talk to your boss.
Always we aredumping here.
Caballero, put the shitback in your truck.
What?That is huge job!
Where I am supposedto be dumping this now?
I just now find out it's asbestosyou've been dumping over there.
What did youthink it was?
I never asked.
Tampax-- What thefuck do I know?
Well, now you know.
You and your friend there stefanohave been pocketing how much
On this cowboys-And-Indianasbestos removal?
Billing the townships
Like you're followingalthe epa regulations.
You got the same scam, Phil, so whydon't we cut through the bullshit?
How much you figureyou're owed on this?
- 25%.- Don't be an asshole.
You know, there's close monitoringat every fucking landfill.
Maybe if somebody had beenupfront with me from the beginning.
Nobody's been hiding nothing. I had thesame dumping deal with what's-His-Name,
The operation's manager since I'vebeen there at barone sanitation.
You're not thereno more. I am.
You're enjoying yourgenerous severance package.
25%-- That's notgonna happen.
You've got a backyard,a pool, dump it there.
That's my onlyother suggestion.
He's got us by the gazz'.I'll tell you that.
Unless that guy at the pennsylandfill decides to play ball.
That asshole's shitting his pantshe'll get pinched by the epa.
Frankly, Ton',
I'm thinking maybe weshould meet Phil's number.
Why? I think that would set aterrible precedent right now.
Just bend over...
when he just became bossof the family over there?
Yeah, well,that's the flying ointment.
Even still,I say let him have it.
Life's too short.
It's also too short tolive it as a fucking lackey.
True too.
What is this,"make-Believe ballroom"?
How many times you gonnachange the stations?
This "departed" soundtrack'sfucking killer.
- You got it?- Yeah, it's good.
Regarding, Phil,I gotta ask:
Whatever happened to"stop and smell the roses"?
You're right.
U're right.
You can't fight everyfucking battle, right?
Asbestos...
each day's a gift.
Every time I look at mykid, that's what I realiz
And that shitwith Junior, please.
Just that peoplike Phil,
They're noton that page--
Take those rosesand stick 'em upyour ass, thorns first.
- This system'sgot no balls.
So how was your partythat day at the hous
Slow the fuck down,will ya?!
Maybe you shgo back, heidi.
Kennedy, I'm on mylearner's permit after dark.
Ton'...
you gotta...help me.
I'm coming.
I'll never passthe drug test.
What?
You gotta get me out.
I'll lose my license.
Never pass a drug test.
Call me a taxi.
911.
We've beenin an accident.
Old pumping station road...
past the reservoir.
Sorry about that.
My friend...
guy I came with,how is he?
Your friend is dead.Paramedics called it in the ambulance.
Breathe in, please. Hold it.
Do you know a contact numberfor his next of kin?
His wife.
- Hello.- Hello, may I speak with Carmela Soprano?
- Who is this?- Nurse al rosario,
St. Clare's hospital, denville.Is mrs. Soprano there?
Yes, this ismrs. Soprano.
I'm here with your husband.He'd like to speak with you.
- Carm.- Tony, is everything okay?
Are you sitting down?
- I'm serious.- Yes, I'm in bed.
All right, listen.
Sweetheart,there's been an accident.
We were coming backfrom the city and...
- Christopher's dead.- Oh my God!
All right.
- Carm.- What happened?
He drove off the roadand the car flipped over.
- I'll tell you in detail.- Are you okay?
I just banged my knee,the one from high school.
I'm fine, but...
he wasn't wearinga belt.
Where are you,St. Clare's?
Listen, they're gonna callkelli if they haven't already...
just get al and ritaon the phone
And get 'em startedover there.
All right, all right.Oh my God, Tony, he's dead?
Yeah.
All right.L-Let me get dressed.
Thank you.
Mr. Tony,Mr. Sil is here.
Okay.
- Mrs. Carmela say you should stay in bed.- Have him come up.
We're right here, Ton'.
We came as soonas we heard.
- Ton'.- Patsy went over to Chrissy's mom's house.
- Yeah, that's where Carmela is.- Carlo's coming up.
Yeah.
- How you doing, Ton'?- My knee got banged up.
They said it'sprobably gonna be okay.
Last thingI remember was...
we pulled awayfrom Phil.
Skid marks all over theplace, the cops told Carm.
He had a heavy foot,that kid, always.
Almost put me througha billboard one time.
- Hey, Ton'.- Come on in.
I'm so sorry, Ton'.
I still can'tbelieve it.
Thanks. I knowyou two were close.
I was makingmy collections
And Anthony maffeicalled me. Jesus.
It's carlo, I bet.
Fucking idiot didn't evenhave his seat belt on.
His chest filled up.
Suffocatedon his own blood.
- Oh, Jesus.- Jesus Christ.
Seems like that'sthe cause of death.
It's not carlo.I heard AJ.
Carlo's coming up?
What's with you and carlfucking arrival?
- I'm just saying.- They're gonna do a full blood test on him.
See, you know,
If alcohol,
- Drugs or...- It did occur to me.
He didn't seem high,did he?
Are you kidding?I would have been furi
I would have fuckingstrangled him.
He'd been working the programever since he threw little Paulie
- Out that window.- Let's not go there.
Even before thathe was battling that shit.
He gave it his all.
Well, anyway,he's gone now,
Our Chrissy.
Crazy fucking maniac.
The thing to taketo heart, t,
You're here.You're all right.
You could have been killed,for ck's sake.
What are you gonna do?
Thanks.
Whoa.What are you doing?
No no no, I gottatry and get up.
Gotta go and meet Carmover at Chrissy's.
Kelli and all that.
I'll make youa plate.
- Get me a scotch.- Are you serious?
Yeah, and haveone yourself.
They were close,two cousins.
You all right?
I know I had mydifferences with that kid,
But maybe I didn'tdo right by him, neither.
If you were his dad,I was his dutch uncle,
And what the fuck didI do but get pissed off,
Fight with him overcocksucking fucking money?
I'd break his balls whenhe ied not to have a drink
Or a little tasteof snow.
It's over, Paulie.
Did anybody ever hearfrom the hospital?
I was waitingtill kelli woke up.
They found cocainein his blood.
- Madonn'.- 'Cause of death was a hemothorax.
Yeah, airbags can crush the ribswhen there's no other restraint.
They said he mighthave made it,
But he didn't.
Couldn't have wornhis goddamn seat belt?
- No wonder. He waswhack-A-Doo. - Al, just stop it.
Aw, baloney. He leavesour granddaughter fatherless.
My only child!
Drinking won't help,honey.
Jesus Christ.
Look at this.Syracuse is losing.
I don't knowwhat to say.
- What?- I just got a call from little Paulie.
Nucci gualtieri died.
Stroke on the bus backto the home.
They had goneto see "Jersey boys."
This is difficult.
This is pain
Like I'm not used to.
We've said before he waslike a son in some ways.
To see him dielike that...
practicallyin my arms.
He was just startinghis life.
Yeah.
You know what?
- This is bullshit.- What?
I haven't been ableto tell anybody this, but...
I'm fucking relieved.
Really?
He was a tremendous dragon my emotions,
On my... thoughtsabout the future.
Every morningI wake up thinking,
"Is today the day thatone of my best friends
Is gonna dime meto the FBI?"
And a weak,fucking sniveling,
Lying drug addict? That'sthe worst kind of bet.
The biggest blunderof my career
Is now gone.
And I don't have to beconfronted by that fact no more.
And as a relative,a friend,
Someone you cancount on...
I see.
Let me tell yousomething:
I've murdered friendsbefore, even relatives--
My cousin Tony,
My best friend--Puss.
But this...
was I talkingin my sleep?
Snoring.
I'm gonna put on the TVif you don't mind.
I can't stay asleepeither. I'm all...
I mean, I can laugh and cry,and I could always get the part.
- First time?- First time. Never can keep it.
They got onto meafter a while.
I'd lose my voice, falldown, get red in the face,
Talk too fastand couldn't act.
Can you make mea cappuccino?
That fucking machine from Paulie,you need a pilot's license.
It's so hard not to think ofChristopher as a child, isn't it?
Caity kind of looks likeim,which makes it doubly hard
Of course that's notgonna do her any favors
When she hits puberty--That schnoz.
A lot of womenfound him very attractive.
I think to myself,
How could I have ever saidthose things about him,
About him and adriana, whather mother said he did to her?
Obviously he was violent as an adult.
His upbringing,but he adored Ade.
He could never lethimself take her life.
Why are weso quick to blame?
What isthe attraction in that?
It's good.
Thank you.
When I called you...
the night afterthe accident,
And you asked me,
"Oh my God, Tony,he's dead?"
Yeah.
And I thought--
Well, I thoughtI picked up a twinge of...
- relief.- What?
It just seemed like--I don't know--
How could you say that? You don'tknow what you're talking about.
Okay, good, I'm wrong.
Maybe if you did pick upsomething like that,
Maybe it's becauseI warelieved...
that it was himand not you.
Well, don't feel bad aboutthat. That makes sense.
To be going downto the hospital again
At 2:00 in the morning?
And you know what?When you were shot,
It was Christopherwho held me.
You knowthe baby's car seat?
A giant tree branchcame through the window
And demolished it.
She would havebeen dead, caitlin,
Mangled beyondrecognition.
I told her aboutthe baby seat
So she wouldn'tfeel so rotten.
I mean, he was high as a fuckingkite. I didn't tell her that.
In retrospect,maybe not the best approach.
Right,I'm the asshole... again.
What?
No, go ahead.
It's amazinghow things work.
His mother,cousin joanne,
A lush.
Totally abandoned himas a parent,
But now she's reapingall the sympathy
And the tears.
How are you doing,Anthony?
There have beensome hard moments.
But a weak,lying drug at
Who fantasizedabout my downfall,
Who even showed peoplehis filthy thoughts
On a movie screen...?
Let me tell you something:I've seen friends die before,
Accidents,
Even murder.
My cousin Tony,they shot his face away.
And I was fuckingprostate with grief.
But this?
I see.
And it occurs to me,I hand-Carried this kid
Through the worstcrisis he ever had.
I can't gointo particulars, but...
wives, girlfriends,
They can complicate lifein a major way.
I don't have totell you that.
Anyway, huge problemof his own making.
And he cried.He couldn't deal with it.
So...
I took up the slack.I handled it.
I felt sorryfor him.
Now he talked gratitude...
but guess what pyproduces in the recipient.
They shiton your pity.
That's what brokethe camel's back.
How are youhandling all this?
The worst part,truthfully,
Is I gotta sit there
Withplewho are hurting... bad.
And I gotta havethe long face
And the sighingand the platitudes.
But I don't feel it.
Then that makes me feellike a hypocrite.
And that makesme mad at them.
Oh, hi.
How are you?
Julianna skiffle,
This is my wifeCarmela Soprano.
Skiff.
Oh, yeah, right.
Julianna's a real estateagent in the old neighborhood.
And you knewChristopher?
I used to buy my meatat Satriale's.
I'm a recovering addict.
- I owe him a lot.- That's nice to hear.
- Well, what are you gonna do, huh?- Nothing you can do.
That's my point.
He was too young.
Good-Looking woman.
They dida beautiful job on him.
Oh, I'm gonna go up.
I'll go up later,
Give my seat to someonein the meantime.
How are you doing?
- It's tough.- Yeah.
He loved y so much.
- Yeah?- Well, you know he did.
I'll go up later.
There she is.3 to 5, 7 to 9.
Why do they call her that?
She nevermisses a wake.
Oh, lord, oh, lord!
FuckingJames brown now.
I'm serious.I can't take it.
It's all right.We're here for you.
Oh my God.Look at this.
- Like a movie star.- Jackie kennedy.
- I'm sorry for the loss of your cousin, bro.- Thanks.
Me too, bro, me too.
He was a good guy.
Hey, don't letthis linger
On your head now.
You know whatI'm talking about.
You know that night,
A tree limb came inthrough the car window,
Completely destroyedthe baby seat.
Tony.
You guys are gonnahang in a while, right?
We really should make anappearance at the other wake.
Are we that late?
Glad you came.
- He'll appreciate it.- Oh, please.
I gottaget out of here.
- Paul.- Ton'.
Thanks for coming.
We are so sorryfor your loss, Paulie.
How you hangin' in,paolucc'?
As well as can be expected.
Must be veryhard for you.
I know how close the twoof you had become again
Yeah.
Not muchof a sendoff here.
- The room is beautiful, Paulie.- Nobody's in it.
What kindof testament is this
To the spirit andgenerosity of the woman?
We're herefor you, Paulie.
You know that.
Okay.
It's a fundamentallack of respect
And I'm never gonnafuckin' forget it, neither.
Jesus, Paulie, people yourmother's age, their friends die off.
What, she outlivedsil? Carlo?
They're all over thereat your nephew's.
- Yeah, but-- - Councilmancarillo was here three minutes.
I clocked him.
People are comin'and they don't, fuck 'em.
I got 500 prayer cards.
Well, Carm and I aere.
What the fuckis that? Nothin'?
No, Ton', of course not.
- Means the world.- Okay.
She suffered too,you know.
Yeah, well, this isn'tthe time or the place.
You're right.
How have you beendealing witht?
It's really sad but it'skinda the same as with blanca.
I mean, I don't really just keepthinking about things the way I did--
Over and over,you know?
Well, for one thing,perhaps the meds are working.
Did you finally enroll?
I'm in a few classes
Unofficially, until mytranscript clears from ramapo.
Beginning english.
Oh, and I wentto a class on the history
Of the israeli-Palestinianconflict.
- Wow.- I mean, it's hard to pick up in the middle.
I might take itxt semester.
I mean, it's sodicked-Up over there
And no one knowswho started it.
- Are you sleeping?- What? In class?
No. You were havingtrouble, remember?
Wellbutrin xlkicks ass.
I'm hearing good thingsabout the lexapro.
Check it, paisan.Long John shithead.
That kid's in mysouth American lit class.
He had his toes amputated.
He said it was an accidentwith his car battery.
Acid burned rightthrough his shoe.
Oh, you littshfooyadell.
She should nurse.
At least somebodyfeels like eating.
She doesn't know.
Isn't God wonderfulthat way?
- Hello?- Alan, it's Tony. You busy?
Usual shit--Some Japanese guy
Got his suit ruinedat cirque du soleil.
- Listen, I need a suite.- So all the guys coming out?
No no. I'm solo.
Oh. We'll see whatwe can do about that.
Look, I just want to-Peace and quiet...
- ...chill out.- You set for transpo?
I'll be happyto send a plane.
No more bets.
33 black odd.
Five red odd.
It's hard to imaginefor a poet,
But wordsworthwas as rich and popular
As, say, someone like
John grisham nowadays.
But wordsworth writes
"The world istoo much with us."
Later, he invokesnature again.
Why such strong wordsagainst the material world?
That was fast.
The gatehouseusually gives
Shitty directions tothe east tower. Come in.
So...
you're a friendof Chris.
Yeah...Tony, by the way.
No, I know.
He's mentioned you,actually.
Well, I heard nothingbut nice things about you.
Except... you're morebeautiful than he let on.
- Really?- Talked about ya...
a few times, told me morethan once to look you up.
Did he?
Well well well.
You want a drinkor something?
I got some pinot grigioin the fridge.
I got some, uh...
serious news.
- Uh-Oh.- It's about Christopher.
- He's dead.- At?
It was a car accident,
Happeneda couple days ago.
Oh my God.
That's fucking awful.
I'm sorry.
- What happened?- Bad wreck...
high-Speed...
he was killed instantly.
Somehow, I walked away.
Jesus, that musthave been scary.
The fuckin' sound alone...
did he ever...
marry that one girl--The one wh-
No.
Found a real sweetheart,though-- Kelli--
And...
they just hada baby girl.
Maybe that's good,you know?
I mean,bad that he left her,
But good that he--He left something.
I thoughtyou should know.
Well, um...
extremely cool, you comingover here. I appreciate that.
- How long you here for?- I don't know.
Just play it as I go.
- What's up?- It's stefano.
Look, I'm sorry to bother you,but I'm here at the school.
The asbestos,it's backing up.
I've gotta dumpthis shit.
It's not wrapped to code andall the other violations--
- Yeah?- I could get nailed big time.
We're workin' on it, John.
I'm tryingto negotiate it out,
But the asshole'staking a hard line for now.
Just hang in there,let me do my thing.
All right.
- Whoa.- Jeff'll clean it up.
Make him clean itin his bare feet.
I got the venison steaks!
Oh!
What the fuck?You blind?
Me?! You open the door,you don't look at all.
Aw, shit, you wreckedmy fuckin' door.
- You did that to your own door!- Whoa whoa whoa.
What the fuckdid you say?
I said he opened the door,he don't look at all.
Look at my fuckin' bike!
- Do you hear this guy?- You saw it!
Fuck you, nigger.
I am not a nigger!
I am from somalia!I go to school and I work!
Do not call mea nigger!
So you're someterrorist piece of shit.
Either way, motherfucker,you're in the wrong neighborhood.
Get the fuck away!
You a tough nigger now?!
You got something to say?
Cocksucker!
Do you mind?
No, knock yourself out.
This is the--
This is the new shit--
Medical-Grade, mellow,
Paranoia-Free.
Oh, well, that's good.
Oh, Chris lovedto party.
What's your point?
Nothing.You just...
remind meof him, obviously.
What's that mean?I fuck like him?
So muchfor paranoia-Free.
No, you were hisfriend, that's all.
Why would youbring him up?
All I'm saying
Is that there'sa certain kind of guy
That I don't run intoon campus.
But where I dance--
That accent,the clothes.
I'm a type?
This coming from the girl who'sstripping her way through college?
Actually,you're a surprise.
Chris sometimes talkedabout some sad shit,
But you seem--I don't know--
Actually sad.
Not right now I'm not.
Jesus, this is somepretty fucking amazing dope.
Chris said you two...
took peyote together.
Yeah.
I mean, I haven't donebuttons in a while, though.
You know, I've been thinkingwhy the fuck I'm here.
You can getto that place.
No. No, I mean Vegas.
Truth is I always wantedto try that shit...
but I always had
All the responsibilities.
You're a hard manto reach.
Nobody's seen hidenor hair.
Yeah, I'm away.What do you want?
What do I want?I'm returning your call.
I think this got nothingto do with asbestos.
Why don't you let go of theold shit and be a businessman?
- You got everything you want.- Not everything.
But listen, allow meto express my condolences
Regarding your nephew.
This is me hanging up.
- I can tell you're upset.- Big fucking deal.
- What exactly happened this week?- Nothing.
You know, people walk aroundlike this is all something.
They'rfucking laughing
And nobody takeseven one second
To think aboutwhat's really going on.
You sounddepressed again.
How can anybody not be?You'd have to be fucking nuts
Not to be.
I mean, you'd have to haveyour head wedged so far
Up your ass that allyou could see
Is your own stupid face.
What specificallyare you talking about?
I mean, everythingis so fucked up.
Why can't we alljust get along?
You don't have tochew it.
You just wash it downlike a pill.
It's the same principleas the solar system.
No more bets.
- 24.- Yes.
Nice.
Press it all.
No more bets.
20.
Holy fucking shit.
Here.
Much appreciated.
No more bets.
24 again.
- He's dead.- What?
What?
I get it.
I get it!