The Empire is gone, Mando.
This asset
<i>I had to ensure its delivery.</i>
He's not a local warlord.
He's Imperial.
I'm in.
<i>Our secrecy is our survival.
<i>Our strength was once in our numbers.</i>
Now, we live in the shadows.
Our world was shattered by the Empire.
You're going
This is the Way.
In the wake of your destruction
Is it still a hunter?
No. But it will protect.
You got a real thing for droids
I got a real thing for that droid.
Let me take the child to him...
Let's kill him and get out of here.
- We both need the client to be eliminated.
As long as the Imp lives
<i>It's a trap.</i>
<i>- Have they brought the child?</i>
<i>You have something I want.</i>
Kuiil? Are you there?
In a few moments...
<i>Kuiil! Are you there?</i>
It will be mine.
Speeder bikes have arrived
Awaiting confirmation.
Knock it off!
Waiting for confirmation
<i>That's a go to proceed
<i>The Moff just touched down and already
Standing by.
Did he just say
Oh, who knows?
These guys like to lay down the law
You know how it is.
I said, shut up. Yeesh.
What is that thing, anyway?
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe Moff wants to eat it.
Can I see it?
Did you not just hear
a dozen of his own troopers
- Okay.
- Do you get the point?
Okay.
Should we offer
You just wanna look at it.
So what?
Barely.
I mean, I grabbed it up off the ground
It's more than I got to see it.
Look, I'm not taking it out of
- Fine.
Let me check on this thing. This is crazy.
Any update yet?
<i>That's a negative.
<i>He just killed an officer
<i>- so this might take a while.</i>
Thank you.
Standing by still. Unbelievable.
Hey, how long has it been
I don't know
Uh, it's been
Oh, my God.
Shouldn't we check
You hit it pretty hard.
You just wanna see it.
We should check
The last thing that you want
and have him open it
Okay. Okay, look.
Take a peek. Everything's fine.
What is that?
I don't know.
A pet? I thought you...
Serves you right.
Stop that.
Identify yourself!
I am IG-11.
I am this child's nurse droid and require
A nurse droid?
I thought it was a hunter.
Yeah, well
I'm sorry, nurse
Are you refusing my request?
No.
I'm telling you to get out of here.
Hey.
That was unpleasant.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
Is there another way out?
No, that's it.
- What about the sewers?
The Mandalorians
If we can get down there
Yeah, sewers are good.
Checking for access points.
What the hell are they waiting for?
Hold up.
They're setting up an E-Web.
It's over.
I found the sewer vent.
Let's get the hell out of here.
It's assembled!
- Blow it.
Get out of the way!
Your astute panic suggests
I would prefer to avoid
and encourage a moment of consideration.
Members of my escort
of an E-Web heavy repeating blaster.
If you are unfamiliar with this weapon
I am sure that Republican Shock Trooper
will advise you that she has witnessed
facing the predecessor
Or perhaps the decommissioned
has heard the songs
when gunships outfitted
laid waste to fields of Mandalorian
I advise disgraced Magistrate Greef Karga
and urge you to lay down your arms
The structure you are trapped in
and your storied lives will come
What do you propose?
Reasonable negotiation.
What assurance do you offer?
If you're asking
Just as you betrayed
I would gladly break any promise
The assurance I give is this:
which at this time involves
I will give you until nightfall, and then
I say we hear him out.
The minute we open that door, we're dead.
We're dead if we don't.
At least out there, we've got a shot.
That's easy for you to say.
I'm a Rebel Shock Trooper.
They'll upload me to a Mind Flayer.
Those aren't real.
I don't care to find out.
What about you, Mando?
I know who he is.
It's Moff Gideon.
No.
Moff Gideon was executed for war crimes.
It's him.
So? What does that prove?
I haven't heard that name
On Mandalore?
I was not born on Mandalore.
But you're a Mandalorian.
Mandalorian isn't a race.
It's a Creed.
I was a foundling.
They raised me in the Fighting Corps.
I was treated as one of their own.
When I came of age
The only record of my family name
Moff Gideon was an ISB Officer
That's how I know it's him.
That's how he knows who we all are.
He says he needs us
I was worried when the Ugnaught
but if they'd captured the kid
Hail them again.
Come in, Kuiil.
Kuiil?
- Nothing.
Kuiil has been terminated.
What did you do?
<i>I am fulfilling my base function.</i>
Which is?
To nurse and protect.
What was that?
Look alive.
Look!
Cover me.
Burn them out.
Stay with me, buddy.
This is our only path out.
Stay with me.
If you go near this child
I understand.
Yes, of course.
Oh, I love IG units.
I'm not gonna make it. Go.
Shut up. You just got your bell rung.
Leave me.
- I'm gonna need to take this thing off.
You make sure the child is safe.
Here.
When you get to the Mandalorian covert
You tell them it's from Din Djarin.
You tell them the foundling was
We can make it.
Come on! Let's go!
I'm not gonna make it and you know it.
You protect the child.
I can hold them back long enough
Let me have a warrior's death.
I won't leave you.
This is the Way.
Come on! It's open, let's go!
Go. Go.
We have to move! Now!
Go.
Escape and protect this child.
I will stay with the Mandalorian.
Promise me you'll bring him.
You have my word.
Do it.
Do what?
Just get it over with.
I'd rather you kill me than some Imp.
I told you.
I am a nurse droid.
IGs are all hunters.
Not this one. I was reprogrammed.
I need to remove your helmet
Try it and I'll kill you.
It is forbidden.
No living thing has seen me
I am not a living thing.
This is a bacta spray.
You have suffered damage
You mean my brain?
That was a joke.
I got you.
Do you know which way to go?
No. I don't know these tunnels.
I've only entered from the bazaar.
Well, if we get the smell
it'll lead us up to the plains
And the Imps will
We need the Mandalorians
Ugh, this place is a maze.
Stop.
I can stand.
The bacta infusion is working.
I'll try to find tracks.
We're close.
Turn here.
We should go.
You go. Take the ship.
Did you know about this?
Is this the work of your bounty hunters?
No.
When you left the system
and the hunters just melted away.
You know how it is.
They're mercenaries. They're not zealots.
Did you do this? Did you?
- No!
We revealed ourselves.
We knew what could happen
The Imperials arrived shortly thereafter.
This is what resulted.
Did any survive?
I hope so.
Come with us.
No.
I will not abandon this place
Show me the one
This is the one.
This is the one that you hunted
Yes. The one that saved me as well.
- From the mudhorn?
It looks helpless.
It's injured, but it is not helpless.
Its species can move objects
I know of such things.
The songs of eons past tell of battles
and an order of sorcerers called Jedi
It is an enemy?
No. Its kind were enemies
What is it?
It is a foundling.
By Creed, it is in your care.
You wish me to train this thing?
It is too weak. It would die.
You have no choice.
Where?
This, you must determine.
You expect me to search the galaxy
for the home of this creature
and deliver it to a race
This is the Way.
Hey.
These tunnels will be lousy with Imps
We should at least discuss an escape plan.
If you follow
it will lead you to the underground river.
It flows downstream toward the lava flats.
I think we should go.
I'm staying.
I need to help her and I need to heal.
You must go.
A foundling is in your care.
By Creed, until it is of age or reunited
you are as its father.
This is the Way.
You have earned your Signet.
You are a clan of two.
Thank you.
I will wear this with honor.
We should go.
IG, please guard
A scouting party draws near.
Hang on.
I have one more gift
Have you trained in the Rising Phoenix?
When I was a boy. Yes.
Then this will make you complete.
Thank you.
ARMORER When you have healed
Until you know it
I understand.
WEBVTT
You are protected.
More will come. You must go.
Come with us.
My place is here.
Restock your munitions.
IG, carry this for Din Djarin
Now, go.
Down to the river and across the plains.
Be safe on your journey.
Thank you.
Hey, Mando.
Where are they?
I said, where are they?
This is the lava river.
The ferry droid is fried.
Yeah, but if we push the boat out
Come on.
Looks old. Will it take the heat?
You got a better idea?
Guess not.
Push!
Come on! What're you doing?
- Let's try this.
You guys mind getting out of the way?
Oh!
Good job.
Watch your feet. It's molten lava.
No kidding.
I don't suppose anybody here speaks droid?
I believe he is asking
Down river. To the lava flat.
That's it. We're free!
No.
No, we're not.
Stormtroopers.
It looks like an entire platoon.
Stop the boat.
Hey, Droid, I said stop the boat.
Hey! I'm talking to you.
I said stop!
We're still moving.
Looks like we fight.
- There are too many.
'Cause I can't surrender.
They will not be satisfied
This is unacceptable.
I will eliminate the enemy
You don't have
You wouldn't even get to daylight.
That is not my objective.
We're getting close. Saddle up.
I still have the security protocols
If my designs are compromised
What're you talking about?
I am not permitted to be captured.
Are we gonna keep talking
I can no longer carry this for you.
Nor can I watch over the child.
Wait. You can't self-destruct.
Your base command is to watch the child.
That supersedes
- Right?
Good. Now, grab a blaster
Victory through combat
We will be captured.
Sadly, there is no scenario where
Listen, you're not going anywhere.
We need you. Let's just come up with a...
Please tell me the child
If you do so
But you'll be destroyed.
And you will live
No. We need you.
There is nothing to be sad about.
I'm not sad.
Yes, you are. I'm a nurse droid.
IG?
What're you doing?
Manufacturer's protocol dictates
I must be destroyed.
Moff Gideon!
- He missed!
Our blasters are useless against him.
Let's make the baby do
Come on, baby! Do the magic hand thing.
- I'm out of ideas.
Here he comes!
No!
That was impressive, Mando.
It looks like your Guild rates
Any more stormtroopers?
I think we cleaned up the town.
I'm thinking of staying around
- You're staying here?
Nevarro is a very fine planet.
And now that the scum and villainy
it's very respectable again.
As a bounty hunter hive?
Some of my favorite people
And perhaps, this specimen of soldier
Yeah. I've got some clerical
And if you would agree
clerical concerns would be
But you, my friend, you will be welcome
So, go off, enjoy yourself.
And when you're ready to return
I'm afraid I have
Take care of this little one.
Or maybe, it'll take care of you.
What do you got there?
I didn't think I'd see this again.
Why don't you hang onto that?