That's it.
Can I just, you know,
You're an artist, Sid.
You're telling me
and I'm never going
There's a good chance
Most guys, you know,
they start
"Mom," girlfriend's initials,
Not you.
You get a full set of sleeves,
Takes guys a few years
I don't have
Wish to hell I did.
The vault. Open it.
We can't. The branch
-Where is he?
He's at White Castle.
White Castle?
It's a fast food restaurant.
They serve
I know what it is.
I'm not playing games.
Open it.
Sir, you have a half
Don't you think
This is the police.
You are completely surrounded.
Put down your weapon.
Put down your weapons now.
Rarely in the case
do we hear a plea
Are you sure about this,
I'm sure, Your Honor.
Your Honor, we'd like
My client's a bit confused
I'm not, Your Honor.
He is, Your Honor.
Perhaps you should heed
take some additional time
I've already done that,
I'll retire to my chambers
Court's recessed until 1:30.
Come on, let's go.
Uncle Mike?
I didn't want you to come.
Go home, LJ.
I didn't want you
He's not gonna
Can you blame him?
He's beginning
that anybody
is gonna
And he's not the only one
who's starting to feel
Will you give us a minute?
One minute.
Don't you understand?
You just put the book
and she's gonna lob it
Justice and punishment
I know.
Then will you please tell me
We've been over this.
I've known you
You don't have
and I know you didn't
Veronica.
Why won't you
You've been good to me.
My whole life, you have.
But you've gotta let me
Okay?
Given your lack
I am inclined
However, the fact that
during the commission
For that reason,
that you see the inside
It says here
somewhere near your home
I'm willing to honor that.
The closest
Level one?
That's maximum security,
I would ask counsel to refrain
As I was saying,
the closest
would be Fox River
As for the term
I'm setting it
You'll be eligible for parole
Sentence to be carried out immediately.
Okay, step inside the door
When you hear
Keep the line moving.
We ain't got all day
- Let's go. Move it.
Move it. You got less
Keep the line moving.
- Move it. Right now. Let's go. Move, move.
Name and back number.
Scofield, Michael.
94941.
Are you
Never really
Good, 'cause
don't mean
We got two commandments
The first commandment
What's the second commandment?
See commandment number one.
Gotcha.
You talking out the side
Come again?
I said, are you
Just trying to fly low,
Do my time... and get out.
There isn't any flying
Good to know.
Hey, can a brother
It's hotter than
To hell with the AC, man.
Come on!
Yo, Fish!
What you looking at?
You look kind of pretty
Fish!
I suggest you
Ain't nothing to do up in here
Ain't nobody
Welcome to
...is now
You wanna talk
No, it's not
If it's keeping you up,
Oh, it's just...
It's nothing, you know.
Michael's case.
You did the best you could.
Yeah, but he didn't.
He just sort of rolled over.
He didn't put up a fight.
It's not like him.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
Hey, if it's on your mind,
Good night.
All wings, guard coming out.
All wings,
Trey Street Deuces
Nortenos got the bleachers.
Woods got the weight pile.
The C.O.s got the rest.
I'm telling you, the guards
The only difference
is the badge.
Who's the pet lover?
He'll deny it,
Parachuted out of a plane
Doesn't look
Who does?
Hey! What up, Wholesale?
-You okay?
Yeah.
What you doing
-He's my new cellie.
Wholesale's got it wired up
Anything you want,
You keep
I swear I'm gonna
Man, you couldn't bust a grape in Napa
-What are you talking about?
Oh, no, no. Now you're
I'm looking for someone.
Guy named Lincoln Burrows.
Linc the Sink?
That what
Yeah.
As in, he'll come at you
Snowflake.
Where can I find him?
Man killed
In a month,
which means no one up this river
'cause he's got
What are they gonna do?
There a way
Oh, no. The only time
is for chapel and P.I.
P.I.? What's that?
Prison Industry.
The guys that get along
You know, painting, scrapping,
I wouldn't get excited, though,
You ain't sniffin'
Why's that?
'Cause John Abruzzi runs it.
"John Abruzzi" John Abruzzi?
"John Abruzzi" John Abruzzi.
Why you wanna see Burrows
Because he's my brother.
They denied the motion.
Then do it again.
I can't. That's it.
May 11th.
That's the date they,
execute me.
I know.
I didn't
The evidence says you did.
I don't care
I didn't kill him.
Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
But how did they get it wrong then?
The courts,
Don't know. Don't know.
All I keep thinking,
I was set up.
And whoever it was
wants me in the ground
What's another word
What's the context?
Oh, you know.
The "I love you so much
I ain't never knocking over
Except, you know, classy.
Mmm.
I'm proposing to my girl,
In a letter?
You got a better way?
Face-to-face
This place ain't exactly
I'm gonna have her get
Then, once she can see
she opens the letter...
It's like almost being there.
Except for the fact
Try "passion."
Ooh! Ooh! "Passion."
Passion.
How do you spell that?
-Is it P-A-S-H?
No "H"?
LJ, hold up.
Hold up.
I don't think I can
Everything's going
Trust me.
We understand
-Yeah.
Not Saturday.
It's totally understood.
I don't want hundreds,
I know, I know.
Tens and 20s only.
It's on.
Police!
Abruzzi, I need you
Beat it.
Maybe you ought to hear
You got nothing I need.
Wouldn't be
My mistake.
Just what I need... a duck.
P.I., Abruzzi.
You might find I can be
Mull it over.
Come find me
All right, guys,
I want to get home tonight!
Maggio.
Yeah? So?
That's the son of a bitch
That's Fibonacci?
I thought the punk
Evidently,
Somebody messing with us?
This you're not
What is it?
Tattoo looks fresh.
I guess, being a diabetic,
I'm Michael, by the way.
Scofield.
And you are?
Dr. Tancredi will do.
"Tancredi" like the governor?
You're not related,
Hmm. Wouldn't think
of Frontier Justice Frank
As a doctor, no less.
I believe in being part
Hmm. "Be the change you want
What?
Nothing. That was just
That was you?
This whole time,
You're very funny.
Sit tight.
I'll be back
So, how do we play this?
You hook me up
Nice try.
I'm the farthest thing
I got news
"Trust me" means absolutely zero
The only way
is if I'm administering it.
Guess we'll be seeing
I guess so.
We're all clear
-Good.
Bishop McMorrow
He's got a lot of influence
They went to prep school
Look, the closer it gets,
that the bottom is going
Well, maybe it's time you arranged a visit
Look, in one month,
"The Son of Man must be delivered
and be crucified
And they remembered His words,
Good day, gentlemen.
Let's go,
Michael.
Let's go. Come on, man.
Keep moving.
- Why?
I'm getting you
Burrows, roll it up.
It's impossible.
Not if you designed
Too formal.
Too "greeting card."
Well, we got
sooner or later,
We have time.
We don't, actually.
I mean, at some point,
I don't want
We're only going
We have to
Honey, can I
Of course.
Are you putting this off?
What do you mean?
I mean, are you
No. Honey, no.
I'm not.
I don't know.
-I just can't help thinking this is about--
I love you.
And I want
Passion?
What were you thinking?
Hey, you went for it.
She probably thinks
"Passion." You know,
That's me from now on.
Yes. No. Love.
Hate. Love.
Give it time.
Are you kidding?
I proposed to her.
That doesn't take time.
Si or no.
One syllable, man.
She's supposed
for a conjugal on Tuesday.
She's always
letting me know
This time, man,
You spooked her.
Scofield.
Get it together.
No good, Fish.
No one gets an audience
Not unless he's real interested
Top of your class at Loyola.
Magna cum laude, in fact.
I can't help wondering
is doing in a place like this.
Took a wrong turn
You make it sound
Like all you did was turn the wrong way
Everyone turns up one
The reason
I noticed in your I-file,
you put down "unemployed."
That's not true, now, is it?
I know you're
Shah Jahan
as a monument
My wife is quite fond
It appeals
Being married to someone
Wouldn't wish it on anyone.
And yet, in 39 years,
my wife
And the worst part of it is,
So, because
I thought, you know,
Come June,
But here, look.
You see,
I build anymore,
it's all gonna come down
That's where I was hoping
For the favor,
three days of work
And it'll keep you
Mmm.
I can't do it.
Son, it's better for me
than it is for you
I can promise you that.
I'll take my chances.
Then we're through here.
Guard!
Two pounds of pot?
What were you trying to do,
It's not funny, LJ.
You could be going
It's pretty obvious to me
Hey.
Thanks.
From who,
Give him a chance.
We got nothing in common.
Come on. Where is this
Last semester you were getting
It's your father, isn't it?
I don't have a father.
It wasn't an immaculate
Trust me.
Maybe it's time
Mom...
Mom.
Don't.
I'm about as excited
but something's gotta give.
You have got
to be screwing up
What if they'd sent you
I think I'd be doing
Eating Jell-O,
I know what you're doing.
It's not the luck of the draw
You forget I know you.
Both of you.
You two have the most
What, he beats you up
so you get yourself tossed
To what?
Save him?
I deserve to know.
I loved him
Past tense for you, maybe.
I gave him a shot
Even with all the stuff
I did everything I could
And he threw it away.
You ever think maybe he was hurt
in the first place?
Don't do this.
Whatever it is you're doing,
There's a better way.
I'm already appealing
I told you
I've gotten in touch with the diocese about Lincoln.
That won't stop it.
You want
You find out
Nobody's trying to bury him.
The evidence was there.
The evidence was cooked.
Visiting hours
Take care of yourself.
Someone wants him
Something more
This is desperation, Michael.
You're grabbing at straws.
Maybe.
But I can't watch him die.
I won't do that.
Gentlemen...
What is it about the Burrows situation
It's our understanding
I wouldn't say it's "great" or "influence."
We're friends.
It's also our understanding
I'm a man of God.
In this case, we're hoping
At least temporarily.
If the inmate appeals
how can I
You have a habit of answering
And you have a way of asking questions
Are you saying
I'm not a man to equivocate.
You're, what, 62 years old now,
That's right.
I would assume, then,
in how our government's
Taking personal
under the church's
that would be fraud,
I will not be cowed
Not by you or anyone else.
Admirable.
Good day, Excellency.
Mr. Kellerman...
What is it about this case
The man killed
What'd you say?
You heard me.
Someone found Fibonacci.
I'm looking at the photos
Son of a bitch
Witness protection,
Who was this someone?
Don't know, there's no return address
Just...
this folded-up bird
Like origami?
Yeah, like that.
Like origami.
You're Charles Westmoreland,
Do I know you?
I knew your wife
You knew Marla?
You mean Ann?
How'd you know her?
We taught together
East Farmington.
You mean West Wilmington?
No more tests.
I promise.
Seems you know
Who are you?
Michael Scofield.
How'd you get it in here?
First off,
She's Marilyn,
back from the days
I heard
Every new fish
first thing they hear,
is that Charles Westmoreland
I'll tell you
You want the Cooper story?
I can't give it to you,
It's too bad.
Sort of wish it was true.
The man's a legend.
Nowhere near as much
I'd have a million-five
I'd put some grass
This thing would go
What is this all about?
Say you were able
would you have
to make sure
What do you care?
Just curious.
Where's Fibonacci?
That's not the way
They come at me, John,
I doubt it.
Fight, fight, fight...
All right.
Get on the ground.
I totally
I didn't think
Behavior like that
Ninety days in the SHU!
That ought to be enough time
Ninety days?
That's right.
Something you want to say?
It's just...
I'm not of much value
Value?
Hmm... The Taj.
It'd be a shame
to collapse because the stress
Properly propagated?
Properly propagated.
The joints are overloaded.
They won't provide anywhere
the completed structure
How much work
You want it by when, June?
Yes.
Then we'd better get started,
Who's there?
Bishop McMorrow
Someone shot him
I thought
Thanks.
Michael was right.
Sink, you got a visitor.
He was arrested.
For what?
Possession of marijuana.
I figured he could use
-Gone forever?
I know you didn't.
Thanks, Lisa.
Sit down.
Dope, huh?
Using or dealing?
What's the difference?
Then what, you, uh, think it gives you
You got a piece
Take advantage.
Look, I get it.
The whole thing.
She drags me in here,
you give me a big speech,
I walk away a changed man.
Straight A's.
Harvard.
It's better than being here.
You got to realize
when you're doing
You think it's me.
I did the same thing.
Punished the old man
Look what it got me.
I'm not asking you
I already screwed up
I'm asking you
You can still put the brakes
So, that's what
Where are you going?
I got homework.
They're putting me
In a month's time,
You get that?
You're already
Yes.
What? You mean "yes," yes?
Yes!
- Yeah!
-Oh, there's just one thing.
Mama wants us to wait
Of course, mi amor.
Oh, and we have
-Okay. Esta bien.
Wouldn't want to mess
You went to Loyola.
You've been
I like to get to know
I went to Northwestern.
Maybe we met before,
out at a bar somewhere.
I would have remembered.
-That a compliment?
Hmm.
What?
Your blood glucose is at
-So?
Your body's reacting
like you're not a diabetic.
You're sure it's type 1 diabetes
Ever since I was a kid.
All right.
Not experiencing
Infirmary.
Yes.
Yeah. I did.
No, I did and I do.
Okay. Um, great.
Thanks.
I'd like to run some tests
Last thing I want is to be
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
How'd you get here,
Oh, you know.
I don't.
You know. Hector.
What?
I didn't have any money
so he offered me a ride.
He was really sweet.
Honey, he's just a friend.
No, he's not
I know Hector.
Men and women
A guy doesn't drive a girl
because he wants
Casanova, wrap it up.
Hey, you got nothing
It's you I'm marrying.
It's not you
Sixteen more months.
I love you.
Be easy, son, all right?
Sucre tells me
-What you need, man?
I only speak English,
It's an insulin blocker.
Standard
You can get it
You can get that
I can't get it at medical.
Why not?
Because they're already
You're one mixed-up cracker,
Can you get it for me,
Only if you tell me
to keep going
to get an insulin shot
I like the ambiance.
Uh-huh.
Are we in business?
All personnel,
Facility Two lockdown
Facility One lockdown
Scofield. I don't know
but Abruzzi wanted me
Congratulations.
You just joined the ranks
Kudos, Fish.
You got spine.
All right, cons,
Move it, guys.
Saw Veronica
Still engaged to that guy?
Yup.
Could have been me.
If you hadn't
You think I meant
I was just being stupid.
Hurt.
Shouldn't have
You pushed everyone away.
I'm an anchor.
All I'll do
Why did you hire him?
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
You mean
I'm not here on vacation,
Getting outside these walls,
You're going to need money.
I'll have it.
And people
People that can
I've already got them.
They just
Look, whatever you got
'cause I'm in the dark here.
Chaparral Associates
to retrofit
Four million dollar contract.
Head partner
So, he subcontracted out,
with a former associate.
That guy was one
We basically ghost-wrote
Crossed the t's, dotted the i's,
You've seen the blueprints.
Better than that.
I've got them on me.
Are you kidding me?
Am I supposed to be seeing
Look closer.
Captioned by Point.360.