Previously on "Marvel's
I've been waiting.
I wanted to come with you,
You know, Sibyl told me
[ Energy blast ]
May: John Garrett's here
and they have
Stay back.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Crunch ]
If he's not here for Jiaying,
Sousa, shoot him!
[ Gunshots ]
They took Simmons.
May: We're not going anywhere.
The Zephyr's been hijacked.
Why am I here?
and every outcome
has one thing in common.
Fitz.
♪♪
What the hell just happened?
They disappeared.
Did they jump? I thought
They didn't jump.
Okay, how do you
Don't they surround
You move above them.
Daisy, I can feel your guilt.
I should've quaked
when I had the chance.
Yo-Yo: 616 requesting
You're clear, 616.
They have Kora.
Maybe she'll have
We can't tell her
She should know
Kora's not stable.
Hearing that her mother died
If she's a bomb, then
Leave that to me.
I won't make the same mistake
♪♪
The potential Inhumans
We dropped them
made sure they're being
You must be Daisy --
[ Rumbling ]
Where did they take
Daisy, that's enough!
Put her down, Agent Johnson!
[ Coughs ]
♪♪
Look, there's no reason
I'm here to help.
How, exactly?
Save lives, of course.
♪♪
I want to be
50,000 miles above Earth
Should be a killer view.
[ Badge clanks on ground ]
And lay off the "sir."
We're trying to make it
Send the signal.
S.H.I.E.L.D.
Not at this range.
We're all alone up here.
♪♪
Just like Nakatomi Plaza.
Yipee-ki-yay?
♪♪
I'm staying posted
Who knows what other powers
And with Garrett
Mack: When we confronted
Fitz designed a device
Now, if we can find Fitz's specs
we should be able to
Until then,
I'm your new babysitter.
♪♪
We know that there's
because Sibyl's been
Exactly. These guys put up
That was too easy,
But now she's selling us
We may be predictable,
but so is the enemy,
because they're always
S.H.I.E.L.D.?
I'm a perfect candidate,
with the perfect instrument
Didn't seem like
when you were
I killed him...to be clear.
During his last-ditch effort
How do we know that's not
Where are they?
Out of reach.
But our goal is to reduce
I've suffered plenty
What do you mean
Knowledge of history
Lives have already
My own.
Those two soldiers
Not all lives were saved.
♪♪
Some were taken.
I'm sorry
They didn't deserve
But it's also
Proof?
You must realize it
Proof that this is
He gets it.
That old one that you
is long gone.
Director, you still remember
Daisy grew up without a sister
Yet here we are.
We have much more definitive
It's a brand-new day.
Why not let S.H.I.E.L.D.
the best it can be?
And how do you plan
Killing.
Yeah, I'm not sure
the S.H.I.E.L.D.
It's not your motto,
Do you want me to list
to protect others?
Coulson:
We've all made
Then another list,
30 names
to save thousands
It sounds like Project Insight
These are names you know --
committed unspeakable acts.
We're not a death squad.
Well, Sibyl predicted
And that Daisy would say --
Let me talk
♪♪
I'd like nothing more.
Why are you really here?
I thought
Despite whatever Nathaniel
Nathaniel thinks
another institution
And maybe in an old timeline
I believe there's a chance
What makes you think
You.
♪♪
I've always wanted a sibling,
and we have the same blood.
You believe
There must be a reason.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
You grew up in Afterlife.
I wasn't aware
I thought I had
Didn't you?
Every child
Not every mother
I'm sorry
I just want to spend time
With you and me
we can do anything.
[ Scoffs ]
What, like a --
Sibyl said
where Daisy Johnson
♪♪
She was right.
[ Electronic lock beeps ]
♪♪
I like to think about the first
That no energy in the universe
And none is destroyed.
That means that every bit
every particle,
will go on to be
[ Gasps ]
As much as I would love to
I need you to show me
I miss you.
I'm here.
Together. We're --
Professional,
and there's this chasm
of all these things
I'm supposed to be able to see
You are blocking me.
How?
I'm not doing anything.
Maybe it's you.
[ Chuckles ]
Maybe you're not
[ Grunts ]
Tell me how.
♪♪
John,
Deke? He's here?
And trying to play hero.
He doesn't know anything,
♪♪
[ Grunts ]
Hi, Nana.
♪♪
Hey,
That's...different.
Going somewhere?
Look, I know that you want to
But just for once,
If you're chasing a lead
I have to do this
You know, I learned
not to let somebody do
You learned that
Brooklyn Scout Troop 87.
Boy Scouts.
We were kinda the bad boys
Have you ever left your post
Like snuck off the base
played pool
You think I'm the kind of person
Then this'll be
You coming?
♪♪
May said this ship
It can't.
Sibyl's whole plan
So the only way to get ahead
Do things against our nature,
Is leaving my post.
Sibyl dropped Kora
because they knew
The thing is, I already have
Her name
Won't we use all the fuel
Well, almost.
We'll find Z1's location,
we'll aim for it,
we'll burn the rest of our fuel
Yeah.
So it's a 100,000-mile
[ Sighs ]
As long as you know
♪♪
Yeah...
You have flown this thing
A few times?
A time?
It's your last chance
♪♪
Without fail.
What? You said you've done this
I mean, everyone in S.H.I.E.L.D.
Literally everyone.
I hear take-off is
Then how are you gonna
without
♪♪
This is the only way
By stealing the Quinjet?
Abandoning your sister?
No.
Well, yes, actually.
If we're gonna beat Sibyl, we --
We can't --
♪♪
[ Beeping ]
How's this
Authorization granted.
[ Doors open ]
Now give me that seat
♪♪
First Simmons and Deke.
They're heading to space --
♪♪
This isn't smart.
I don't like it.
If you're trying to beat
you have to go
Shake things up.
Director of S.H.I.E.L.D.
Yeah, I've seen that happen
It's up to us
What were you feeling
you know,
She seemed sincere.
Her rage
Why don't you
see what else
♪♪
Leave him alone!
It's okay, Jemma,
Oh!
[ Coughs ]
Okay. [ Gasps ]
That was something,
He'll tire out eventually.
Someone's got a mouth
Physical pain won't break you,
Now let's try
That's usually
What if I crack her skull,
and then go fishing around
Stop!
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Never mind.
If you think that
[ Rumbling ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts, panting ]
Find a way to get whatever
♪♪
Guys, my stomach feels...
Whoa.
Thank you.
♪♪
Now that we're
we should be able to
My goodness.
♪♪
It's really something,
[ Beeping ]
All right.
Better strap in there,
This next part's
Seriously, if this isn't
we will freeze to death
So, buckle up,
Okay.
Triangulating burn path
Executing controlled burn
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Electronic lock beeps ]
Where's Daisy?
Places to go,
Well, I want to
I can feel
but I was hoping
could get to
I already know you.
The Cavalry.
I saw how you handled
She was out of control.
I made peace with that
What you did was sickening.
Who would have done
Isn't that what your list
She had a power
That wasn't her fault.
She fed off suffering.
Do you?
Did you take pleasure
Li thought
You were.
I was being confined.
Suffocated.
Okay, calm down, show me that
Or what? Huh?
Kora --
You want to see control?
♪♪
You okay?
She took out the Lighthouse's
♪♪
And lowered
for Sibyl.
♪♪
That's what
Sibyl was still
Yeah, now she's back
At least
I know what that's like.
Thirsty, Sibyl?
"I know only hunger now."
That's not creepy at all.
"You killed my Hunters.
You know, maybe don't recite
I can read English,
♪♪
Hey, can you read
You just said you know
♪♪
I don't...think so...
Daisy: We're never going home,
♪♪
You think
The O.G. timeline?
I pray it is. But...
[ Sighs ]
All right, this should be
everything but the life support
[ Sighs ] Okay.
Should try
♪♪
[ Sighs, grunts ]
Enoch said this will be the
♪♪
Even if we survive?
That was my impression,
Well, maybe it's time.
We've had a crazy run.
What?
How can you say that?
It's just -- That's it?
That...
Look, we have these things
Now, I know -- I know you
just for taking pictures
but in the '80s, we actually
I'm serious. What...
We're not just
the people who used to
and, you know, "Well, hey,
and, "We used to be close
That's...
Sounds like we might.
Mack...
The...
You guys are my family.
[ Voice breaking ] I don't know
Daisy --
You know exactly
With anyone.
♪♪
Ugh, oof.
What?
Stop.
[ Laughs ]
In the --
we kind of kissed.
Whatever.
See, that's messed up, because
[ Laughs ]
'Cause Yo-Yo owes me $20.
♪♪
It won't be the same.
No, it won't.
But...
[ Sighs ]
...that's okay.
♪♪
But why
I'm the only one
There's a zero percent
you'll be able to extract
Fitz isn't coming to save you
You know that for sure?
Nathaniel:
Just used to getting
I'll climb in your mind
Find that little wizard
The more you dig,
until he's disappeared
[ Grunts ]
Then the race is on.
If he moves, kill him.
♪♪
Enoch: We must act now.
This will be the hardest thing
Hello, there he is.
Now, let's go deeper.
Power's back up
Yo-Yo said the prisoners
What are you doing?
Sibyl's looking
Communication files.
[ Gasps ]
Ehhh, I'm getting
I'm trying to slow her down by
and that is literally
the first time I've heard
How do you even know
I don't know
I just...
But all I can do
The only person who can purge
Kora.
She got Sibyl in,
We got to get her
She's due
I don't think so.
That's your duty now.
I've got a new superpower I'm
We're not
But I -- I talked to her
and -- and -- and
You were trying
To see how dangerous
Now see how good
Like you did with Yo-Yo.
Like you always did
With me.
Brand-new day, right?
♪♪
God! Okay, okay, okay,
The automatic locks
♪♪
Durant.
You know, S.H.I.E.L.D.
He tried
Hey, I was just
You see?
These are the lives Malick
Not heroes, hit men.
Who now owe their lives
And so do you.
You would prefer
We want you to stop helping
sow chaos.
They're tearing us away from
♪♪
There.
Now we're
Does that feel better?
Kora: I can keep pushing
back toward your timeline
Your new friend Sousa
Or...
We start checking names
Not a chance.
What's the first name?
Yo-Yo.
Why not?
Let's hear them.
If she's gonna go kill,
let's at least point her
There's no name that comes free
Grant Ward.
♪♪
He's just a child right now.
You're not against
So much pain can be averted
Andrew can be here
Rosalind. Lincoln.
Is Garrett next, then?
Because it was your Messiah's
who made Ward who he was.
Without Garrett,
We've seen a world
where he was put on the right
People can change.
Even you.
My mom thought that,
No, this is who I am.
Who I'm meant to be.
And someday,
♪♪
Jiaying's here.
How about we show her
♪♪
We used to hope for this,
Everyone in my time.
[ Scoffs ] It was a dream,
Sousa...
Preserve oxygen.
What are your intentions?
Sir?
With Daisy.
I don't have
Well, then,
And quick.
'Cause this thing
This...thing?
[ Sighs ]
She's into you.
And I'm not even sure
but pretty soon,
And when she does...
[ Chuckles ]
...watch out.
'Cause when she gets something
She won't stop.
But listen...
Daisy's been hurt.
Bad.
So I'm happy
and I'm happy it's you.
I like you.
You seem like a good man.
Even if you're a little,
Wait, is that bad?
But I'm not about
You hear what I'm saying?
I think so.
I think you're...
threatening me. Sir.
No.
Not just me.
Every member
And we have technology
I hear you.
Loud and clear.
I would never hurt her.
Hmm.
Imagine that.
The man out of time
[ Chuckles ]
Hold on.
Hmm? Uh, Quake.
It's, uh --
Really?
Yeah. Yeah, really.
Quake?
Do you not hear
Quake.
[ Both laugh ]
♪♪
I do now.
Quake.
♪♪
Simmons:
but it's another thing
Do not despair.
Yours is one of the
You look at a lot of brains,
The 19th century was
[ Sighs ]
Much better.
Have to admit, I might be
of all the time you two
Fitz, I think we may be close
Well, I'm not.
I need better materials.
It's a good thing
as it does not matter
Well, thanks for the vote
Can you give us
Yes.
Oh, to yourselves.
Of course.
With this working,
we'll be able to rush back to
Or not.
♪♪
Enoch's not wrong.
It doesn't matter
So...
We don't have to rush.
We could just
live.
Fitz...
We could spruce it up.
Live, together.
No mission,
no end of the world.
We could just...be.
Is this
No.
And yeah.
But because we deserve it
We don't even know
Listen.
If May and Coulson
it's that we should
Ominous.
But I need to see that home
Let's cycle through
♪♪
I'm gonna give you
no one has given you
And what's that?
The truth.
♪♪
It's okay.
[ Voice breaking ]
That's her power.
[ Sniffles ]
Come on.
Go on.
Mom, please.
Please heal.
[ Crying ]
♪♪
Her neck,
A quake...
Where's my sister?
You know who did this,
No, he must have
She attacked Nathaniel,
Your mother died
♪♪
Here we go.
No, this isn't what the implant
We have no choice.
It was supposed to forget
I know,
Not this.
Never this.
You have to be strong,
And if you remember,
you won't be able to be strong
No, no, no!
You can't ask me
Saying goodbye
Yeah, but you won't remember
You won't know.
But I'll feel the guilt
The guilt for having left,
I don't want to forget!
I don't want to forget,
[ Muttering ]
♪♪
Mm!
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
We'll see
The two of you
to the greatest show
♪♪
Are you okay?
Am I okay? Are you okay?
I'm guessing from his attitude
Fitz?
Who's Fitz?
♪♪
Jiaying wasn't perfect,
I felt it.
No.
She loved who I was.
I changed and it faded --
a long time ago.
That change was painful,
but Nathaniel is using that pain
Using you.
Nathaniel isn't using me.
He saved me.
He showed me
And I can never repay him
All he wants is chaos.
[ Sighs ] Chaos.
You're not using my pain?
[ Grunting ]
Do you know
You think you feel
Yes.
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
Kora...
Time to go, sunshine.
♪♪
What are you, like,
Yes.
[ Beeping ]
What do we have here?
The last thing
The S.H.I.E.L.D. bases.
Yep. Everything from the Hub
Oh, no.
They didn't go to space
I have a visual on Z1.
A few minutes out.
Be prepped for docking.
Hey.
Thank you.
For what?
Just, being here.
It was nothing,
Quake.
I'm sorry, what, now?
Nothing, just happy to help,
Are you being funny?
Uh, is it funny?
Not if that's what you like
I --
I never --
so people know it's you.
[ Clicks tongue ]
That is really smart,
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
who can literally
Yeah, you can Quake me.
That's why they call you
[ Rumbling ]
Mack, what's happening?
You tell me.
♪♪
That's why
To call reinforcements.
♪♪
Sir, the Chronicom ships
[ Grunts ]
What did I say
Was I not very specific
about how the new world order
These are
Sibyl contacted her home planet
Had her Hunters make some
The signal we sent
♪♪
To all Chronicom vessels,
Your Predictor Sibyl
You may fire
♪♪
Repeat, this is the Lighthouse,
Man: 10-4 Lighthouse,
Good to hear from you.
We thought that base
♪♪
Oh, no.
They're doing it.
♪♪
They're destroying
Garrett: Always wanted to be
And we're just getting started.
♪♪
Kora.
You are a sight
Thank you for today.
Couldn't have done it
Did we give people
We did.
By ending so, so many.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]