Previously on "Marvel's
[ Breathing heavily ]
Kora, you don't
How'd you know
I have my new friend,
I was actually
but I found
You want to come along?
That woman --
She's none
I only wanted
There's only fear
You don't see anything
No. I love you.
You were gonna let him
Li, no! Stop!
[ Grunts ]
I can't leave my people
My daughter
We won't let you
We'll send coordinates
when we're ready to meet.
You should find someplace
This just feels right.
I feel like we should give
And what's that?
Anarchy.
[ Rock music plays ]
Here you go.
♪ You broke my car down ♪
♪ I let my guard down ♪
♪ You took my money,
♪ You left me stranded ♪
♪ And I let you say ♪
♪ Well, it's a cryin' shame ♪
♪ It ain't a victim,
♪ I'm in the middle,
♪ I ain't into teasin',
You care
Sure.
A good challenge
Sounds like
That's pretty rare
I don't know
but I am
Fair warning.
How about we add
Oh, I'm not sure
to the hottest recruit.
Hmm?
Well, top test scores
You know, I need
I appreciate you
but I don't think
We haven't.
But I know a lot
Like how your relationship
is headed for
What the hell
Seven years from now,
you get wounded
lying there
You call for an extract,
[ Laughs ]
You survive,
but you and S.H.I.E.L.D.
and you fall right into
[ Dart thuds ]
Wow.
The future.
[ Chuckles ]
Why don't I call
and tell them
[ Laughs ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Glass shatters ]
Damn.
That's a neat trick.
Yeah, that's called
Would you like one?
Sweetheart.
Two more beers
Okay.
Under the name
-- Captions by VITAC --
♪♪
Mack:
Used to have nostalgia
That is very gone.
Roxy.
Likewise, sir.
Yeah, well, [chuckles]
I know you guys are up to
The Lighthouse is all yours.
Wish I could
Congrats on
Thanks. Yeah.
I thought I was in S.H.I.E.L.D.,
Deke wasn't authorized
Mack: Mm-hmm.
Rest of the gang
Maybe we'll be reunited
after we graduate.
Hey.
You're not in a TV anymore,
That's cool.
Just don't ask me
[ Chuckles lightly ]
Well, duty calls.
Good luck, Agent Glass.
[ Footsteps departing ]
She mentioned the Triskelion,
Wasn't in use yet.
It's ahead of schedule.
Just like
What are you thinking?
Well,
No, enough with
We're dead in the water here.
So if you have a mission
Timeline's coming apart.
We have to put it back.
Nathaniel Malick's
with quake powers
You made a promise
that she wouldn't
♪♪
I think it's time
Sousa: Wow.
[ Simmons sighs deeply ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Well, consider me
A multi-story base
Daisy: Yeah, we've just spent
so maybe we're over it.
Any idea why
after we fixed the Drive?
Uh, the electrochron
did stabilize it, but it is
severed our operative
to penetrate space-time.
Did you understand that?
Actually, yes.
I'm gonna grab
Uh, the bunks are
Can I take that
Um, I got it.
Just thought I'd put some weight
O...kay.
Thank you.
What?
Say what you will
At least he doesn't know
Okay, anyway...
I wish you'd pulled a solution
I need Fitz's brain now --
So, you don't remember anything
No.
What was the last thing
You were being hunted
but did it ever
Why are you asking?
Did I say something
Not exactly.
Daisy,
I thought we agreed --
I don't have
You couldn't
No matter how confused
You were not confused.
You were devastated.
I've never seen you
Y-Y-You were inconsolable.
That's why I asked.
Mack: Johnson, Simmons,
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
Mack: We're not waiting
We're gonna do
Even if we could
leaving this Malick
could have
He's taken control of Afterlife.
Starting with
And protecting Jiaying
Simmons, can you send
On it.
Uh...
it's a good idea
I hear you, but we can't lose
This is about
Aside from May and Yo-Yo,
We could minimize
Nothing about her future,
Daughter?
May: [ Sighs ]
Um, Daisy,
one other thing.
At Afterlife,
[ Energy crackles ]
That was fast.
He's hunting us.
Nathaniel:
I couldn't have picked
Everyone I bring here has been
and given
How do you do that?
How did you see
I'll show you.
It's called
Sent back
[ Beeps ]
Almost done prepping,
As soon as Dr. Grady
you'll get to
Grady here's not afraid
S.H.I.E.L.D. decided
and was set to take him out,
You saying
Well, nothing to worry about.
It'll just...
You'll be meeting Sibyl.
She'll guide you.
There's a lady in there?
[ Laughs ]
Something like that.
She and I
same thing you were after
in the story of your life
Immortality.
Prepare yourself.
Most people
♪♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
My people need protection.
You should leave that
I don't know
and somehow,
We needed your help.
And then you led that man
Daisy:
We save Inhumans.
That's how he got his.
Is that even possible?
It is.
That could kill them.
If I can get in,
I got my power back --
And if you get taken,
and then you give it to --
Scout a point of attack.
You said "be me."
This me is disposable.
Disposable's
Recyclable, then.
I can take him in.
I can't allow that.
It's the easiest way.
I know the layout.
I'll drop him somewhere secret
Alright.
We'll fly close
You and Gordon drop in, do
Then Yo-Yo and I
I'm going with you.
We need you alive.
Your people
I have to get her back.
Kora won't listen to you.
Maybe I can
But if she sees you,
A-And then
Gordon: They're right.
We can't risk it.
I'll stay.
But you have to
♪♪
What the hell, May?
Did it just slip your mind
We were trying not to be
Were you purposely trying
Is this some weird way
No.
[ Sighs ]
But Kora is volatile.
She already tried
[ Sighs ]
She just never
about a sister,
[ Sighs ]
It's possible
When we were at Afterlife,
and I think she intended
But Nathaniel
I think, in the original
She went through with it.
Which is why my mom
to go do charity work
We can't go down that hole
Let me go with you.
No.
We need you and your mother
You're staying put.
Don't tell me it's
You're not going.
This isn't time
We promised your mom
If she can be saved.
Nathaniel:
into our friend Mr. Durant.
The process
But a guy I know
discovery requires
so we experimented,
Still not painless.
This is Kora,
The others felt entitled
who is given gifts,
It was tradition.
When you're raised in it,
Those days are over.
Kora and I are
like Robin Hood -- stealing
and giving
Take Durant here.
Simple mercenary, just trying
S.H.I.E.L.D. decided
What did they do, Durant?
They shot down
They shot it
And who are they
S.H.I.E.L.D., Hydra,
all committing horrors
Control.
You saved him
And from
What kind of power
♪♪
That's what
[ Chuckles ]
Kora.
Mr. Li is
Why don't you put him
Mercy comes
I should have killed you
♪♪
I forgive you
[ Screams ]
♪♪
I want a power like that.
Nathaniel:
You'll get yours as soon
♪♪
[ Switches click ]
20 minutes out.
Nope.
What?
You seem pretty calm,
Well, this fight
That probably helps.
♪♪
[ Alternative music plays ]
[ Humming ]
[ Vocalizing ]
[ Chuckles lightly ]
Hey.
[ Click, music stops ]
I was just...
taking a look at this
Staying in the '80s wouldn't be
I know everybody wants
[ Sighs ]
And, hey, at least
It's not the first time
When it looked like the end
there was Enoch.
Yeah, well,
so that we could
And we will.
Just got to figure out why
with Fitz anymore.
Maybe it never was.
But you said he was
I thought he was,
We followed
They dictated
The Zephyr could have been
But we took out
And the Drive was damaged
Every jump since then
So, why wouldn't Fitz
♪♪
Don't.
Maybe it's too painful
To want to remember.
Please don't even
I sent him messages
that disappeared
No answer.
Fitz is out there.
[ Sighs ] Whatever's
is happening
We're gonna fix this
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
♪♪
[ Quinjet engines shut off ]
Find the location of
Copy.
If you're not back in
And no hero business.
Understood.
I'm taking us into a section
so no one will see us.
Is there anything special
Do we have to, like...
[ Chuckles lightly ]
You guys might want
♪♪
[ Energy crackles ]
I feel tingly.
It goes away.
Actually,
If we head this way, we can find
[ Energy blasts ]
Waiting is
Take him to be prepped.
♪♪
You knew we were coming.
To this very spot.
Well, if you want
I knew
Because you have
♪♪
You don't know what
Sibyl wants this planet
Oh, you hear that,
I think he's giving us
appealing to the "better
Ooh.
Maybe I'm just
Your father was co-opted by
Um, my father was killed
Or do you want to try
Didn't get me as choked up
Sounds like the apple
I have no use for
He trapped himself
bound by its history,
No, thanks.
Here's my pitch --
Say hello to anarchy.
You'd be surprised how tempting
♪♪
Buddy!
There he is!
[ Weapon cocks ]
You don't
He's just a kid.
We gave him a chance
You must be Kora.
And you're Agent Coulson.
Oh, call him Phil.
I've seen it all, bud --
I'm sorry --
Not yet, but I got
and you play
Here's a hint --
you vaporize me
Garrett.
Clever -- digging up
I'm not even mad.
They let me watch you die
Made me feel better.
Oh, yeah?
Uh -- Oh.
Long-haired creepo,
[ Laughs ]
You haven't changed
And I'm aware
[ Knobs click ]
Here comes the good stuff,
[ Whirring ]
[ Grunts softly ]
♪♪
Hmm.
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
Hey.
Lookin' spry
How's it feeling?
Fantastic.
I think I'm a fan
Yeah, don't get
We make a mean prosthetic,
You mean the thing I helped
Yeah. The past
Yeah, Mack caught me up.
You know, you said her name
Malick was doing
Jiaying.
Hydra did
They cut her up,
in my past
She can heal herself,
Malick thought
He's after
Did Mack say anything about
Yeah, well, things got
[ Sighs ]
It's a long story.
But it came to an end.
Maybe now's your chance
what she was like
You should talk to her.
No, I shouldn't.
She -- She can't know
Why not?
Because of
The timeline is screwed.
Pardon my French.
And look who
a guy who served
and was supposed to be dead
Ike?
Y--
Point is...
you got
I got a list of people
I'd do anything to have
Regardless of what space-time
I don't know.
I'll be your chaperone.
You need me to bail you out,
You really are a square,
Harsh, but...yes.
♪♪
Coulson, come in.
Coulson!
Something's wrong.
My turn, then.
I'll go in
[ Door opens ]
You stay put.
I'll zip in and out.
Unless they do.
Mack.
who knows
Just stand by
As soon as I find Coulson,
I'll be ready.
♪♪
This isn't anarchy.
Justice isn't always pretty,
You know, a man who's died
should understand that
Garrett:
I get to keep
Good question.
You know,
What?
Whoa. No, no, no, no, no.
That is not
Kora, please.
Gordon helped Jiaying
[ Garrett groaning ]
I don't feel so hot.
Uh, unplug me, man.
I changed my mind!
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Nathaniel chuckles ]
You see?
Everything worked out.
Pun intended.
You don't know
giving that man
It was written
[ Breathing heavily ]
I wanted out,
I disappeared,
There should be
You teleported.
I like that!
Yeah. Thanks, Phil.
Alright, you think
you could
you could go
Bet your bottom dollar.
Good.
We have our target out there.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hang on.
Is that...
Oh, yep!
Here it comes.
Cleared for takeoff, bud.
[ Energy crackles ]
♪♪
Tell me there's news.
I'm sorry.
I knew
I never should've agreed
You can trust us.
Trust you?
I don't know
And no one will
We just want to help.
Afterlife is important
You don't know
She's been there.
Before your friends
we'd never had
[ Exhales sharply ]
Go on. Show her.
[ High-pitched tone ]
Vibrations.
Where did you learn that?
From you.
At Afterlife.
In 30 years.
We're from the future,
but it's...
[ Sighs ]
...it's the truth.
I, um...
I had a feeling I...
I knew you.
There's something...
so familiar.
Your gift --
♪♪
Nathaniel took that
It almost killed me.
It's knowledge of the future
that he used
and turn her against me.
♪♪
Were you close
Inseparable.
She clung to my leg
Shy, sweet girl.
What changed?
Terrigenesis.
I thought she was ready,
Kora lost control.
There were accidents.
The more I tried to help,
That must be hard.
Being so close to someone
and not being able
The others...
they wanted her gone.
But they don't see
Kora has a --
She's worth saving.
Well, she's lucky
My power has allowed me
I used to think
but I was wrong.
It was her.
♪♪
Um...sorry.
Did I say something?
Uh...
Growing up, I...
I never knew my mom.
And when I finally
uh...
she wasn't who I'd hoped
She hurt you.
I can't speak
but for me...
sometimes, trying to do
comes out all wrong.
♪♪
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
We're here.
Nailed it!
More like
Hey. I saw these guys
You've had yourself a day,
We're gonna have to split up.
If the job was easy,
♪♪
[ Handcuffs clatter ]
Coulson.
Hang in there.
The door.
You let me
This room was built
Yeah?
And I'm about to
Watch.
It's gonna be
You can't get us out.
But maybe I can.
[ Grunts ]
Save your energy.
[ Inhales sharply ]
The other Inhumans...
I can't let this
Gordon, wait!
[ Energy crackles ]
It's okay.
You're hilarious.
♪♪
Who the hell are you?
Melinda May!
Blast from the future!
It's your old buddy --
Same rugged good looks --
just...maybe
How'd you find this place,
Well, my pal Nate
He's around here
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Crash ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
I know where I'm going,
but the landing part's
Coulson called it
Gordon.
What are you doing here?
Planning
Looking for an open-minded gal
Thought you'd never ask.
[ Chuckles ]
You ain't who I'm --
[ Groans ]
[ Both grunting ]
♪♪
Oh, right.
Bye.
[ Energy crackles ]
Whoa.
[ Groans ]
Daisy, do you copy?
Daisy, come in.
May, what's wrong?
John Garrett's here
and they have
Get Jiaying someplace safe.
We have to go.
♪♪
I've been looking
Mack: Coulson.
Gordon?
The Inhumans are being held
Alright.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Better call Yo-Yo.
Yo -- Yo --
Still not used to that.
May radio'd.
He's with John Garrett.
I'll explain
Okay.
Yo-Yo and I
Find Kora. We'll meet
I got a feeling
Malick's got guards
No problem.
Hey, dummy!
Do your thing.
[ Blade slices ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
It's okay.
For the record,
Alright.
Don't shoot.
The two of us in here?
You want to bring the whole of
Give me a reason.
Where's Kora?
Sorry.
But she sends her best.
And don't you look at me
You still have Daisy.
Isn't one daughter enough?
[ Laughs ]
Oh.
Wow. It's like a season finale
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
What you said
you were talking
It's...
It's okay.
I hurt you?
But I would never --
It's actually
See, Hydra just cuts you
You're left for dead,
That part, you both
Daisy grows up alone.
Sad.
Finds you eventually,
you're all militant
Stop it.
So you start to drain
Enough.
You're about to kill her.
But guess who steps in
Dear old --
[ Rumbling ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Nice quake.
I'd give it a B.
B-plus.
Definitely room
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Coughs ]
If you haven't done
I've had these powers
[ Crackling ]
[ Groans,
[ Crackling continues ]
[ Both grunt ]
Stay back.
I won't say it again.
Mom, no!
[ Rumbling ]
[ Crunch ]
Well, I guess
And you won't live at all.
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Rumbling stops ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
If he's not here for Jiaying,
Who's this Garrett fella,
[ Energy crackles ]
There you are!
Sousa, shoot him!
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Gunshots ]
♪♪
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Kora.
Turn around.
Slowly.
Agent Coulson.
I've been waiting.
The rest of your gang
They abandoned you.
Garrett moved them off
I wanted
Meet my sister.
You know, Sibyl told me
[ Weapon fires ]
♪♪
May:
I don't understand, but he
I'm still trying
and Garrett's MIA, too.
♪♪
They took Simmons.
[ Energy crackles ]
Where's Deke?
[ Grunts ]
May: Deke, come in.
Deke.
[ Humming ]
Deke, come in.
[ Switches click ]
[ Engine starts ]
♪♪
Deke Shaw,
May,
We're not going anywhere.
The Zephyr's been hijacked.
♪♪
We'll return in a moment.
Garrett: Today just keeps
First, superpowers,
Can I get
Best day ever!
If duct tape doesn't work,
It's your call.
[ Latches click ]
Why am I here?
My pal Sibyl
and every outcome
has one thing in common.
Fitz.
He's gotten in our way
And now you're gonna
♪♪