Sorry guys, I just wanted to upload a subtitle in order to upgrade my allowed daily downloads.
Can I gave you a hand?
If I needed a hand,
Thank you very much.
There you go, miss.Thanks.
Marion.
Eh. Could be worse.
Is it a pastrami day?
Yeah. Uh, one
Not a pound and a half,
Oh.
What do we have here?
Extra-sharp Wisconsin cheddar.
"Extra-sharp," hmm?
Ohh.
You can keep it, Wisconsin.
It wasn't like this
Need some help?
I'm fine!
Are you sure
I'm sure.
What happened to poor Nippy?
Ah. It was my fault.
I was driving
you know, before all this hit.
And... I don't know...
He saw a cat or something...
Oh, no.
I pulled right over,
screaming my head off,
Ohh.But... he was gone.
Oh, that's terrible.
I hope you find him.
If you could keep an eye out.
Yeah, I will.
I-I live right over here
This is my route.
When I can get this thing going.
Maybe just a little push.
Well, if you're sure
Nah.
Okay.
And one, two, three.
There you go.
Oh, sorry for the trouble.
Put it back in drive.
Have a nice day. Yeah, you too.
Hope you find Nippy.
Thank you.
Ohh.
How ya doing, Marion?
Great. Ah, good.
Are you okay? Oh, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
Actually,
Hmm. I like it. And I think
Ma?
In the kitchen, Jeffie!
I have a little trick.
I bet it's the same
An egg.
And you really work it in.
I mean, you got to use
You are speaking my language.
Do you cook? Uh, just a few favorites,
Yeah, simple's best.
Oh. Jeffie, this is Mr. Takavic.
Oh, please,
Call me "Gene."
Don't worry, hon,
If he was gonna chop me to bits
Right, Gene?
Well, don't just stand there
Sometimes he gets a little
Ma... Well, you do.
Now come on.
Grab a glass and sit down.
Tell him how we met, Gene.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, well,
Yeah.
Well, he ran away.
And Gene here
And your mom was on her way back
And my wheels got stuck
Well, that was before
Yeah, but Gene here
He even fixed my dumb scooter...
Ah.
To Gene. Come on.
Yeah.Ahh...
Mm.
So your mom tells me
Have you ever driven
Oh, he sure did.
Tell him, Jeffie.
Sammy Hagar.
No!
Hey, I love him.
That's it! Hey!
What was he like?
I guess.
Mm.Oh. You know what?
I will rescue
Look at that.
Ta-da!
Gene's staying for dinner.
Dude, what the fuck?!
I know it's awkward, right?
But you don't have to
I dunno what this is about...
is pick up the phone
Yeah, but you haven't picked up
Or tried to strong-arm me
And guess what?
Because reward money,
That's not gonna
I know what you really want.
Oh, yeah?
You want in the game.
"The game"?
The game.
The one you've been watching
You got your nose pressed up
peerin' in
Man, speak English.
What the hell
The game.
It's right there...
You can see it,
The cars, the clothes, the cash.
The ladies.
It's about knowing
putting it all on the line
But here you are, Jeffie.
Standing outside
Tryin' to pay off that cab,
gettin' older.
It's so close, but, damn it,
Until now.
I can make it happen.
You?
Saul Goodman.
So, here's the deal.
I will show you the game.
And then we're done.
Two days.
Caller thinks
with history of violence.
10-4.
Noise complaint.
Parents possibly out of town.
Neighbors say
Man #3:10-20?
37882 Crestview.
Headed that way.
Missing juvenile.
6'2", 240 pounds.
Last seen at gas station
Parents called?
Got ahold of Mom.
Woman #4:10-23.
G'night, ladies.
See ya, Gene.Bye.
Yeah.
There a problem?
No, I...
Um, I'm Gene.
From Cinnabon.
Uh, you called the EMTs for me
when I... fainted.
Yeah.
"Get a lawyer!"
Nick!
Yeah!
Well, Christ almighty,
I'm sorry about
Just slipped out.
It's a free country.
Hi.
Uh...
Hey, Gene. I'm Frank.
Yeah. Nick here, um,
so, uh...
Well...
Please...
Well, God bless ya.
Well, 9:45.
Nick, you wanna
Sure.Yeah.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh...
You want to take a load off?
Grab yourself a cup of coffee
Yeah.
Oh.
Ohh.
I should not be doing this.
Hey, do me a favor,
if you were ever to cross paths
Oh.
Scout's honor.
Ahh.
I haven't had one of these
Watching my waistline.
Yeah, but every now
Oh, wow.
Mmm.
So, did you catch the game
The game?
What the hell is wrong
I can't even talk about it.
Mm.
Really thought
Yeah, me too.
Mm.
You know,
I know.
Play-calling was crazy.
The worst.
Three downs to make
How hard can it be?
Well, you can't win
Martinez.
I mean, what's up with him?
You think something's off?
Maybe.
Mm.
Next week, Oklahoma State.
The Okies.
Uh, that's what we called them.
You ever done the drive?
Well, then you haven't done it.
Can't beat Memorial.
Damn straight.
What do you love most?
Now, that's a tough one.
You think Weedon'll come through
Yeah.
With that thumb? Thumb's a dealbreaker.
I'll tell you something.
The Cougar helmet
Mmm.
Delicious.
Mmm!
Welp, I should probably
Well, thanks again.
Oh, it's the least I could do.
Have a good one.
Come back anytime.
Have a good night,
Goodnight.Goodnight.
Frank?
Gene, Gene,
I could smell ya
Oh, I get that all the time.
Here you go, guys.
Hey, can I...
Hey, Gene, don't even ask.
That was one hell
What were you thinking
Well, uh, I was thinking,
"Hey, this could, uh...
This could be a long one."
And I tell you, you know who
Pelini. Nah.Pelini. That's...
You know me.
but when he does something good,
Goodnight, Gene. Goodnight!
They got him in there
Mm-mmm-mmm.
I still got it.
Mm-mm-mm-mmm-mmm.
Can I help you, sir?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, no thanks.
I'm just browsing.
Okay. Yeah.
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9...
14...
15, 17, 18.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
2...
11, 12, 13,
14, 15.
Alright. Aaand...
17 feet.
Right here.
Ribbon it off.
Come on.
All the way, guys.
Okay.
Check, check, one, two.
Alright, let's move.
Starting position.
Alright, we ready?
And grab your bag!
And go!
That's it!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Halt!
Too many.
You gotta be precise.
Just three of each.
Why?
And why do I gotta run
I already told you.
Three minutes.
Got it?
Yeah, but why three minutes?
Because at three minutes,
on the cameras and the cops haul
So let's go. Wait...
Sure, there's cameras!
They erase the tapes
So that's why you only
And only the pricey stuff.
When the store opens
they won't even know
By the time they do inventory,
No more Jeffie on the tape,
So, three items, three minutes.
It's easy.
Let's go.
How many of each?
Three.
Pigs get fat,
I dunno...
What don't you know?
It's just, this whole thing...
Is this too hot for you?
You know, just say so.
You know what?
"Crazy"?
I'll tell you what's crazy.
Fifty-year-old
comes into my office.
The guy is so broke,
One year later,
as big as a Volkswagen.
That's crazy.
I'll do it.
This sounds good to you?
I think it'll work.
Well, look at you.
You're young.
You're probably, uh,
Okay, I-I didn't say
I just had some questions
Are you in or out?
In.
Okay.
Back to one.
Check, test, one, two, one, two.
Okay, and ready, set, action!
Move! Move! Move!
Pick up the pace!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Let's go! Let's go!
Barbara?
Let's ask maintenance
Got it, I'll call now.
Thanks.
Okay, then.
You too.
Excuse me, ma'am?
There's a delivery.
A delivery?
No.
No, no.
Stop.
You are not leaving that thing
No way.
Fourteen twelve
Dock... Dock D.
Let me see.
Two-stroke engine sprayer pumps?
This is a department store.
Does it look like
Well, we don't.
I was given this address, ma'am.
I need to talk
Got it.
Dispatch. Steve.
Yes... this is Kathy Deutsch,
I'm the manager
And you guys
that we did not order.
Your guy brought a giant wooden
seems to be some kind
The invoice number
Okay, just, uh, give me a second
Uh...
Yeah, I think I got it.
Omaha, right?
Yes, but I run
We don't sell anything
Clearly this is a mistake
Oh, my God.
My boss is gonna just...
Ah, great.
Ricky's booked solid.
Ricky?
He's the driver.
Well, Ricky's just gonna have
Uh, little problem with that.
Cargo space.
He's got a pickup
It's a messy one, too.
It's, uh, nine hundred pounds
Okay. I'm sorry,
No, I know.
I mean, if he's late,
Pun intended.
Gene?
Yep. Oh, I'm just, uh,
It's a delivery issue.
Don't worry.Okay.
I got it.
Sorry.
- You still there?
Look, I don't know what to
it's just I can't have
I-I understand.
It's just... I mean,
we have to answer to, right?
Hey, I've got an idea.
Um, I've got an extra truck.
I could drive over there myself.
Great.
Well, I'm just over
Um, so, if I leave right now,
Four hours?
No, no, it's fine.
I'll crank the tunes,
I mean, no, I can't wait
We're closing
Oh. Whew.
How's this?
Yeah?
If you promise me that...
Ricky will get back here
I'll hold the box overnight.
You would do that?
Oh, my God.
What's your name again?
Kathy.
Yeah, my guy'll be there,
With flowers.
Well, f-flowers
but thanks for the thought.
No, thank you.
G'night, ladies.
'Night.
Gentlemen. Hey, Gene.
Heya, Gene.
Well, better hit it.
Good luck to Lizzie
She's a little nervous.
Nah, she's gonna be great.
Yeah. Hey,
Ohh.
Probably heard me screaming
I was hoarse.
Uh, and Martinez... ahh.
484 yards?
Wow.
I love that kid.
Hey, if he and Kinnie
I think they still got a shot.
Ohh.
Ahh. Okay.
Wow.
Mmm.
Mm-mm-mmm.
Hm-hmm.
Hello, gorgeous.
Mmm.
One, Armani suits and run.
Armani, Armani, Armani.
Armani.
Armani?
Two, Air Jordan shoes for you.
Alright.
Three, linen shirts for free.
One, two, three.
Four, cashmere sweaters
No.
One, two, three.
Five, Patagonias to survive.
6,000 more seats.
6,000 more fans.
I don't know.
Start saving now.
Mm, you see that interview
The guy's feeling his oats.
He can taste it now.
You think he'll ever get outta
Mm.
Wow.
I mean, a hall of famer
Mm.
Seven, spendy dresses
Mm-mm-mmm.
'95 team?
Wow.
I mean,
Well, I'll tell ya, Pelini could
Nine, pricey lingerie is mine.
Ten, calfskin briefcases
Apples and oranges, my friend.
Aw.
Osborne had the great
Frazier! Yeah, say it with me.
Huh? Say it with me.
Twelve, luxury pumps
How about that 44-21 win
Ahh.
Mmm.
Seventy-six yard pass
And never sacked once.
Wow. You have got
Yeah, well, uh,
I can remember every stitch
I was wearing during that game,
but ask me what I had
and clean slate.
Yeah.
Mm.
Well, I tell ya, if you're
that's what's gonna happen.
Mmm.
Eighteen, Kate Spade's queen.
Nineteen, Calvin leathers
Twenty, Uggs look funny.
Sure looks pretty, Huskers red
It's like Christmas out there.
Ahh! Ugh!
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Mmm. Ohh.
So, you think our guys
like they're saying?
Big Ten?
Yeah. I mean,
the, you know, mighty dollar,
I mean, both powerhouses,
But, you know, you got
But Michigan,
I-I don't know.
Guess I like tradition.
Mmm.
So good.
That center.
Just amazing.
Mm-mm-mmm.
Wow. Mmm.
Oh, God.
What am I doing?
What?
Look at me!
I-I don't know.
Oh, Jesus.
Gene?
Oh, God.
You...
You have a wife, right, Frank?
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
And she's waiting for you.
Look at me.
I got...
I got no one.
My parents are dead.
Oh.
My brother...
My brother is dead.
I, uh...
I got no wife...
No kids.
No friends.
If I died tonight...
no one would care.
What difference would it make?
Gene, buddy...
No, I-I-I'm sure that you mean
To a lot of... lots of people.
If I died tonight, my landlord
It'd take him three hours.
And Cinnabon would just
Gene who?
Poof!
I'd be gone.
a...
a ghost.
Less than a ghost.
I'd just be...
nothing.
I mean, Frank...
What's the poi...
Ah.
Oh, you... I'm so sorry.
You didn't need to hear
No, no, no, no, no,
No, that... that is okay.
Everybody has bad days.
You've felt like this?
No, I mean, not me...
I-I think a lot of people.
Yeah, I mean, i-it's just like
Yeah.
Hey, you're not gonna tell
Oh.
No, 'course not.
Well... thanks so much
Yeah, no, no.
I don't know.
I'm thinking maybe
What's the occasion?
My sister's wedding.
Oh, very exciting.
Um, what size are you?
Usually a 38 or a 40?
Do you want to try both?
Yeah.
Sir, do you need help?
I'm good.
Well, Barbara's right here
Mm-hmm.
Kathy, is this it? Yes.
Excuse me, ma'am? Truck's here
Great, thank you.
Uh...
Really?
Look. Ooh la la! Ooh la la!
Oh.
Buongiorno, ladies!
How much you think
I don't know.
But shit, man.
Maybe I just keep 'em
I've been eyeing these Jordans.
You guys enjoying yourselves?
Well, hold onto that feeling.
'Cause this is it.
Yeah, we know.
Well, in case you forget...
You transported stolen goods
with a value exceeding
And the truck you used to do it
across state lines.
You told us to rent
Theft from
Up to ten years.
Transportation of Stolen Goods.
Sale of Stolen Goods.
Conspiracy to commit
Whoa, whoa. "Conspiracy"?
Yeah. It's called
So, if I go down, you go down.
Man, you don't
We're all friends here.
I am not your friend.
And if you get greedy
to come back for more, don't.
Gene Takavic...
The Cottonwood Mall?
You see me coming, you cross
Dude...
Now I need you to say it:
Come on! Say it.
"We're. Done."
Say it.
We're done.
We're... We're done.
Gene?
Hey, Gene, I see your car!
Well, that's a start.
Looks like your problem
Look at you boys, hard at work.
Well, Marion, guys,
I will take another look
Wait a minute.
No, you can't go anywhere
Come on inside and wash up.
Ma...
Jeffie, don't vex me.
You can help me
Huh, Gene? Sounds like a plan.
Nice of you to
You might not know it, but
He, uh... He fell in with
Albuquerque, huh?
Lucky you.
But things are so much better
Even more so
You're a good influence, Gene.
Oh, where's my brain?
I keep forgetting to ask you
Nippy?
Oh, oh, right.
You're not gonna believe this,
but, uh, he was with a family
the whole time, just...
Oh, well, that's wonderful!
Yeah.
So, after all that...
a happy ending.
Oh, well...
Here you go, Ma'am.
And looky here.
For you, m'lady. Thank you.
Hey, Gene,
Huh?
Thanks.
I get it.
Please, believe me.
Before you know it,
Go.