Previously on "Marvel's
Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
[ Breathing heavily ]
Kora, you don't
have to die today.
How'd you know
I was gonna be out here?
I have my new friend,
Sibyl, to thank for that.
I was actually
supposed to die, too,
but I found
an escape hatch.
You want to come along?
That woman --
what did you do to her?
She's none
of your concern.
I only wanted
what was best for you.
There's only fear
in your eyes.
You don't see anything
but a threat.
No. I love you.
I've always loved you.
You were gonna let him
put a knife through my heart!
Li, no! Stop!
[ Grunts ]
I can't leave my people
behind to die.
My daughter
is still out there.
We won't let you
fight this battle alone.
We'll send coordinates
to that watch
when we're ready to meet.
You should find someplace
to hide until then.
This just feels right.
I feel like we should give
the world something new.
And what's that?
Anarchy.
[ Rock music plays ]
Here you go.
♪ You broke my car down ♪
♪ I let my guard down ♪
♪ You took my money,
and you ran away ♪
♪ You left me stranded ♪
♪ And I let you say ♪
♪ Well, it's a cryin' shame ♪
♪ It ain't a victim,
I'm in a high note ♪
♪ I'm in the middle,
and I don't know why ♪
♪ I ain't into teasin',
well, can't you see then ♪
You care
for a challenge?
Sure.
A good challenge
makes life worth living.
Sounds like
someone's a philosopher.
That's pretty rare
for a S.H.I.E.L.D. hangout.
I don't know
about all that,
but I am
a damn good dart thrower.
Fair warning.
How about we add
a little wager? Make it fun?
Oh, I'm not sure
I want to lose all my money
to the hottest recruit.
Hmm?
Well, top test scores
and an ace pilot.
You know, I need
a pilot on my team.
I appreciate you
blowing smoke up my ass,
but I don't think
we've met.
We haven't.
But I know a lot
about you.
Like how your relationship
with S.H.I.E.L.D.
is headed for
a very, very sad breakup.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Seven years from now,
in the Balkans,
you get wounded
real ugly,
lying there
with your guts out.
You call for an extract,
but they refuse.
[ Laughs ]
You survive,
but you and S.H.I.E.L.D.
are over with,
and you fall right into
the loving arms of Hydra.
[ Dart thuds ]
Wow.
The future.
[ Chuckles ]
Why don't I call
the psych ward
and tell them
you wandered off?
[ Laughs ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Glass shatters ]
Damn.
That's a neat trick.
Yeah, that's called
a superpower.
Would you like one?
Sweetheart.
Two more beers
on my tab.
Okay.
Under the name
John Garrett.
-- Captions by VITAC --
♪♪
Mack:
Stuck in the 1980s.
Used to have nostalgia
for them.
That is very gone.
Roxy.
It's good to see you.
Likewise, sir.
Didn't expect you again so soon.
Yeah, well, [chuckles]
couldn't be helped.
I know you guys are up to
some top-secret stuff.
The Lighthouse is all yours.
Control is up and running.
Wish I could
hang with you.
Congrats on
getting into the Academy.
Thanks. Yeah.
I thought I was in S.H.I.E.L.D.,
but it turns out
Deke wasn't authorized
to make me an agent.
Mack: Mm-hmm.
Rest of the gang
signed up, too.
Maybe we'll be reunited
at the Triskelion
after we graduate.
Hey.
You're not in a TV anymore,
Coulson.
That's cool.
Just don't ask me
to explain it.
[ Chuckles lightly ]
Well, duty calls.
Good luck, Agent Glass.
[ Footsteps departing ]
She mentioned the Triskelion,
but it's 1983.
Wasn't in use yet.
It's ahead of schedule.
Just like
Project Insight.
What are you thinking?
Well,
you're the Director --
No, enough with
the formalities.
We're dead in the water here.
I need you to be you.
So if you have a mission
for us, let us know.
Timeline's coming apart.
We have to put it back.
Nathaniel Malick's
out there
with quake powers
and a new base.
You made a promise
to Daisy's mom
that she wouldn't
have to fight him alone.
♪♪
I think it's time
to keep that promise.
Sousa: Wow.
[ Simmons sighs deeply ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Well, consider me
impressed.
A multi-story base
under a lighthouse?
Daisy: Yeah, we've just spent
a lot of time down here,
so maybe we're over it.
Any idea why
the new countdown didn't start
after we fixed the Drive?
Uh, the electrochron
displacement mechanism
did stabilize it, but it is
possible the cumulative damage
severed our operative
transmission receiver's ability
to penetrate space-time.
Did you understand that?
Actually, yes.
I did.
I'm gonna grab
some rest.
Uh, the bunks are
down that way.
Can I take that
off your hands?
Um, I got it.
Thanks.
Just thought I'd put some weight
on the new leg, is all.
O...kay.
Thank you.
What?
Say what you will
about the '50s.
At least he doesn't know
chivalry is dead.
Okay, anyway...
I wish you'd pulled a solution
for this out of my head.
I need Fitz's brain now --
wherever it is.
So, you don't remember anything
about where you guys were?
No.
That's the point.
What was the last thing
that you...do remember?
You were being hunted
by Chronicoms,
but did it ever
get...violent?
Why are you asking?
Did I say something
when you removed the implant?
Not exactly.
Daisy,
I don't want to know.
I thought we agreed --
no information was
supposed to come out.
I don't have
any information. I --
You couldn't
control yourself.
No matter how confused
I was, I can't know --
You were not confused.
You were...
You were devastated.
I've never seen you
so freaked.
Y-Y-You were inconsolable.
That's why I asked.
Mack: Johnson, Simmons,
report to Control.
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
Mack: We're not waiting
on a broken clock.
We're gonna do
something.
Even if we could
leave this time,
leaving this Malick
unleashed on the world
could have
irreparable consequences.
He's taken control of Afterlife.
We have to take it back.
Starting with
his hostages.
And protecting Jiaying
at all costs.
Simmons, can you send
our coordinates to her watch?
On it.
Uh...
I-I-I don't think
it's a good idea
to bring her here.
I hear you, but we can't lose
any more parents.
This is about
protecting your existence.
Aside from May and Yo-Yo,
Jiaying doesn't know us.
We could minimize
what we tell her.
Nothing about her future,
her power, or you, her --
Daughter?
May: [ Sighs ]
Um, Daisy,
there's, uh...
one other thing.
At Afterlife,
there was a woman who --
[ Energy crackles ]
That was fast.
He's hunting us.
Nathaniel:
They call it Afterlife.
I couldn't have picked
a better name myself.
Everyone I bring here has been
saved from a tragic end
and given
a new beginning.
How do you do that?
How did you see
my future?
I'll show you.
It's called
the Time Stream.
Sent back
from the future.
[ Beeps ]
Almost done prepping,
Mr. Malick.
As soon as Dr. Grady
here is finished,
you'll get to
dip your toe in.
Grady here's not afraid
of hazardous materials.
S.H.I.E.L.D. decided
his tech was too dangerous
and was set to take him out,
so I brought him into the fold.
You saying
this thing's hazardous?
Well, nothing to worry about.
It's not gonna hurt you.
It'll just...
blow your mind.
You'll be meeting Sibyl.
She'll guide you.
There's a lady in there?
[ Laughs ]
Something like that.
She and I
are after something --
same thing you were after
in the story of your life
you're about to see.
Immortality.
Prepare yourself.
Most people
don't like the ending.
♪♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
My people need protection.
You should leave that
to us.
I don't know
who you people are,
and somehow,
you knew how to find me.
We needed your help.
And then you led that man
right to our front door.
Daisy:
We're not your enemy.
We save Inhumans.
He wants to take their gifts.
That's how he got his.
Is that even possible?
It is.
That could kill them.
If I can get in,
I can get them out
without being seen.
I got my power back --
thanks to you.
And if you get taken,
you could lose it again,
and then you give it to --
I'll go.
Scout a point of attack.
You said "be me."
This me is disposable.
If I get caught --
Disposable's
the last thing you are.
Recyclable, then.
Minimal risk.
I can take him in.
I can't allow that.
It's the easiest way.
I know the layout.
I'll drop him somewhere secret
and then go.
Alright.
We'll fly close
in the Quinjet.
You and Gordon drop in, do
recon, and find the prisoners.
Then Yo-Yo and I
will go in.
I'm going with you.
We need you alive.
Your people
need you to lead.
I have to get her back.
Kora won't listen to you.
Maybe I can
talk some sense into her.
But if she sees you,
it can provoke her.
A-And then
everyone's at risk.
Gordon: They're right.
We can't risk it.
I'll stay.
But you have to
bring back my daughter.
♪♪
What the hell, May?
Did it just slip your mind
that I have a sister?
We were trying not to be
swallowed by a time storm.
Were you purposely trying
to keep me in the dark?
Is this some weird way
of you trying to protect me?
No.
[ Sighs ]
But Kora is volatile.
She already tried
to kill your mother.
[ Sighs ]
She just never
said anything
about a sister,
another kid.
[ Sighs ]
It's possible
that Kora wasn't alive.
When we were at Afterlife,
she stole a gun from a guard,
and I think she intended
to use it on herself.
But Nathaniel
got to her.
I think, in the original
timeline, she --
She went through with it.
Which is why my mom
would have left Afterlife
to go do charity work
and meet my dad and --
We can't go down that hole
right now, Daisy.
Let me go with you.
No.
We need you and your mother
to survive.
You're staying put.
Don't tell me it's
because I'm not 100%,
because I feel fine.
You're not going.
This isn't time
for that family reunion.
We promised your mom
we'd save Kora.
If she can be saved.
Nathaniel:
You can see the fluids
draining from Mr. Li here
into our friend Mr. Durant.
The process
used to be messy.
But a guy I know
once said
discovery requires
experimentation,
so we experimented,
found a better way.
Still not painless.
This is Kora,
the one Inhuman we trust.
The others felt entitled
to judge
who is given gifts,
who not.
It was tradition.
When you're raised in it,
you don't know any better.
Those days are over.
Kora and I are
champions of the people,
like Robin Hood -- stealing
from the high and mighty
and giving
to those more deserving.
Take Durant here.
Simple mercenary, just trying
to earn a decent living.
S.H.I.E.L.D. decided
he worked for the wrong people.
What did they do, Durant?
They shot down
our plane.
They shot it
right out of the sky.
And who are they
to decide that?
S.H.I.E.L.D., Hydra,
Inhumans --
all committing horrors
in the name of world order.
Control.
You saved him
from that oppression.
And from
the crashing plane.
What kind of power
is he getting?
♪♪
That's what
he's getting.
[ Chuckles ]
Kora.
Mr. Li is
in a lot of pain.
Why don't you put him
out of his misery.
Mercy comes
in many forms.
I should have killed you
years ago.
♪♪
I forgive you
for believing that.
♪♪
[ Screams ]
I want a power like that.
Nathaniel:
Don't worry.
You'll get yours as soon
as we take it from S.H.I.E.L.D.
♪♪
[ Switches click ]
20 minutes out.
Nope.
What?
You don't trust me?
You seem pretty calm,
considering where we're headed.
Well, this fight
is necessary.
That probably helps.
♪♪
[ Alternative music plays ]
[ Humming ]
[ Vocalizing ]
[ Chuckles lightly ]
Hey.
[ Click, music stops ]
I was just...
taking a look at this
again.
Staying in the '80s wouldn't be
my worst-case scenario, but...
I know everybody wants
to go home.
[ Sighs ]
And, hey, at least
we're still alive, right?
It's not the first time
he's saved us.
When it looked like the end
for Fitz and me,
there was Enoch.
Yeah, well,
he sacrificed himself
so that we could
all go on.
And we will.
Just got to figure out why
this thing isn't communicating
with Fitz anymore.
Maybe it never was.
But you said he was
controlling the jumps.
I thought he was,
but consider the logic.
We followed
wherever the Chronicoms went.
They dictated
time and place.
The Zephyr could have been
pre-programmed to follow.
But we took out
the Chronicoms.
And the Drive was damaged
in the process.
Every jump since then
has been a malfunction.
So, why wouldn't Fitz
help us?
♪♪
Don't.
Maybe it's too painful
to remember.
To want to remember.
Please don't even
think that.
I sent him messages
that disappeared
into the depths of space.
No answer.
Fitz is out there.
[ Sighs ] Whatever's
happening right now
is happening
for a reason.
We're gonna fix this
and get back to him.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
♪♪
[ Quinjet engines shut off ]
Find the location of
the prisoners, then jump back.
Copy.
If you're not back in
30 minutes, we're coming in.
And no hero business.
Understood?
Understood.
I'm taking us into a section
that's usually empty,
so no one will see us.
Is there anything special
you need me to do?
Do we have to, like...
hug or something?
[ Chuckles lightly ]
You're hilarious, but no.
You guys might want
to take a step back, though.
♪♪
[ Energy crackles ]
I feel tingly.
It goes away.
Actually,
it's not unpleasant.
If we head this way, we can find
where they're keeping them.
[ Energy blasts ]
[ Grunts ]
Waiting is
the hardest part.
Take him to be prepped.
♪♪
You knew we were coming.
To this very spot.
Well, if you want
to get technical,
I knew
there was a 94% chance.
Because you have
the Time Stream.
♪♪
You don't know what
you've gotten yourself into.
Sibyl wants this planet
for her Chronicoms.
Oh, you hear that,
Durant?
I think he's giving us
the old good guy pitch,
appealing to the "better
angels of my nature."
Ooh.
Nice Abe Lincoln reference.
Maybe I'm just
helping you not die.
Your father was co-opted by
Sibyl. Look where that got him.
Um, my father was killed
by your team.
Or do you want to try
to deny that?
Didn't get me as choked up
as I thought it would.
Sounds like the apple
fell far from the tree.
I have no use for
my father's way of thinking.
He trapped himself
in Hydra,
bound by its history,
rules, hierarchy.
No, thanks.
Here's my pitch --
goodbye to all that.
Say hello to anarchy.
You'd be surprised how tempting
that is to some people.
♪♪
Buddy!
There he is!
[ Weapon cocks ]
You don't
have to do this.
He's just a kid.
We gave him a chance
to join us.
You must be Kora.
And you're Agent Coulson.
Oh, call him Phil.
I've seen it all, bud --
everything you did to me.
I'm sorry --
have we met?
Not yet, but I got
a sneak peek at my future,
and you play
a big part in it.
Here's a hint --
you vaporize me
with a space laser.
Garrett.
Clever -- digging up
our greatest hits.
I'm not even mad.
They let me watch you die
a bunch of times.
Made me feel better.
Oh, yeah?
Which one was your favorite?
Uh -- Oh.
Long-haired creepo,
stabbed you with a pointy stick.
[ Laughs ]
That was funny.
You haven't changed
a bit.
And I'm aware
that statement makes no sense.
[ Knobs click ]
Here comes the good stuff,
John.
[ Whirring ]
[ Grunts softly ]
♪♪
Hmm.
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
Hey.
Lookin' spry
for an old guy.
How's it feeling?
Fantastic.
I think I'm a fan
of the 21st century.
Yeah, don't get
your hopes up.
We make a mean prosthetic,
but, uh, fascism is back.
You mean the thing I helped
wipe out 10 years ago?
Yeah. The past
won't leave us alone.
Yeah, Mack caught me up.
You know, you said her name
to me when, uh...
Malick was doing
a number on you.
Jiaying.
Hydra did
the same thing to her.
They cut her up,
they took her power --
in my past
and in her future.
She can heal herself,
live...a long time.
Malick thought
that's what I could do.
He's after
the real thing now.
Did Mack say anything about
what happened with her and I?
Yeah, well, things got
really bad, and it...
[ Sighs ]
It's a long story.
But it came to an end.
Maybe now's your chance
to experience
what she was like
before that.
You should talk to her.
No, I shouldn't.
She -- She can't know
who I am.
Why not?
Because of
the timeline --
The timeline is screwed.
Pardon my French.
And look who
you're talking to --
a guy who served
under "I Like Ike"
and was supposed to be dead
by now.
Ike?
Y--
Point is...
you got
a rare opportunity here.
I got a list of people
long gone by now I'd...
I'd do anything to have
one last stolen moment with.
Regardless of what space-time
has to say about it.
I don't know.
I'll be your chaperone.
How about that?
You need me to bail you out,
I'll be right there.
You really are a square,
aren't you?
Harsh, but...yes.
♪♪
Coulson, come in.
Coulson!
Something's wrong.
They should be back by now.
My turn, then.
I'll go in
and take a look around.
[ Door opens ]
No. It should be me.
You stay put.
I'll zip in and out.
They'll never see me coming.
Unless they do.
Mack.
If they caught Gordon,
who knows
what we're walking into.
Just stand by
for my signal.
As soon as I find Coulson,
I'll call for you.
I'll be ready.
♪♪
This isn't anarchy.
This is evil.
Justice isn't always pretty,
Agent Coulson.
You know, a man who's died
and killed as much as you
should understand that
by now.
Garrett:
Speaking of pretty,
I get to keep
the old baby blues, right?
Good question.
You know,
I'm not...really sure.
What?
Whoa. No, no, no, no, no.
Time out, man!
That is not
what I signed up for!
Kora, please.
Gordon helped Jiaying
keep Kora prisoner.
[ Garrett groaning ]
Uh, dude, come on.
I don't feel so hot.
Uh, unplug me, man.
I changed my mind!
[ Energy crackles ]
Garrett: Yoo-hoooo!
[ Nathaniel chuckles ]
You see?
Everything worked out.
Huh?
Pun intended.
You don't know
what you're doing,
giving that man
that power.
It was written
in the stars.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I wanted out,
and I was out.
I disappeared,
reappeared.
There should be
a word for that.
You teleported.
I like that!
Yeah. Thanks, Phil.
Alright, you think
with enough practice,
you could
take me with you,
you could go
where I tell you to?
Bet your bottom dollar.
Good.
We have our target out there.
Let's go find her.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hang on.
Is that...
Oh, yep!
Here it comes.
Cleared for takeoff, bud.
[ Energy crackles ]
♪♪
Tell me there's news.
I'm sorry.
Nothing yet.
I knew
this was a mistake.
I never should've agreed
to this plan.
You can trust us.
Trust you?
I don't know
anything about you.
And no one will
tell me anything.
We just want to help.
Afterlife is important
to us, too.
You don't know
the first thing about it.
She's been there.
Before your friends
showed up,
we'd never had
an outsider find us.
[ Exhales sharply ]
She's no outsider.
Go on. Show her.
[ High-pitched tone ]
Vibrations.
Where did you learn that?
From you.
At Afterlife.
In 30 years.
We're from the future,
and I know how that sounds,
but it's...
[ Sighs ]
...it's the truth.
I, um...
I had a feeling I...
I knew you.
There's something...
so familiar.
Your gift --
it's a lot like...
♪♪
Nathaniel took that
from you.
It almost killed me.
It's knowledge of the future
that led him to us,
that he used
to warp Kora's mind
and turn her against me.
♪♪
Were you close
with her?
Inseparable.
She clung to my leg
for the first three years.
Shy, sweet girl.
What changed?
Terrigenesis.
I thought she was ready,
but...
Kora lost control.
There were accidents.
The more I tried to help,
the more she pulled away.
That must be hard.
Being so close to someone
and not being able
to reach them.
The others...
they wanted her gone.
But they don't see
what I do.
Kora has a --
a good heart.
She's worth saving.
Well, she's lucky
to have you.
My power has allowed me
to live a long life.
I used to think
it was my greatest gift,
but I was wrong.
It was her.
♪♪
Um...sorry.
Did I say something?
Uh...
Growing up, I...
I never knew my mom.
And when I finally
found her...
uh...
she wasn't who I'd hoped
she would be.
She hurt you.
I can't speak
to your mother's reasons,
but for me...
sometimes, trying to do
the right thing
comes out all wrong.
♪♪
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
We're here.
Nailed it!
Yoo!
More like
third time's a charm.
Hey. I saw these guys
open up for Twisted Sister.
You've had yourself a day,
but it's not over yet.
We're gonna have to split up.
Are you ready?
If the job was easy,
it wouldn't be any fun.
♪♪
[ Handcuffs clatter ]
Coulson.
Hang in there.
We're leaving.
The door.
You let me
worry about that.
This room was built
to hold powerful Inhumans.
Yeah?
And I'm about to
bust us out of here.
Watch.
It's gonna be
super-satisfying.
You can't get us out.
But maybe I can.
[ Grunts ]
Save your energy.
You're too weak.
[ Inhales sharply ]
The other Inhumans...
I can't let this
happen to them.
Gordon, wait!
[ Energy crackles ]
It's okay.
You're gonna be alright.
You're hilarious.
♪♪
Who the hell are you?
Melinda May!
Blast from the future!
It's your old buddy --
John Garrett.
Same rugged good looks --
just...maybe
a little less rugged.
How'd you find this place,
John?
Well, my pal Nate
told me how to find it.
He's around here
somewhere.
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Crash ]
[ Groans ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
I know where I'm going,
but the landing part's
a little tricky.
Coulson called it
teleporting.
Gordon.
What are you doing here?
Planning
a little road trip.
Looking for an open-minded gal
to tag along.
Thought you'd never ask.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, sorry, babe.
You ain't who I'm --
[ Groans ]
[ Both grunting ]
♪♪
Oh, right.
Bye.
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Grunts ]
Whoa.
[ Groans ]
Daisy, do you copy?
Daisy, come in.
May, what's wrong?
John Garrett's here
with Nathaniel,
and they have
Gordon's powers.
Get Jiaying someplace safe.
We have to go.
♪♪
I've been looking
all over for you.
♪♪
Mack: Coulson.
Gordon?
The Inhumans are being held
in a room down that way.
Alright.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Better call Yo-Yo.
Yo -- Yo --
Still not used to that.
May radio'd.
Nathaniel's at the Lighthouse.
He's with John Garrett.
I'll explain
on the way back.
Okay.
Yo-Yo and I
will get the hostages out.
Find Kora. We'll meet
back at the Quinjet.
I got a feeling
she might be expecting that.
Malick's got guards
up ahead.
No problem.
Hey, dummy!
Do your thing.
[ Blade slices ]
Aah!
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
It's okay.
You're safe.
For the record,
I'm digging the upgrade.
Alright.
Let's get you out of here.
Don't shoot.
The two of us in here?
You want to bring the whole of
River's End down on our heads?
Give me a reason.
Where's Kora?
What have you done with her?
Sorry.
Kora couldn't make it.
But she sends her best.
And don't you look at me
like that.
You still have Daisy.
Isn't one daughter enough?
[ Laughs ]
Oh.
Y-You didn't know.
Wow. It's like a season finale
of "Dallas" around here.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
but I --
What you said
about your mother --
you were talking
about me.
It's...
It's okay.
I hurt you?
But I would never --
It's actually
a riveting story.
See, Hydra just cuts you
all to bits.
You're left for dead,
your powers stolen.
That part, you both
have in common now.
Daisy grows up alone.
Sad.
Finds you eventually,
but by then,
you're all militant
and she's with S.H.I.E.L.D. --
Stop it.
You're on opposite sides.
So you start to drain
the life out of her.
Enough.
And it's working.
You're about to kill her.
But guess who steps in
to crush your spine.
Dear old --
[ Rumbling ]
Enough!
[ Exhales sharply ]
Nice quake.
I'd give it a B.
B-plus.
Definitely room
for improvement.
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Coughs ]
If you haven't done
the math,
I've had these powers
a lot longer than you have.
[ Crackling ]
Leave my daughter
alone.
[ Groans,
breathing heavily ]
[ Crackling continues ]
[ Both grunt ]
Stay back.
I won't say it again.
Mom, no!
[ Rumbling ]
[ Crunch ]
Well, I guess
she won't live forever.
And you won't live at all.
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Rumbling stops ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
If he's not here for Jiaying,
what's he after?
Who's this Garrett fella,
anyway?
[ Energy crackles ]
There you are!
Sousa, shoot him!
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Gunshots ]
♪♪
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Kora.
Turn around.
Slowly.
Agent Coulson.
I've been waiting.
The rest of your gang
is gone.
They abandoned you.
Garrett moved them off
somewhere else.
I wanted
to come with you.
Meet my sister.
You know, Sibyl told me
all about her --
[ Weapon fires ]
♪♪
May:
Nathaniel killed Jiaying.
I don't understand, but he
didn't want her power at all.
I'm still trying
to find where he went,
and Garrett's MIA, too.
♪♪
They took Simmons.
[ Energy crackles ]
Where's Deke?
[ Grunts ]
May: Deke, come in.
Deke.
[ Humming ]
Deke, come in.
Where are you?
[ Switches click ]
[ Engine starts ]
♪♪
Deke Shaw,
answer your radio!
May,
where are we going?
We're not going anywhere.
You are.
The Zephyr's been hijacked.
♪♪
We'll return in a moment.
Garrett: Today just keeps
getting better and better.
First, superpowers,
now a spaceship.
Can I get
a "best day ever"?!
Best day ever!
If duct tape doesn't work,
I can liquify a femur or two.
It's your call.
[ Latches click ]
Why am I here?
What do you want?
My pal Sibyl
ran the numbers,
and every outcome
where we don't come out on top
has one thing in common.
Fitz.
He's gotten in our way
long enough.
And now you're gonna
take us to him.
♪♪