Do you want subtitles for any video?<br/>-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Whoa whoa<br/>whoa whoa!
Stop dumping.<br/>Stop dumping.
- What is matter?<br/>- Lower your bed.
You can't dump here no more.<br/>You need to talk to your boss.
Always we are<br/>dumping here.
Caballero, put the shit<br/>back in your truck.
What?<br/>That is huge job!
Where I am supposed<br/>to be dumping this now?
I just now find out it's asbestos<br/>you've been dumping over there.
What did you<br/>think it was?
I never asked.
<i>Tampax-- What the<br/>fuck do I know?</i>
Well, now you know.
You and your friend there stefano<br/>have been pocketing how much
On this cowboys-And-Indian<br/>asbestos removal?
Billing the townships
Like you're following<br/>althe epa regulations.
You got the same scam, Phil, so why<br/>don't we cut through the bullshit?
<i>How much you figure<br/>you're owed on this?</i>
- 25%.<br/>- Don't be an asshole.
You know, there's close monitoring<br/>at every fucking landfill.
Maybe if somebody had been<br/>upfront with me from the beginning.
Nobody's been hiding nothing. I had the<br/>same dumping deal with what's-His-Name
The operation's manager since I've<br/>been there at barone sanitation.
You're not there<br/>no more. I am.
You're enjoying your<br/>generous severance package.
25%-- That's not<br/>gonna happen.
You've got a backyard,<br/>a pool, dump it there.
That's my only<br/>other suggestion.
He's got us by the gazz'.<br/>I'll tell you that.
Unless that guy at the pennsy<br/>landfill decides to play ball.
That asshole's shitting his pants<br/>he'll get pinched by the epa.
Frankly, Ton'
I'm thinking maybe we<br/>should meet Phil's number.
Why? I think that would set a<br/>terrible precedent right now.
Just bend over...
when he just became boss<br/>of the family over there?
Yeah, well,<br/>that's the flying ointment.
Even still,<br/>I say let him have it.
Life's too short.
It's also too short to<br/>live it as a fucking lackey.
True too.
What is this,<br/>"make-Believe ballroom"?
How many times you gonna<br/>change the stations?
This "departed" soundtrack's<br/>fucking killer.
<i>- You got it?<br/>- Yeah, it's good.</i>
Regarding, Phil,<br/>I gotta ask:
Whatever happened to<br/>"stop and smell the roses"?
You're right.
U're right.
You can't fight every<br/>fucking battle, right?
Asbestos...
each day's a gift.
Every time I look at my<br/>kid, that's what I realiz
And that shit<br/>with Junior, please.
Just that peoplike Phil
They're not<br/>on that page--
Take those rosesand stick 'em up<br/>your ass, thorns first.
<i>- This system's<br/>got no balls.</i>
So how was your party<br/>that day at the hous
Slow the fuck down,<br/>will ya?!
Maybe you sh<br/>go back, heidi.
Kennedy, I'm on my<br/>learner's permit after dark.
Ton'...
you gotta...<br/>help me.
I'm coming.
I'll never pass<br/>the drug test.
What?
You gotta get me out.
I'll lose my license.
Never pass a drug test.
Call me a taxi.
<i>911.</i>
We've been<br/>in an accident.
<i>Old pumping station road...</i>
past the reservoir.
Sorry about that.
My friend...
guy I came with,<br/>how is he?
<i>Your friend is dead.<br/>Paramedics called it in the ambulance.</i>
<i>Breathe in, please. Hold it.</i>
Do you know a contact number<br/>for his next of kin?
His wife.
<i>- Hello.<br/>- Hello, may I speak with Carmela Soprano?</i>
<i>- Who is this?<br/>- Nurse al rosario,</i>
<i>St. Clare's hospital, denville.<br/>Is mrs. Soprano there?</i>
Yes, this is<br/>mrs. Soprano.
<i>I'm here with your husband.<br/>He'd like to speak with you.</i>
<i>- Carm.<br/>- Tony, is everything okay?</i>
<i>Are you sitting down?</i>
<i>- I'm serious.<br/>- Yes, I'm in bed.</i>
<i>All right, listen.</i>
<i>Sweetheart,<br/>there's been an accident.</i>
<i>We were coming back<br/>from the city and...</i>
<i>- Christopher's dead.<br/>- Oh my God!</i>
All right.
- Carm.<br/>- What happened?
He drove off the road<br/>and the car flipped over.
<i>- I'll tell you in detail.<br/>- Are you okay?</i>
I just banged my knee,<br/>the one from high school.
I'm fine, but...
he wasn't wearing<br/>a belt.
Where are you,<br/>St. Clare's?
Listen, they're gonna call<br/>kelli if they haven't already...
just get al and rita<br/>on the phone
And get 'em started<br/>over there.
All right, all right.<br/>Oh my God, Tony, he's dead?
Yeah.
All right.<br/>L-Let me get dressed.
Thank you.
Mr. Tony,<br/>Mr. Sil is here.
Okay.
- Mrs. Carmela say you should stay in bed.<br/>- Have him come up.
We're right here, Ton'.
We came as soon<br/>as we heard.
- Ton'.<br/>- Patsy went over to Chrissy's mom's house.
- Yeah, that's where Carmela is.<br/>- Carlo's coming up.
Yeah.
- How you doing, Ton'?<br/>- My knee got banged up.
<i>They said it's<br/>probably gonna be okay.</i>
Last thing<br/>I remember was...
we pulled away<br/>from Phil.
Skid marks all over the<br/>place, the cops told Carm.
He had a heavy foot,<br/>that kid, always.
Almost put me through<br/>a billboard one time.
- Hey, Ton'.<br/>- Come on in.
I'm so sorry, Ton'.
I still can't<br/>believe it.
Thanks. I know<br/>you two were close.
I was making<br/>my collections
And Anthony maffei<br/>called me. Jesus.
<i>It's carlo, I bet.</i>
Fucking idiot didn't even<br/>have his seat belt on.
His chest filled up.
Suffocated<br/>on his own blood.
- Oh, Jesus.<br/>- Jesus Christ.
Seems like that's<br/>the cause of death.
It's not carlo.<br/>I heard AJ.
Carlo's coming up?
What's with you and carlfucking arrival?
- I'm just saying.<br/>- They're gonna do a full blood test on him.
See, you know
If alcohol
- Drugs or...<br/>- It did occur to me.
He didn't seem high,<br/>did he?
Are you kidding?<br/>I would have been furi
I would have fucking<br/>strangled him.
He'd been working the program<br/>ever since he threw little Paulie
- Out that window.<br/>- Let's not go there.
Even before that<br/>he was battling that shit.
He gave it his all.
Well, anyway,<br/>he's gone now
Our Chrissy.
Crazy fucking maniac.
The thing to take<br/>to heart, t
You're here.<br/>You're all right.
You could have been killed,<br/>for ck's sake.
What are you gonna do?
Thanks.
Whoa.<br/>What are you doing?
No no no, I gotta<br/>try and get up.
Gotta go and meet Carm<br/>over at Chrissy's.
Kelli and all that.
I'll make you<br/>a plate.
- Get me a scotch.<br/>- Are you serious?
Yeah, and have<br/>one yourself.
They were close,<br/>two cousins.
You all right?
I know I had my<br/>differences with that kid
But maybe I didn't<br/>do right by him, neither.
If you were his dad,<br/>I was his dutch uncle
And what the fuck did<br/>I do but get pissed off
Fight with him over<br/>cocksucking fucking money?
I'd break his balls when<br/>he ied not to have a drink
Or a little taste<br/>of snow.
It's over, Paulie.
Did anybody ever hear<br/>from the hospital?
I was waiting<br/>till kelli woke up.
They found cocaine<br/>in his blood.
- Madonn'.<br/>- 'Cause of death was a hemothorax.
Yeah, airbags can crush the ribs<br/>when there's no other restraint.
They said he might<br/>have made it
But he didn't.
Couldn't have worn<br/>his goddamn seat belt?
- No wonder. He was<br/>whack-A-Doo. - Al, just stop it.
Aw, baloney. He leaves<br/>our granddaughter fatherless.
My only child!
Drinking won't help,<br/>honey.
Jesus Christ.
Look at this.<br/>Syracuse is losing.
I don't know<br/>what to say.
- What?<br/>- I just got a call from little Paulie.
Nucci gualtieri died.
Stroke on the bus back<br/>to the home.
They had gone<br/>to see "Jersey boys."
This is difficult.
This is pain
Like I'm not used to.
We've said before he was<br/>like a son in some ways.
To see him die<br/>like that...
practically<br/>in my arms.
He was just starting<br/>his life.
Yeah.
You know what?
- This is bullshit.<br/>- What?
I haven't been able<br/>to tell anybody this, but...
I'm fucking relieved.
Really?
He was a tremendous drag<br/>on my emotions
On my... thoughts<br/>about the future.
Every morning<br/>I wake up thinking
"Is today the day that<br/>one of my best friends
Is gonna dime me<br/>to the FBI?"
And a weak,<br/>fucking sniveling
Lying drug addict? That's<br/>the worst kind of bet.
The biggest blunder<br/>of my career
Is now gone.
And I don't have to be<br/>confronted by that fact no more.
And as a relative,<br/>a friend
Someone you can<br/>count on...
I see.
Let me tell you<br/>something:
I've murdered friends<br/>before, even relatives--
My cousin Tony
My best friend--<br/>Puss.
But this...
was I talking<br/>in my sleep?
Snoring.
I'm gonna put on the TV<br/>if you don't mind.
I can't stay asleep<br/>either. I'm all...
I mean, I can laugh and cry,<br/>and I could always get the part.
- First time?<br/>- First time. Never can keep it.
They got onto me<br/>after a while.
I'd lose my voice, fall<br/>down, get red in the face
Talk too fast<br/>and couldn't act.
Can you make me<br/>a cappuccino?
That fucking machine from Paulie,<br/>you need a pilot's license.
It's so hard not to think of<br/>Christopher as a child, isn't it?
Caity kind of looks likeim,<br/>which makes it doubly hard
Of course that's not<br/>gonna do her any favors
When she hits puberty--<br/>That schnoz.
A lot of women<br/>found him very attractive.
I think to myself
How could I have ever said<br/>those things about him
About him and adriana, what<br/>her mother said he did to her?
Obviously he was violent as an adult.
His upbringing,<br/>but he adored Ade.
He could never let<br/>himself take her life.
Why are we<br/>so quick to blame?
What is<br/>the attraction in that?
It's good.
Thank you.
When I called you...
the night after<br/>the accident
And you asked me
"Oh my God, Tony,<br/>he's dead?"
Yeah.
And I thought--
Well, I thought<br/>I picked up a twinge of...
- relief.<br/>- What?
It just seemed like--<br/>I don't know--
How could you say that? You don't<br/>know what you're talking about.
Okay, good, I'm wrong.
Maybe if you did pick up<br/>something like that
Maybe it's because<br/>I warelieved...
that it was him<br/>and not you.
Well, don't feel bad about<br/>that. That makes sense.
To be going down<br/>to the hospital again
At 2:00 in the morning?
And you know what?<br/>When you were shot
It was Christopher<br/>who held me.
You know<br/>the baby's car seat?
A giant tree branch<br/>came through the window
And demolished it.
She would have<br/>been dead, caitlin
Mangled beyond<br/>recognition.
I told her about<br/>the baby seat
So she wouldn't<br/>feel so rotten.
I mean, he was high as a fucking<br/>kite. I didn't tell her that.
In retrospect,<br/>maybe not the best approach.
Right,<br/>I'm the asshole... again.
What?
No, go ahead.
It's amazing<br/>how things work.
His mother,<br/>cousin joanne
A lush.
Totally abandoned him<br/>as a parent
But now she's reaping<br/>all the sympathy
And the tears.
How are you doing,<br/>Anthony?
There have been<br/>some hard moments.
But a weak,<br/>lying drug at
Who fantasized<br/>about my downfall
Who even showed people<br/>his filthy thoughts
On a movie screen...?
Let me tell you something:<br/>I've seen friends die before
Accidents
Even murder.
My cousin Tony,<br/>they shot his face away.
And I was fucking<br/>prostate with grief.
But this?
I see.
And it occurs to me,<br/>I hand-Carried this kid
Through the worst<br/>crisis he ever had.
I can't go<br/>into particulars, but...
wives, girlfriends
They can complicate life<br/>in a major way.
I don't have to<br/>tell you that.
Anyway, huge problem<br/>of his own making.
And he cried.<br/>He couldn't deal with it.
So...
I took up the slack.<br/>I handled it.
I felt sorry<br/>for him.
Now he talked gratitude...
but guess what py<br/>produces in the recipient.
<i>They shit<br/>on your pity.</i>
That's what broke<br/>the camel's back.
How are you<br/>handling all this?
The worst part,<br/>truthfully
Is I gotta sit there
Withple<br/>who are hurting... bad.
And I gotta have<br/>the long face
And the sighing<br/>and the platitudes.
But I don't feel it.
Then that makes me feel<br/>like a hypocrite.
And that makes<br/>me mad at them.
Oh, hi.
How are you?
Julianna skiffle
This is my wife<br/>Carmela Soprano.
Skiff.
Oh, yeah, right.
Julianna's a real estate<br/>agent in the old neighborhood.
And you knew<br/>Christopher?
I used to buy my meat<br/>at Satriale's.
I'm a recovering addict.
- I owe him a lot.<br/>- That's nice to hear.
- Well, what are you gonna do, huh?<br/>- Nothing you can do.
That's my point.
He was too young.
Good-Looking woman.
They did<br/>a beautiful job on him.
Oh, I'm gonna go up.
I'll go up later
Give my seat to someone<br/>in the meantime.
How are you doing?
- It's tough.<br/>- Yeah.
He loved y so much.
- Yeah?<br/>- Well, you know he did.
I'll go up later.
There she is.<br/>3 to 5, 7 to 9.
<i>Why do they call her that?</i>
She never<br/>misses a wake.
Oh, lord, oh, lord!
Fucking<br/>James brown now.
I'm serious.<br/>I can't take it.
It's all right.<br/>We're here for you.
Oh my God.<br/>Look at this.
- Like a movie star.<br/>- Jackie kennedy.
- I'm sorry for the loss of your cousin, bro.<br/>- Thanks.
Me too, bro, me too.
He was a good guy.
Hey, don't let<br/>this linger
On your head now.
You know what<br/>I'm talking about.
You know that night
A tree limb came in<br/>through the car window
Completely destroyed<br/>the baby seat.
Tony.
You guys are gonna<br/>hang in a while, right?
We really should make an<br/>appearance at the other wake.
Are we that late?
Glad you came.
- He'll appreciate it.<br/>- Oh, please.
I gotta<br/>get out of here.
- Paul.<br/>- Ton'.
Thanks for coming.
We are so sorry<br/>for your loss, Paulie.
How you hangin' in,<br/>paolucc'?
As well as can be expected.
Must be very<br/>hard for you.
I know how close the two<br/>of you had become again
Yeah.
Not much<br/>of a sendoff here.
- The room is beautiful, Paulie.<br/>- Nobody's in it.
What kind<br/>of testament is this
To the spirit and<br/>generosity of the woman?
We're here<br/>for you, Paulie.
You know that.
Okay.
It's a fundamental<br/>lack of respect
And I'm never gonna<br/>fuckin' forget it, neither.
Jesus, Paulie, people your<br/>mother's age, their friends die off.
What, she outlived<br/>sil? Carlo?
They're all over there<br/>at your nephew's.
- Yeah, but-- - Councilman<br/>carillo was here three minutes.
I clocked him.
People are comin'<br/>and they don't, fuck 'em.
I got 500 prayer cards.
Well, Carm and I aere.
What the fuck<br/>is that? Nothin'?
No, Ton', of course not.
- Means the world.<br/>- Okay.
She suffered too,<br/>you know.
Yeah, well, this isn't<br/>the time or the place.
You're right.
How have you been<br/>dealing witht?
It's really sad but it's<br/>kinda the same as with blanca.
I mean, I don't really just keep<br/>thinking about things the way I did--
Over and over,<br/>you know?
Well, for one thing,<br/>perhaps the meds are working.
Did you finally enroll?
I'm in a few classes
Unofficially, until my<br/>transcript clears from ramapo.
Beginning english.
Oh, and I went<br/>to a class on the history
Of the israeli-Palestinian<br/>conflict.
- Wow.<br/>- I mean, it's hard to pick up in the middle.
I might take it<br/>xt semester.
I mean, it's so<br/>dicked-Up over there
And no one knows<br/>who started it.
- Are you sleeping?<br/>- What? In class?
No. You were having<br/>trouble, remember?
Wellbutrin xl<br/>kicks ass.
I'm hearing good things<br/>about the lexapro.
Check it, paisan.<br/>Long John shithead.
That kid's in my<br/>south American lit class.
He had his toes amputated.
He said it was an accident<br/>with his car battery.
Acid burned right<br/>through his shoe.
Oh, you litt<br/>shfooyadell.
She should nurse.
At least somebody<br/>feels like eating.
She doesn't know.
Isn't God wonderful<br/>that way?
<i>- Hello?<br/>- Alan, it's Tony. You busy?</i>
Usual shit--<br/>Some Japanese guy
Got his suit ruined<br/>at cirque du soleil.
<i>- Listen, I need a suite.<br/>- So all the guys coming out?</i>
No no. I'm solo.
Oh. We'll see what<br/>we can do about that.
<i>Look, I just want to-<br/>Peace and quiet...</i>
- ...chill out.<br/>- You set for transpo?
<i>I'll be happy<br/>to send a plane.</i>
No more bets.
33 black odd.
Five red odd.
It's hard to imagine<br/>for a poet
But wordsworth<br/>was as rich and popular
As, say, someone like
<i>John grisham nowadays.</i>
But wordsworth writes
"The world is<br/>too much with us."
Later, he invokes<br/>nature again.
Why such strong words<br/>against the material world?
That was fast.
The gatehouse<br/>usually gives
Shitty directions to<br/>the east tower. Come in.
<i>So...</i>
you're a friend<br/>of Chris.
Yeah...<br/>Tony, by the way.
No, I know.
He's mentioned you,<br/>actually.
Well, I heard nothing<br/>but nice things about you.
Except... you're more<br/>beautiful than he let on.
<i>- Really?<br/>- Talked about ya...</i>
a few times, told me more<br/>than once to look you up.
Did he?
Well well well.
You want a drink<br/>or something?
I got some pinot grigio<br/>in the fridge.
I got some, uh...
serious news.
- Uh-Oh.<br/>- It's about Christopher.
- He's dead.<br/>- At?
It was a car accident
Happened<br/>a couple days ago.
Oh my God.
That's fucking awful.
I'm sorry.
- What happened?<br/>- Bad wreck...
high-Speed...
he was killed instantly.
Somehow, I walked away.
Jesus, that must<br/>have been scary.
The fuckin' sound alone...
did he ever...
marry that one girl--The one wh-
No.
Found a real sweetheart,<br/>though-- Kelli--
And...
they just had<br/>a baby girl.
Maybe that's good,<br/>you know?
I mean,<br/>bad that he left her
But good that he--<br/>He left something.
I thought<br/>you should know.
Well, um...
extremely cool, you coming<br/>over here. I appreciate that.
- How long you here for?<br/>- I don't know.
Just play it as I go.
<i>- What's up?<br/>- It's stefano.</i>
Look, I'm sorry to bother you,<br/>but I'm here at the school.
<i>The asbestos,<br/>it's backing up.</i>
<i>I've gotta dump<br/>this shit.</i>
<i>It's not wrapped to code and<br/>all the other violations--</i>
- Yeah?<br/>- I could get nailed big time.
We're workin' on it, John.
I'm trying<br/>to negotiate it out
But the asshole's<br/>taking a hard line for now.
Just hang in there,<br/>let me do my thing.
All right.
- Whoa.<br/>- Jeff'll clean it up.
Make him clean it<br/>in his bare feet.
I got the venison steaks!
Oh!
What the fuck?<br/>You blind?
Me?! You open the door,<br/>you don't look at all.
Aw, shit, you wrecked<br/>my fuckin' door.
- You did that to your own door!<br/>- Whoa whoa whoa.
What the fuck<br/>did you say?
I said he opened the door,<br/>he don't look at all.
Look at my fuckin' bike!
- Do you hear this guy?<br/>- You saw it!
Fuck you, nigger.
I am not a nigger!
I am from somalia!<br/>I go to school and I work!
Do not call me<br/>a nigger!
So you're some<br/>terrorist piece of shit.
Either way, motherfucker,<br/>you're in the wrong neighborhood.
Get the fuck away!
You a tough nigger now?!
You got something to say?
<i>Cocksucker!</i>
Do you mind?
No, knock yourself out.
This is the--
This is the new shit--
Medical-Grade, mellow
Paranoia-Free.
Oh, well, that's good.
Oh, Chris loved<br/>to party.
What's your point?
Nothing.<br/>You just...
remind me<br/>of him, obviously.
What's that mean?<br/>I fuck like him?
So much<br/>for paranoia-Free.
No, you were his<br/>friend, that's all.
Why would you<br/>bring him up?
All I'm saying
Is that there's<br/>a certain kind of guy
That I don't run into<br/>on campus.
But where I dance--
That accent,<br/>the clothes.
I'm a type?
This coming from the girl who's<br/>stripping her way through college?
Actually,<br/>you're a surprise.
Chris sometimes talked<br/>about some sad shit
But you seem--<br/>I don't know--
Actually sad.
Not right now I'm not.
Jesus, this is some<br/>pretty fucking amazing dope.
Chris said you two...
took peyote together.
Yeah.
I mean, I haven't done<br/>buttons in a while, though.
You know, I've been thinking<br/>why the fuck I'm here.
You can get<br/>to that place.
No. No, I mean Vegas.
<i>Truth is I always wanted<br/>to try that shit...</i>
but I always had
All the responsibilities.
You're a hard man<br/>to reach.
Nobody's seen hide<br/>nor hair.
Yeah, I'm away.<br/>What do you want?
<i>What do I want?<br/>I'm returning your call.</i>
I think this got nothing<br/>to do with asbestos.
Why don't you let go of the<br/>old shit and be a businessman?
- You got everything you want.<br/>- Not everything.
But listen, allow me<br/>to express my condolences
Regarding your nephew.
This is me hanging up.
- I can tell you're upset.<br/>- Big fucking deal.
- What exactly happened this week?<br/>- Nothing.
You know, people walk around<br/>like this is all something.
They'rfucking laughing
And nobody takes<br/>even one second
To think about<br/>what's really going on.
You sound<br/>depressed again.
How can anybody not be?<br/>You'd have to be fucking nuts
Not to be.
I mean, you'd have to have<br/>your head wedged so far
Up your ass that all<br/>you could see
Is your own stupid face.
What specifically<br/>are you talking about?
I mean, everything<br/>is so fucked up.
Why can't we all<br/>just get along?
You don't have to<br/>chew it.
You just wash it down<br/>like a pill.
It's the same principle<br/>as the solar system.
No more bets.
- 24.<br/>- Yes.
Nice.
Press it all.
No more bets.
20.
Holy fucking shit.
Here.
Much appreciated.
<i>No more bets.</i>
24 again.
- He's dead.<br/>- What?
What?
I get it.
I get it!