Previously on "Marvel's
Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
I've been waiting.
I wanted to come with you,
meet my sister.
You know, Sibyl told me
all about her --
[ Energy blast ]
May: John Garrett's here
with Nathaniel,
and they have
Gordon's powers.
Stay back.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Crunch ]
If he's not here for Jiaying,
what's he after?
Sousa, shoot him!
[ Gunshots ]
They took Simmons.
May, where are we going?
May: We're not going anywhere.
You are.
The Zephyr's been hijacked.
Why am I here?
My pal Sibyl
ran the numbers,
and every outcome
where we don't come out on top
has one thing in common.
Fitz.
And now you're gonna
take us to him.
♪♪
What the hell just happened?
They disappeared.
Dropped off satellite.
Did they jump? I thought
the Time Drive wasn't working.
They didn't jump.
How do you know?
Okay, how do you
drop off satellite?
Don't they surround
the planet?
You move above them.
Daisy, I can feel your guilt.
This isn't your fault.
I should've quaked
that psychopath's bones apart
when I had the chance.
Yo-Yo: 616 requesting
permission to land.
You're clear, 616.
They have Kora.
Maybe she'll have
answers.
We can't tell her
about Jiaying's death.
She should know
what her boyfriend did.
Kora's not stable.
Hearing that her mother died
might set her off.
If she's a bomb, then
what's the plan if she explodes?
Leave that to me.
I won't make the same mistake
I made with Nathaniel.
♪♪
The potential Inhumans
are safe.
We dropped them
at a hospital,
made sure they're being
taken care of.
You must be Daisy --
[ Rumbling ]
Where did they take
Simmons?
Daisy, that's enough!
Not until she talks!
Put her down, Agent Johnson!
That's an order.
[ Coughs ]
♪♪
Look, there's no reason
to hurt each other.
I'm here to help.
How, exactly?
Save lives, of course.
♪♪
I want to be
an Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
♪♪
50,000 miles above Earth
and rising, sir.
Should be a killer view.
[ Badge clanks on ground ]
And lay off the "sir."
We're trying to make it
so no one has to call
anyone "sir" ever again.
Send the signal.
S.H.I.E.L.D.
can't follow us?
Not at this range.
We're all alone up here.
♪♪
Just like Nakatomi Plaza.
Yipee-ki-yay?
♪♪
I'm staying posted
right here.
Who knows what other powers
they stole.
And with Garrett
being able to teleport...
Mack: When we confronted
the older Gordon,
Fitz designed a device
to trap him in a room.
Now, if we can find Fitz's specs
on this hard drive,
we should be able to
rig something up.
Until then,
I'm your new babysitter.
♪♪
We know that there's
some strategy at play here
because Sibyl's been
predicting our every move.
Exactly. These guys put up
a fight, but Kora...
That was too easy,
I know.
But now she's selling us
this story of compliance.
We may be predictable,
but so is the enemy,
because they're always
planning to ruin our day.
S.H.I.E.L.D.?
I'm a perfect candidate,
with the perfect instrument
to save lives.
Didn't seem like
it was your priority
when you were
attacking Li.
I killed him...to be clear.
During his last-ditch effort
to do the same to me.
How do we know that's not
Malick's plan with Simmons?
Where are they?
Out of reach.
But our goal is to reduce
suffering, believe me.
I've suffered plenty
at his hands.
What do you mean
"instrument"?
Knowledge of history
yet to be written.
Lives have already
been spared with it.
My own.
Agent Daniel Sousa.
Those two soldiers
you just locked in a cell.
Not all lives were saved.
♪♪
Some were taken.
I'm sorry
about your parents.
They didn't deserve
to die.
But it's also
the proof you needed.
Proof?
You must realize it
by now.
Proof that this is
a new timeline.
He gets it.
That old one that you
were fighting to preserve
is long gone.
Director, you still remember
growing up with your parents.
Daisy grew up without a sister
because I died alone weeks ago.
Yet here we are.
We have much more definitive
proof than that.
It's a brand-new day.
Why not let S.H.I.E.L.D.
make this universe
the best it can be?
And how do you plan
on doing that?
Killing.
Yeah, I'm not sure
you understand
the S.H.I.E.L.D.
motto here, lady.
It's not your motto,
it's your method.
Do you want me to list
the people you've chosen to kill
to protect others?
Coulson:
There's no need.
We've all made
hard choices.
Then another list,
of easy choices.
30 names
we can kill right now
to save thousands
of innocent lives.
It sounds like Project Insight
with a fancy new bow on it.
These are names you know --
history knows --
committed unspeakable acts.
We're not a death squad.
Well, Sibyl predicted
you'd say that.
And that Daisy would say --
Let me talk
to my sister alone.
♪♪
I'd like nothing more.
Why are you really here?
I thought
I just explained --
We're not morons.
Despite whatever Nathaniel
has told you.
Nathaniel thinks
S.H.I.E.L.D. is
another institution
hell-bent on control.
And maybe in an old timeline
it was, but...
I believe there's a chance
we could work together.
What makes you think
that we would ever --
You.
♪♪
I've always wanted a sibling,
and we have the same blood.
You believe
in S.H.I.E.L.D.
There must be a reason.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
You grew up in Afterlife.
I wasn't aware
I was confined.
I thought I had
a happy childhood.
Didn't you?
Every child
loves her mother.
Not every mother
loves her back.
I'm sorry
you didn't get that.
you threw it away.
I just want to spend time
together, to talk.
With you and me
on the same page,
we can do anything.
[ Scoffs ]
What, like a --
like a sister superhero squad?
Sibyl said
there is no future
where Daisy Johnson
lets her sister fight alone.
♪♪
She was right.
[ Electronic lock beeps ]
♪♪
I like to think about the first
law of thermodynamics...
That no energy in the universe
is created --
And none is destroyed.
That means that every bit
of energy inside us,
every particle,
will go on to be
a part of something else --
[ Gasps ]
As much as I would love to
watch you leave Fitz catatonic,
I need you to show me
where he is now.
I miss you.
I'm here.
Together. We're --
Professional,
and matter of fact,
and there's this chasm
in the middle of the room
of all these things
of --
I'm supposed to be able to see
whatever memory I want.
You are blocking me.
How?
I'm not doing anything.
Maybe it's you.
[ Chuckles ]
Maybe you're not
equipped to --
[ Grunts ]
Tell me how.
♪♪
John,
bring in the grandson.
Deke? He's here?
And trying to play hero.
He doesn't know anything,
please, you can't --
♪♪
[ Grunts ]
Hi, Nana.
How's your day been?
♪♪
Hey,
I was just coming to...
That's...different.
Going somewhere?
Look, I know that you want to
help, believe me, I know.
But just for once,
don't, okay?
If you're chasing a lead
and you need backup --
I have to do this
on my own.
You know, I learned
a long time ago
not to let somebody do
something stupid on their own.
You learned that
in the Army?
Brooklyn Scout Troop 87.
Boy Scouts.
We were kinda the bad boys
of the Boy Scouts.
Have you ever left your post
before?
Like snuck off the base
and, I don't know,
played pool
and got drunk?
You think I'm the kind of person
that would do that?
Then this'll be
your first time.
You coming?
♪♪
May said this ship
can't travel far in space.
It can't.
Sibyl's whole plan
is based on her projections.
So the only way to get ahead
is to act unpredictably.
Do things against our nature,
which, for you --
Is leaving my post.
And you?
Sibyl dropped Kora
in my lap
because they knew
I'd want to save her.
The thing is, I already have
a sister to save.
Her name
is Jemma Simmons.
Won't we use all the fuel
getting out of the atmosphere?
Well, almost.
We'll find Z1's location,
we'll aim for it,
we'll burn the rest of our fuel
and float.
Yeah.
So it's a 100,000-mile
Hail Mary?
[ Sighs ]
As long as you know
what you're doing.
♪♪
Yeah...
You have flown this thing
before, right?
A few times?
A time?
It's your last chance
to stay behind.
♪♪
Without fail.
What? You said you've done this
zero times.
I mean, everyone in S.H.I.E.L.D.
has flown a Quinjet.
Literally everyone.
I hear take-off is
a piece of cake.
Then how are you gonna
get the hangar doors open
without
Director authorization?
♪♪
This is the only way
to bring back Deke and Simmons.
By stealing the Quinjet?
Abandoning your sister?
No.
Well, yes, actually.
Exactly that.
If we're gonna beat Sibyl, we --
we have to be unpredictable.
We can't --
We can't play by her rules.
♪♪
[ Beeping ]
How's this
for unpredictable?
Authorization granted.
[ Doors open ]
Now give me that seat
before I change my mind.
♪♪
First Simmons and Deke.
Now Mack and Daisy.
♪♪
They're heading to space --
This isn't smart.
I don't like it.
I do.
If you're trying to beat
a super-computing oracle,
you have to go
against the flow.
Shake things up.
Director of S.H.I.E.L.D.
going rogue...
Yeah, I've seen that happen
before.
It's up to us
to predict her next move.
What were you feeling
off her...
you know,
aura or whatever?
She seemed sincere.
Her rage
was tamped down.
Why don't you
take a run at her,
see what else
comes to the surface?
♪♪
Leave him alone!
It's okay, Jemma,
he's got nothing --
Oh!
[ Coughs ]
Okay. [ Gasps ]
That was something,
but I'm okay.
He'll tire out eventually.
Someone's got a mouth
on him.
Physical pain won't break you,
congratulations.
Now let's try
the emotional variety.
That's usually
a little harder to break.
What if I crack her skull,
put her in a coma,
and then go fishing around
in her brain?
[ Rumbling ]
Stop!
How is she blocking me
from Fitz?!
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Never mind.
If you think that
you can --
[ Rumbling ]
[ Gasps ]
That's for my old man.
[ Grunts, panting ]
Find a way to get whatever
that is out of her head.
♪♪
Guys, my stomach feels...
Whoa.
Thank you.
♪♪
Now that we're
out of the atmosphere,
we should be able to
lock on to the Zephyr.
My goodness.
♪♪
It's really something,
huh?
[ Beeping ]
All right.
Better strap in there,
buddy.
This next part's
gonna be tricky.
Seriously, if this isn't
timed out just right,
we will freeze to death
in the dark void of space.
So, buckle up,
Danny Boy.
Okay.
Triangulating burn path
to Z1.
Executing controlled burn
in 3, 2, 1.
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Electronic lock beeps ]
Where's Daisy?
Places to go,
people to see.
Well, I want to
talk to her.
I can feel
your disappointment,
but I was hoping
that you and I
could get to
know each other --
I already know you.
The Cavalry.
I saw how you handled
that poor girl in Bahrain.
She was out of control.
I made peace with that
a while ago.
What you did was sickening.
She was just a child.
Who would have done
worse.
Isn't that what your list
is about?
She had a power
that she couldn't control.
That wasn't her fault.
She fed off suffering.
Do you?
Did you take pleasure
in killing?
Li thought
I was out of control.
You were.
I saw it.
I was being confined.
Suffocated.
I needed out!
Okay, calm down, show me that
you can control your power.
Or what? Huh?
You'll strangle me?!
Kora --
You want to see control?
♪♪
You okay?
She took out the Lighthouse's
power with one punch.
♪♪
And lowered
our firewalls...
for Sibyl.
♪♪
That's what
Kora was here for.
Sibyl was still
in the power grid --
Yeah, now she's back
in our computers.
At least
she's just code.
I know what that's like.
Thirsty, Sibyl?
"I know only hunger now."
That's not creepy at all.
"You killed my Hunters.
Prepare to meet the same --"
You know, maybe don't recite
the messages out loud,
I can read English,
so I'm good.
♪♪
Hey, can you read
the rest of it?
You just said you know
what it's like to be code.
♪♪
I don't...think so...
Daisy: We're never going home,
are we?
♪♪
You think
it's still out there?
The O.G. timeline?
I pray it is. But...
[ Sighs ]
...who knows?
All right, this should be
everything but the life support
and grav systems.
[ Sighs ] Okay.
Should try
to conserve oxygen.
♪♪
[ Sighs, grunts ]
Enoch said this will be the
team's last mission together.
♪♪
Even if we survive?
That was my impression,
yeah.
Well, maybe it's time.
We've had a crazy run.
What?
How can you say that?
It's just -- That's it?
Just, "Talk to you later"?
That...
Look, we have these things
called phones.
Now, I know -- I know you
millennials like to use them
just for taking pictures
of yourselves,
but in the '80s, we actually
used them to talk to each other.
I'm serious. What...
We're not just
gonna turn into
the people who used to
work together
and, you know, "Well, hey,
I'm in town,"
and, "We used to be close
a long time ago."
That's...
Sounds like we might.
Mack...
The...
You guys are my family.
[ Voice breaking ] I don't know
who I am without you guys.
Daisy --
No, it's --
You know exactly
who you are.
With anyone.
♪♪
Ugh, oof.
What?
Really. Subtle.
Stop.
Cool.
[ Laughs ]
In the --
In the time loops, we...
we kind of kissed.
Whatever.
He's a dork.
See, that's messed up, because
he doesn't remember that.
[ Laughs ]
Then why are you smiling?
'Cause Yo-Yo owes me $20.
♪♪
It won't be the same.
No, it won't.
But...
[ Sighs ]
...that's okay.
♪♪
But why
won't this work?!
I'm the only one
who can use the device.
There's a zero percent
probability
you'll be able to extract
the implant with it.
Fitz isn't coming to save you
this time.
You know that for sure?
Nathaniel:
Sorry about that.
Just used to getting
the things I want, I guess.
I'll climb in your mind
with you.
Find that little wizard
myself.
The more you dig,
the deeper Fitz will go
until he's disappeared
completely.
[ Grunts ]
Then the race is on.
If he moves, kill him.
♪♪
Enoch: We must act now.
Yeah, of course.
This will be the hardest thing
you have ever done.
Hello, there he is.
Now, let's go deeper.
What happened next?
Power's back up
in the rest of the base.
Yo-Yo said the prisoners
are...
What are you doing?
Sibyl's looking
for something.
Communication files.
[ Gasps ]
You can read it.
Ehhh, I'm getting
bits and pieces.
I'm trying to slow her down by
disrupting the log aggregation,
and that is literally
the first time I've heard
those words out loud.
How do you even know
what that is?
I don't know
what that is.
I just...
know how it works.
But all I can do
is slow her down.
The only person who can purge
her from the power is --
Kora.
She got Sibyl in,
so she can get her out.
We got to get her
to come around.
She's due
for the Coulson talk.
I don't think so.
That's your duty now.
I've got a new superpower I'm
very busy with, but so do you.
We're not
who we used to be.
But I -- I talked to her
already,
and -- and -- and
look how that turned out.
You were trying
to get a rise.
To see how dangerous
she is.
Now see how good
she can be.
Like you did with Yo-Yo.
Like you always did
with her sister.
With me.
Brand-new day, right?
♪♪
God! Okay, okay, okay,
you got me.
The automatic locks
are --
♪♪
Durant.
You know, S.H.I.E.L.D.
killed him once.
He tried
to cut my throat.
Hey, I was just
following orders.
You see?
These are the lives Malick
is saving, Kora.
Not heroes, hit men.
Who now owe their lives
to him.
And so do you.
You would prefer
we didn't survive?
We want you to stop helping
Nathaniel and the Chronicoms
sow chaos.
They're tearing us away from
a timeline we need to restore.
♪♪
There.
Now we're
a little bit closer to it.
Does that feel better?
Kora: I can keep pushing
the stream
back toward your timeline
if you want.
Your new friend Sousa
would be next.
Or...
We start checking names
off your list?
Not a chance.
What's the first name?
Yo-Yo.
Why not?
Let's hear them.
If she's gonna go kill,
let's at least point her
in the right direction.
There's no name that comes free
of consequence, we have to --
Grant Ward.
♪♪
He's just a child right now.
You're not against
killing kids.
So much pain can be averted
with one death.
Andrew can be here
with you.
Rosalind. Lincoln.
Is Garrett next, then?
Because it was your Messiah's
right hand
who made Ward who he was.
Without Garrett,
Ward would've been worse.
We've seen a world
where Ward was good,
where he was put on the right
path by the right person.
People can change.
Even you.
My mom thought that,
too.
No, this is who I am.
Who I'm meant to be.
And someday,
I'm gonna show her that.
♪♪
Jiaying's here.
How about we show her
right now?
♪♪
We used to hope for this,
you know.
Everyone in my time.
[ Scoffs ] It was a dream,
but a dream we all thought --
Sousa...
Preserve oxygen.
Copy that.
What are your intentions?
Sir?
With Daisy.
I don't have
any intentions.
Well, then,
you better get some.
And quick.
'Cause this thing
is coming for you.
This...thing?
[ Sighs ]
She's into you.
And I'm not even sure
she knows it yet,
but pretty soon,
she'll figure it out.
And when she does...
[ Chuckles ]
...watch out.
'Cause when she gets something
into her head --
She won't stop.
Yeah, I noticed.
But listen...
Daisy's been hurt.
Bad.
So I'm happy
she's ready to dive back in,
and I'm happy it's you.
I like you.
You seem like a good man.
Thanks, I --
Even if you're a little,
you know, straight ahead --
Wait, is that bad?
But I'm not about
to let her get hurt again.
You hear what I'm saying?
I think so.
I think you're...
threatening me. Sir.
No.
Not just me.
Every member
of this team.
And we have technology
at S.H.I.E.L.D. that
you've never even --
I hear you.
Loud and clear.
I would never hurt her.
Hmm.
Imagine that.
The man out of time
and Quake.
[ Chuckles ]
Just like a damn comic book.
Hold on.
What did you just call her?
Hmm? Uh, Quake.
It's, uh --
It's her superhero name.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah, really.
Quake?
Mm-hmm.
Do you not hear
how hilarious that sounds?
Quake.
[ Both laugh ]
♪♪
I do now.
Quake.
♪♪
Simmons:
I've studied brains before,
but it's another thing
to study your own.
Do not despair.
Yours is one of the
better brains I have seen.
You look at a lot of brains,
Enoch?
The 19th century was
a strange time for humanity.
[ Sighs ]
Much better.
Have to admit, I might be
getting a bit jealous...
of all the time you two
are spending together.
Fitz, I think we may be close
to a working design.
Well, I'm not.
I need better materials.
Not this salvaged scrap.
[ Metal clangs ]
It's a good thing
we are building a time machine,
as it does not matter
how long it takes.
Well, thanks for the vote
of confidence, Enoch.
Can you give us
a moment?
Yes.
Oh, to yourselves.
Of course.
With this working,
and you in the building phase,
we'll be able to rush back to
the temple before we know it.
Or not.
♪♪
Enoch's not wrong.
It doesn't matter
how long we take.
So...
We don't have to rush.
We could just
take some time to...
live.
Fitz...
We've built a nice home
for ourselves here.
We could spruce it up.
Live, together.
No mission,
no end of the world.
We could just...be.
Is this
about the blood work?
No.
And yeah.
But because we deserve it
regardless.
We don't even know
if it's --
Listen.
If May and Coulson
taught us anything,
it's that we should
take the time that we have.
Ominous.
But I need to see that home
you built.
Let's cycle through
your last memories together.
♪♪
I'm gonna give you
something
no one has given you
in a long time.
And what's that?
The truth.
♪♪
It's okay.
[ Voice breaking ]
It's okay, she can heal.
That's her power.
She just --
[ Sniffles ]
She just needs some help.
Just take my energy.
Come on.
Take my energy.
Go on.
Mom, please.
Please heal.
[ Crying ]
♪♪
Her neck,
it's shattered.
A quake...
Where's my sister?
You know who did this,
Kora.
No, he must have
had a reason.
She attacked Nathaniel,
or he was protecting me --
Your mother died
protecting Daisy from him.
♪♪
Here we go.
No.
No, this isn't what the implant
was built to do.
We have no choice.
Wait a minute.
It was supposed to forget
your location, that's all.
I know,
but that was before we knew.
Not this.
Never this.
You have to be strong,
okay?
And if you remember,
you won't be able to be strong
to do what you have to do.
No, no, no!
Where we are?
You can't ask me
to do this!
Saying goodbye
is hard enough!
Yeah, but you won't remember
what you've forgotten.
You won't know.
Where are you?!
But I'll feel the guilt
inside.
The guilt for having left,
a part of me being torn away --
Listen to me.
I don't want to forget!
Hey, hey, it's gonna be --
it's gonna be okay.
I don't want to forget!
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay, I promise.
I don't want to forget,
I don't want to forget.
[ Muttering ]
♪♪
Mm!
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
We'll see
if it even matters.
The two of you
have just scored front-row seats
to the greatest show
on Earth.
♪♪
Are you okay?
Am I okay? Are you okay?
What happened in there?
I'm guessing from his attitude
that he didn't find Fitz.
Fitz?
Who's Fitz?
♪♪
Jiaying wasn't perfect,
but you loved each other.
I felt it.
No.
She loved who I was.
I changed and it faded --
a long time ago.
That change was painful,
but Nathaniel is using that pain
against you.
Using you.
Nathaniel isn't using me.
He saved me.
He showed me
how to live again.
And I can never repay him
for that.
All he wants is chaos.
[ Sighs ] Chaos.
You're not using my pain?
[ Grunting ]
Do you know
what I'm capable of?
You think you feel
what's inside me?
Yes.
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
Kora...
Time to go, sunshine.
♪♪
What are you, like,
a computer genius now?
Yes.
[ Beeping ]
What do we have here?
The last thing
Sibyl accessed.
The S.H.I.E.L.D. bases.
Yep. Everything from the Hub
to the Sandbox to the...
Oh, no.
Coulson, what is it?
They didn't go to space
to hide.
I have a visual on Z1.
A few minutes out.
Be prepped for docking.
Hey.
Thank you.
For what?
Just, being here.
It was nothing,
but you're welcome...
Quake.
I'm sorry, what, now?
Nothing, just happy to help,
Quake. Whatever you need.
Are you being funny?
Uh, is it funny?
Not if that's what you like
to be called...Quake.
I --
The press called me that.
I never --
You should probably have a Q
on your utility belt
so people know it's you.
[ Clicks tongue ]
[ Chuckles ]
That is really smart,
yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
make fun of the person
who can literally
turn you to dust.
Yeah, you can Quake me.
No, I get it.
That's why they call you
that.
[ Rumbling ]
Mack, what's happening?
You tell me.
♪♪
That's why
he came up here.
To call reinforcements.
♪♪
Sir, the Chronicom ships
are --
[ Grunts ]
What did I say
about calling me sir?!
Was I not very specific
about how the new world order
would be structured?
These are
the Chronicom ships?
Sibyl contacted her home planet
years ago.
Had her Hunters make some
modifications to their fleet.
The signal we sent
called them here.
♪♪
To all Chronicom vessels,
this is Nathaniel Malick.
Your Predictor Sibyl
has given you your marks.
You may fire
whenever you want.
♪♪
Repeat, this is the Lighthouse,
do you copy?
Man: 10-4 Lighthouse,
this is the Hub.
Good to hear from you.
We thought that base
was decom--
♪♪
Oh, no.
They're doing it.
♪♪
They're destroying
S.H.I.E.L.D.
♪♪
Garrett: Always wanted to be
a part of something bigger.
And we're just getting started.
♪♪
Kora.
You are a sight
for sore eyes.
Thank you for today.
Couldn't have done it
without you.
Did we give people
new life?
We did.
By ending so, so many.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]