That's it.
Can I just, you know,
look at it for a minute?
You're an artist, Sid.
You're telling me
you're just gonna walk out of here
and I'm never going
to see it again?
There's a good chance
of that, yes.
Most guys, you know,
for the first one,
they start
with something small.
"Mom," girlfriend's initials,
something like that.
Not you.
You get a full set of sleeves,
all in a couple of months.
Takes guys a few years
to get the ink you got.
I don't have
a few years.
Wish to hell I did.
The vault. Open it.
We can't. The branch
manager's not here.
-Where is he?
-It's lunchtime.
He's at White Castle.
White Castle?
It's a fast food restaurant.
They serve
those little square burgers.
I know what it is.
I'm not playing games.
Open it.
Sir, you have a half
a million dollars cash in your bag.
Don't you think
it would be better...
This is the police.
You are completely surrounded.
Put down your weapon.
Put down your weapons now.
Rarely in the case
of armed robbery
do we hear a plea
of no contest.
Are you sure about this,
Mr. Scofield?
I'm sure, Your Honor.
Your Honor, we'd like
to recess if we could.
My client's a bit confused
at the moment.
I'm not, Your Honor.
He is, Your Honor.
Perhaps you should heed
your representation's advice,
take some additional time
to consider your response.
I've already done that,
Your Honor.
I'll retire to my chambers
to determine sentencing.
Court's recessed until 1:30.
Come on, let's go.
Uncle Mike?
I didn't want you to come.
Go home, LJ.
I didn't want you
to see this.
He's not gonna
take this well.
Can you blame him?
He's your nephew.
He's beginning
to get the idea
that anybody
he attaches himself to
is gonna
end up in prison...
And he's not the only one
who's starting to feel
that way, Michael.
Will you give us a minute?
One minute.
Don't you understand?
You just put the book
in that woman's hand
and she's gonna lob it
at you like a grenade.
Justice and punishment
are the same thing to her.
I know.
Then will you please tell me
what's going through your head?
We've been over this.
I've known you
my entire life.
You don't have
a violent bone in your body,
and I know you didn't
need the money.
Veronica.
Why won't you
let me help you?
You've been good to me.
My whole life, you have.
But you've gotta let me
deal with this.
Okay?
Given your lack
of prior criminal conduct,
I am inclined
toward probation.
However, the fact that
you discharged a deadly weapon
during the commission
of the crime suggests malice to me.
For that reason,
I find it incumbent
that you see the inside
of a prison cell, Mr. Scofield.
It says here
that you've requested to be incarcerated
somewhere near your home
here in Chicago.
I'm willing to honor that.
The closest
level one facility to--
Level one?
That's maximum security,
Your Honor.
I would ask counsel to refrain
from interrupting me.
As I was saying,
the closest
level one facility
would be Fox River
State Penitentiary.
As for the term
of your sentence,
I'm setting it
at five years.
You'll be eligible for parole
in half that time.
Sentence to be carried out immediately.
Okay, step inside the door
and check yourself for bugs.
When you hear
the knock, step out.
Keep the line moving.
We ain't got all day
to get this done.
- Let's go. Move it.
- No more talking in line.
Move it. You got less
than five minutes to take a shower.
Keep the line moving.
Keep it moving.
- Move it. Right now. Let's go. Move, move.
- Next!
Name and back number.
Scofield, Michael.
94941.
Are you
a religious man, Scofield?
Never really
thought about it.
Good, 'cause
the Ten Commandments
don't mean
a box of piss in here.
We got two commandments
and two only.
The first commandment
is you got nothing coming.
What's the second commandment?
See commandment number one.
Gotcha.
You talking out the side
of your neck?
Come again?
I said, are you
being a smartass?
Just trying to fly low,
avoid the radar, boss.
Do my time... and get out.
There isn't any flying
under my radar.
Good to know.
Hey, can a brother
get some air conditioning up here, cuz?
It's hotter than
a crack ho's mouth, man.
To hell with the AC, man.
Give me the crack ho.
Come on!
Yo, Fish!
What you looking at?
You look kind of pretty
to be up in here, man.
Fish!
I suggest you
take a seat, Fish.
Ain't nothing to do up in here
but serve time.
Ain't nobody
gonna serve it for you.
Welcome to
Prisneyland, Fish.
...is now
on mandatory lockdown...
You wanna talk
about it?
No, it's not
worth talking about.
If it's keeping you up,
it is.
Oh, it's just...
It's nothing, you know.
Michael's case.
You did the best you could.
Yeah, but he didn't.
He just sort of rolled over.
He didn't put up a fight.
It's not like him.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
be talking about him.
Hey, if it's on your mind,
it's on your mind, right?
Good night.
All wings, guard coming out.
All wings,
guard coming out.
Trey Street Deuces
got the hoops.
Nortenos got the bleachers.
Woods got the weight pile.
The C.O.s got the rest.
I'm telling you, the guards
are the dirtiest gang in this whole place.
The only difference
between us and them...
is the badge.
Who's the pet lover?
He'll deny it,
but he's D.B. Cooper.
Parachuted out of a plane
30 years ago with a million and a half in cash.
Doesn't look
like the type.
Who does?
Hey! What up, Wholesale?
-You okay?
-Gonna be greater later.
Yeah.
What you doing
with this fish, man?
-He's my new cellie.
-Huh.
Wholesale's got it wired up
at the commissary.
Anything you want,
he can get it for you.
You keep
handing out my jacket,
I swear I'm gonna
bust your grape.
Man, you couldn't bust a grape in Napa
with a set of cleats on.
-What are you talking about?
-Man, you want to bump your gums.
Oh, no, no. Now you're
talking, talking, talking...
I'm looking for someone.
Guy named Lincoln Burrows.
Linc the Sink?
That what
they're calling him now?
Yeah.
As in, he'll come at you
with everything but the kitchen...
Snowflake.
Where can I find him?
Man killed
the Vice President's brother.
In a month,
he's getting the chair,
which means no one up this river
is more dangerous than him,
'cause he's got
nothing to lose now.
What are they gonna do?
Kill him twice?
There a way
I can get to him?
Oh, no. The only time
those boys get out
is for chapel and P.I.
P.I.? What's that?
Prison Industry.
The guys that get along
get to work.
You know, painting, scrapping,
making mattresses, you name it.
I wouldn't get excited, though,
if I were you, Fish.
You ain't sniffin'
none of P.I.
Why's that?
'Cause John Abruzzi runs it.
"John Abruzzi" John Abruzzi?
"John Abruzzi" John Abruzzi.
Why you wanna see Burrows
so bad anyhow?
Because he's my brother.
They denied the motion.
Then do it again.
I can't. That's it.
May 11th.
That's the date, man.
That's the date they,
uh, you know...
execute me.
I know.
I didn't
kill that man, Michael.
The evidence says you did.
I don't care
what the evidence says.
I didn't kill him.
Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
But how did they get it wrong then?
The courts,
the appeals.
Don't know. Don't know.
All I keep thinking,
looking back on it is, uh...
I was set up.
And whoever it was
that set me up
wants me in the ground
as quickly as possible.
What's another word
for "love"?
What's the context?
Oh, you know.
The "I love you so much
I ain't never knocking over
a liquor store again" context.
Except, you know, classy.
Mmm.
I'm proposing to my girl,
if you gotta know.
In a letter?
You got a better way?
Face-to-face
works pretty good.
This place ain't exactly
the romantic spot.
I'm gonna have her get
on the Staten Island Ferry.
Then, once she can see
the Empire State Building,
she opens the letter...
It's like almost being there.
Except for the fact
that I won't be there.
Try "passion."
Ooh! Ooh! "Passion."
"Passion." That's dope.
Passion.
How do you spell that?
-Is it P-A-S-H?
-Uh-uh.
No "H"?
LJ, hold up.
Hold up.
I don't think I can
go through with this.
Everything's going
to be fine.
Trust me.
We understand
each other, then?
-Yeah.
-Friday.
Not Saturday.
Not Sunday. Friday.
It's totally understood.
I don't want hundreds,
I don't want fives, I don't want ones.
I know, I know.
Tens and 20s only.
It's on.
Police!
Abruzzi, I need you
to hire me a P.I.
Beat it.
Maybe you ought to hear
what I got to say.
You got nothing I need.
Wouldn't be
too sure of that.
My mistake.
Just what I need... a duck.
P.I., Abruzzi.
You might find I can be
of more assistance than you think.
Mull it over.
Come find me
when you're ready to talk.
All right, guys,
pick it up!
I want to get home tonight!
Maggio.
Yeah? So?
That's the son of a bitch
that fingered Abruzzi.
That's Fibonacci?
I thought the punk
was gone forever.
Evidently,
somebody found him.
Somebody messing with us?
This you're not
going to believe.
What is it?
Tattoo looks fresh.
Hold that.
I guess, being a diabetic,
you don't mind needles.
I'm Michael, by the way.
Scofield.
I read your report.
And you are?
Dr. Tancredi will do.
"Tancredi" like the governor?
You're not related,
are you?
Hmm. Wouldn't think
you'd find the daughter
of Frontier Justice Frank
working in a prison.
As a doctor, no less.
I believe in being part
of the solution, not the problem.
Hmm. "Be the change you want
to see in the world."
What?
Nothing. That was just
my senior quote.
That was you?
This whole time,
I was thinking it was Gandhi.
You're very funny.
Sit tight.
Put direct pressure on that.
I'll be back
in a sec.
So, how do we play this?
You hook me up
with a few weeks' supply?
Nice try.
No hypos on the floor.
I'm the farthest thing
from a junkie. Trust me.
I got news
for you, Michael.
"Trust me" means absolutely zero
inside these walls.
The only way
you're getting that insulin
is if I'm administering it.
Guess we'll be seeing
a lot of each other, then, huh?
I guess so.
We're all clear
on the Burrows execution.
-Good.
-Except for one thing.
Bishop McMorrow
is not in the fold.
He's got a lot of influence
with the governor.
They went to prep school
together, apparently.
Look, the closer it gets,
the more I'm worried
that the bottom is going
to fall out of this whole thing.
Well, maybe it's time you arranged a visit
with the good bishop, then.
Look, in one month,
it'll all be over.
"The Son of Man must be delivered
into the hands of sinful men
and be crucified
and the third day, rise again."
And they remembered His words,
and so should you.
Good day, gentlemen.
May God be with you.
Let's go,
let's go, let's go.
Michael.
Let's go. Come on, man.
Keep moving.
Move. Come on.
- Why?
- Let's go, man. Come on.
I'm getting you
out of here.
Burrows, roll it up.
Happy hour's over.
It's impossible.
Not if you designed
the place, it isn't.
Too formal.
Too "greeting card."
Well, we got
to make a decision
sooner or later,
you know.
We have time.
We don't, actually.
I mean, at some point,
we got to pull the trigger on this thing.
I don't want
to rush this.
We're only going
to do it once.
We have to
get it right.
Honey, can I
ask you something?
Of course.
Are you putting this off?
What do you mean?
I mean, are you
having second thoughts?
No. Honey, no.
I'm not.
I don't know.
-I just can't help thinking this is about--
-It's not.
I love you.
And I want
to be your wife.
Passion?
What were you thinking?
Hey, you went for it.
She probably thinks
I went sissy up in here.
"Passion." You know,
got more than one syllable, too much talkin'.
That's me from now on.
One-syllable Sucre.
Yes. No. Love.
Hate. Love.
Give it time.
Are you kidding?
I proposed to her.
That doesn't take time.
Si or no.
One syllable, man.
She's supposed
to come around
for a conjugal on Tuesday.
She's always
calling me beforehand,
letting me know
she's coming.
This time, man,
I ain't heard a peep.
You spooked her.
Scofield.
Get it together.
Pope wants to see you.
No good, Fish.
No one gets an audience
with the Pope.
Not unless he's real interested
in what you got going on.
Top of your class at Loyola.
Magna cum laude, in fact.
I can't help wondering
what someone with your credentials
is doing in a place like this.
Took a wrong turn
a few months back, I guess.
You make it sound
like a traffic infraction.
Like all you did was turn the wrong way
up a one-way street.
Everyone turns up one
sooner or later.
The reason
I called you here...
I noticed in your I-file,
under occupation,
you put down "unemployed."
That's not true, now, is it?
I know you're
a structural engineer, Scofield.
Shah Jahan
built the Taj Majal
as a monument
to his undying love for his wife.
My wife is quite fond
of the story.
It appeals
to the romantic in her.
Being married to someone
in Corrections, terrible job.
Wouldn't wish it on anyone.
And yet, in 39 years,
my wife
has never complained.
And the worst part of it is,
I've never thanked her.
So, because
I couldn't say it,
I thought, you know,
I could build it.
Come June,
it's our 40th anniversary.
But here, look.
You see,
the problem is,
I build anymore,
it's all gonna come down
like a house of cards.
That's where I was hoping
you could be of assistance.
For the favor,
I can offer you
three days of work
a week in here.
And it'll keep you
off the yard.
Mmm.
I can't do it.
Son, it's better for me
to owe you one in here
than it is for you
to owe me one,
I can promise you that.
I'll take my chances.
Then we're through here.
Guard!
Two pounds of pot?
What were you trying to do,
set a record?
It's not funny, LJ.
You could be going
to jail.
It's pretty obvious to me
you need some guidance.
Hey.
Thanks.
From who,
old Daddy Warbucks?
Give him a chance.
He's a good man.
We got nothing in common.
Come on. Where is this
coming from, LJ?
Last semester you were getting
almost all A's and now...
It's your father, isn't it?
I don't have a father.
It wasn't an immaculate
conception, honey.
Trust me.
Maybe it's time
we went and saw him.
Mom...
Mom.
Don't.
I'm about as excited
by the prospect as you are,
but something's gotta give.
You have got
too much potential
to be screwing up
your life like this.
What if they'd sent you
to Taylorville or Marion and not here?
I think I'd be doing
the same thing I'm doing in here.
Eating Jell-O,
drinking Kool-Aid...
I know what you're doing.
It's not the luck of the draw
that you're in here with Lincoln.
You forget I know you.
Both of you.
You two have the most
dysfunctional idea of love I've ever seen.
What, he beats you up
to keep you off the streets,
so you get yourself tossed
into Fox River with him?
To what?
Save him?
I deserve to know.
I loved him
as much as you did.
Past tense for you, maybe.
Not me.
I gave him a shot
when I got back from college. I did.
Even with all the stuff
that was going on with him,
I did everything I could
to make it work.
And he threw it away.
You ever think maybe he was hurt
that you left
in the first place?
Don't do this.
Whatever it is you're doing,
don't do it.
There's a better way.
I'm already appealing
your case.
I told you
to leave that alone.
I've gotten in touch with the diocese about Lincoln.
The bishop may be able to help.
That won't stop it.
It'll only delay it.
You want
to do something?
You find out
who's trying to bury him.
Nobody's trying to bury him.
The evidence was there.
The evidence was cooked.
Visiting hours
are now over.
Take care of yourself.
Someone wants him
dead, Veronica.
Something more
is going on here.
This is desperation, Michael.
You're grabbing at straws.
You're in denial.
Maybe.
But I can't watch him die.
I won't do that.
Gentlemen...
What is it about the Burrows situation
that I can help you with?
It's our understanding
that you have great influence with the governor.
I wouldn't say it's "great" or "influence."
We're friends.
It's also our understanding
that you oppose the death penalty.
I'm a man of God.
How could I not?
In this case, we're hoping
you'll suspend that position.
At least temporarily.
If the inmate appeals
to me for intervention,
how can I
turn my back on him?
You have a habit of answering
a question with a question.
And you have a way of asking questions
that beg more questions.
Are you saying
you won't do it?
I'm not a man to equivocate.
You're, what, 62 years old now,
Your Excellency.
That's right.
I would assume, then,
that you'd be well-versed
in how our government's
tax system works.
Taking personal
capital gains
under the church's
tax shelter...
that would be fraud,
wouldn't it, Your Excellency?
I will not be cowed
into forsaking my beliefs.
Not by you or anyone else.
Admirable.
Good day, Excellency.
Mr. Kellerman...
What is it about this case
that the Secret Service is so interested in?
The man killed
the Vice President's brother.
What'd you say?
You heard me.
Someone found Fibonacci.
I'm looking at the photos
right now.
Son of a bitch
has got a beard, sunglasses...
Witness protection,
if I ever saw it.
Who was this someone?
Don't know, there's no return address
on the envelope.
Just...
this folded-up bird
made of paper.
Like origami?
Yeah, like that.
Like origami.
You're Charles Westmoreland,
right?
Do I know you?
I knew your wife
before she passed.
You knew Marla?
You mean Ann?
How'd you know her?
We taught together
in Boston.
East Farmington.
You mean West Wilmington?
No more tests.
I promise.
Seems you know
everything about me.
Who are you?
Michael Scofield.
How'd you get it in here?
First off,
she's not an "it."
She's Marilyn,
and she's grandfathered
back from the days
when prisoners were allowed a creature comfort or two.
I heard
you were D.B. Cooper.
Every new fish
comes in here,
first thing they hear,
is that Charles Westmoreland
is D.B. Cooper.
I'll tell you
like I tell them...
You want the Cooper story?
I can't give it to you,
'cause I'm not him.
It's too bad.
Sort of wish it was true.
The man's a legend.
Nowhere near as much
as I wish it were true, friend.
I'd have a million-five
waiting for me on the outside.
I'd put some grass
under 'em if I were you.
This thing would go
a whole lot easier if you'd just hire me.
What is this all about?
Say you were able
to get outside those walls...
would you have
the people in place
to make sure
you disappeared forever?
What do you care?
Just curious.
Where's Fibonacci?
That's not the way
it works.
They come at me, John,
I'm coming after you.
I doubt it.
Fight, fight, fight...
All right.
Get on the ground.
I totally
misjudged you, Scofield.
I didn't think
you were the agitating type.
Behavior like that
will not be tolerated in my prison.
Ninety days in the SHU!
That ought to be enough time
to convince you of that fact.
Ninety days?
That's right.
Something you want to say?
It's just...
I'm not of much value
to you in the SHU.
Value?
Hmm... The Taj.
It'd be a shame
for the eighth wonder of the modern world
to collapse because the stress
isn't properly propagated.
Properly propagated?
Properly propagated.
The joints are overloaded.
They won't provide anywhere
near the sheer strength
the completed structure
will need.
How much work
are we talking?
You want it by when, June?
Yes.
Then we'd better get started,
wouldn't you say?
Who's there?
Bishop McMorrow
was killed last night.
Someone shot him
while he was sleeping.
I thought
you'd want to know.
Thanks.
Michael was right.
Sink, you got a visitor.
He was arrested.
For what?
Possession of marijuana.
I figured he could use
some fatherly advice before it's...
-Gone forever?
-I didn't mean that.
I know you didn't.
Thanks, Lisa.
Sit down.
Dope, huh?
Using or dealing?
What's the difference?
Then what, you, uh, think it gives you
some kind of street cred?
You got a piece
of the good life.
Take advantage.
Look, I get it.
The whole thing.
She drags me in here,
you give me a big speech,
I walk away a changed man.
Straight A's.
Harvard.
Grow up and be a dentist.
It's better than being here.
You got to realize
who's getting punished
when you're doing
the things you're doing.
You think it's me.
It's you.
I did the same thing.
Punished the old man
'cause he was gone.
Look what it got me.
I'm not asking you
to love me.
I already screwed up
that chance long ago.
I'm asking you
to love yourself.
You can still put the brakes
on this thing.
So, that's what
fatherly advice is like.
Where are you going?
I got homework.
They're putting me
to death, LJ.
In a month's time,
I'll be dead.
You get that?
You're already
dead to me.
Yes.
What? You mean "yes," yes?
Yes!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
-Oh, there's just one thing.
-Of course.
Mama wants us to wait
till you get out.
Of course, mi amor.
Oh, and we have
to get married in a church.
-Okay. Esta bien.
-A Catholic church.
Wouldn't want to mess
with the Catholic roots, would we?
You went to Loyola.
You've been
checking up on me.
I like to get to know
my patients.
I went to Northwestern.
Graduated two years after you did.
Maybe we met before,
you know, drunk,
out at a bar somewhere.
I would have remembered.
-That a compliment?
-No.
Hmm.
What?
Your blood glucose is at
50 milligrams per deciliter.
-So?
-That's hypoglycemic.
Your body's reacting
to the insulin
like you're not a diabetic.
You're sure it's type 1 diabetes
you've got?
Ever since I was a kid.
All right.
Not experiencing
any tingling sensation, cold sweats--
Infirmary.
Yes.
Yeah. I did.
No, I did and I do.
I need them.
Okay. Um, great.
Well, I'll call him after lunch, then.
Thanks.
I'm with a patient. Okay.
I'd like to run some tests
next time you're in.
Last thing I want is to be
administering insulin to a man who doesn't need it.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
How'd you get here,
by the way?
Oh, you know.
I don't.
That's why I asked.
You know. Hector.
What?
I didn't have any money
for the bus,
so he offered me a ride.
He was really sweet.
Honey, he's just a friend.
No, he's not
just a friend.
I know Hector.
I know men.
Men and women
can't be friends.
A guy doesn't drive a girl
500 miles across state lines
because he wants
to be friends.
Casanova, wrap it up.
Hey, you got nothing
to worry about, okay?
It's you I'm marrying.
It's not you
I'm worried about.
Sixteen more months.
I love you.
Be easy, son, all right?
Sucre tells me
you're the local pharmacy.
-What you need, man?
-PUGNAc.
I only speak English,
white boy.
It's an insulin blocker.
Standard
over-the-counter variety.
You can get it
at any pharmacy.
You can get that
at medical then.
I can't get it at medical.
Why not?
Because they're already
giving me insulin shots.
You're one mixed-up cracker,
you know that?
Can you get it for me,
or not?
Only if you tell me
why is it you want
to keep going
back up to medical
to get an insulin shot
for which you don't need.
I like the ambiance.
Uh-huh.
Are we in business?
All personnel,
Facility Two lockdown
in 20 minutes.
Facility One lockdown
in ten minutes.
Scofield. I don't know
what you did,
but Abruzzi wanted me
to give you this P.I. card.
Congratulations.
You just joined the ranks
of the employed.
Kudos, Fish.
You got spine.
All right, cons,
break it down!
Move it, guys.
Saw Veronica
came by yesterday.
Still engaged to that guy?
Yup.
Could have been me.
If you hadn't
self-destructed.
You think I meant
to knock up Lisa Rix?
I was just being stupid.
Hurt.
Shouldn't have
pushed her away, though.
You pushed everyone away.
I'm an anchor.
All I'll do
is drag him down with me.
Why did you hire him?
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
You mean
what you said earlier?
I'm not here on vacation,
trust me.
Getting outside these walls,
that's just the beginning.
You're going to need money.
I'll have it.
And people
on the outside...
People that can
help you disappear.
I've already got them.
They just
don't know it yet.
Look, whatever you got
going on, fill me in,
'cause I'm in the dark here.
Chaparral Associates
got the contract
to retrofit
this place in '99.
Four million dollar contract.
Head partner
couldn't crack it.
So, he subcontracted out,
an under-the-table sort of deal
with a former associate.
That guy was one
of the partners in my firm.
We basically ghost-wrote
the whole plan.
Crossed the t's, dotted the i's,
grouted the tiles.
You've seen the blueprints.
Better than that.
I've got them on me.
Are you kidding me?
Am I supposed to be seeing
something here?
Look closer.
Captioned by Point.360.