<Boold>The Empire is gone, Mando.</Boold>
<Boold>This asset</Boold>
<Boold><i>I had to ensure its delivery.</i></Boold>
<Boold>He's not a local warlord.</Boold>
<Boold>He's Imperial.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm in.</Boold>
<Boold><i>Our secrecy is our survival.</Boold>
<Boold><i>Our strength was once in our numbers.</i></Boold>
<Boold>Now, we live in the shadows.</Boold>
<Boold>Our world was shattered by the Empire.</Boold>
<Boold>You're going</Boold>
<Boold>This is the Way.</Boold>
<Boold>In the wake of your destruction</Boold>
<Boold>Is it still a hunter?</Boold>
<Boold>No. But it will protect.</Boold>
<Boold>You got a real thing for droids</Boold>
<Boold>I got a real thing for that droid.</Boold>
<Boold>Let me take the child to him...</Boold>
<Boold>Let's kill him and get out of here.</Boold>
<Boold>- We both need the client to be eliminated.</Boold>
<Boold>As long as the Imp lives</Boold>
<Boold><i>It's a trap.</i></Boold>
<Boold><i>- Have they brought the child?</i></Boold>
<Boold><i>You have something I want.</i></Boold>
<Boold>Kuiil? Are you there?</Boold>
<Boold>In a few moments...</Boold>
<Boold><i>Kuiil! Are you there?</i></Boold>
<Boold>It will be mine.</Boold>
<Boold>Speeder bikes have arrived</Boold>
<Boold>Awaiting confirmation.</Boold>
<Boold>Knock it off!</Boold>
<Boold>Waiting for confirmation</Boold>
<Boold><i>That's a go to proceed</Boold>
<Boold><i>The Moff just touched down and already</Boold>
<Boold>Standing by.</Boold>
<Boold>Did he just say</Boold>
<Boold>Oh, who knows?</Boold>
<Boold>These guys like to lay down the law</Boold>
<Boold>You know how it is.</Boold>
<Boold>I said, shut up. Yeesh.</Boold>
<Boold>What is that thing, anyway?</Boold>
<Boold>Uh, I don't know.</Boold>
<Boold>Maybe Moff wants to eat it.</Boold>
<Boold>Can I see it?</Boold>
<Boold>Did you not just hear</Boold>
<Boold>a dozen of his own troopers</Boold>
<Boold>- Okay.</Boold>
<Boold>- Do you get the point?</Boold>
<Boold>Okay.</Boold>
<Boold>Should we offer</Boold>
<Boold>You just wanna look at it.</Boold>
<Boold>So what?</Boold>
<Boold>Barely.</Boold>
<Boold>I mean, I grabbed it up off the ground</Boold>
<Boold>It's more than I got to see it.</Boold>
<Boold>Look, I'm not taking it out of</Boold>
<Boold>- Fine.</Boold>
<Boold>Let me check on this thing. This is crazy.</Boold>
<Boold>Any update yet?</Boold>
<Boold><i>That's a negative.</Boold>
<Boold><i>He just killed an officer</Boold>
<Boold><i>- so this might take a while.</i></Boold>
<Boold>Thank you.</Boold>
<Boold>Standing by still. Unbelievable.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey, how long has it been</Boold>
<Boold>I don't know</Boold>
<Boold>Uh, it's been</Boold>
<Boold>Oh, my God.</Boold>
<Boold>Shouldn't we check</Boold>
<Boold>You hit it pretty hard.</Boold>
<Boold>You just wanna see it.</Boold>
<Boold>We should check</Boold>
<Boold>The last thing that you want</Boold>
<Boold>and have him open it</Boold>
<Boold>Okay. Okay, look.</Boold>
<Boold>Take a peek. Everything's fine.</Boold>
<Boold>What is that?</Boold>
<Boold>I don't know.</Boold>
<Boold>A pet? I thought you...</Boold>
<Boold>Serves you right.</Boold>
<Boold>Stop that.</Boold>
<Boold>Identify yourself!</Boold>
<Boold>I am IG-11.</Boold>
<Boold>I am this child's nurse droid and require</Boold>
<Boold>A nurse droid?</Boold>
<Boold>I thought it was a hunter.</Boold>
<Boold>Yeah, well</Boold>
<Boold>I'm sorry, nurse</Boold>
<Boold>Are you refusing my request?</Boold>
<Boold>No.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm telling you to get out of here.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey.</Boold>
<Boold>That was unpleasant.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm sorry you had to see that.</Boold>
<Boold>Is there another way out?</Boold>
<Boold>No, that's it.</Boold>
<Boold>- What about the sewers?</Boold>
<Boold>The Mandalorians</Boold>
<Boold>If we can get down there</Boold>
<Boold>Yeah, sewers are good.</Boold>
<Boold>Checking for access points.</Boold>
<Boold>What the hell are they waiting for?</Boold>
<Boold>Hold up.</Boold>
<Boold>They're setting up an E-Web.</Boold>
<Boold>It's over.</Boold>
<Boold>I found the sewer vent.</Boold>
<Boold>Let's get the hell out of here.</Boold>
<Boold>It's assembled!</Boold>
<Boold>- Blow it.</Boold>
<Boold>Get out of the way!</Boold>
<Boold>Your astute panic suggests</Boold>
<Boold>I would prefer to avoid</Boold>
<Boold>and encourage a moment of consideration.</Boold>
<Boold>Members of my escort</Boold>
<Boold>of an E-Web heavy repeating blaster.</Boold>
<Boold>If you are unfamiliar with this weapon</Boold>
<Boold>I am sure that Republican Shock Trooper</Boold>
<Boold>will advise you that she has witnessed</Boold>
<Boold>facing the predecessor</Boold>
<Boold>Or perhaps the decommissioned</Boold>
<Boold>has heard the songs</Boold>
<Boold>when gunships outfitted</Boold>
<Boold>laid waste to fields of Mandalorian</Boold>
<Boold>I advise disgraced Magistrate Greef Karga</Boold>
<Boold>and urge you to lay down your arms</Boold>
<Boold>The structure you are trapped in</Boold>
<Boold>and your storied lives will come</Boold>
<Boold>What do you propose?</Boold>
<Boold>Reasonable negotiation.</Boold>
<Boold>What assurance do you offer?</Boold>
<Boold>If you're asking</Boold>
<Boold>Just as you betrayed</Boold>
<Boold>I would gladly break any promise</Boold>
<Boold>The assurance I give is this:</Boold>
<Boold>which at this time involves</Boold>
<Boold>I will give you until nightfall, and then</Boold>
<Boold>I say we hear him out.</Boold>
<Boold>The minute we open that door, we're dead.</Boold>
<Boold>We're dead if we don't.</Boold>
<Boold>At least out there, we've got a shot.</Boold>
<Boold>That's easy for you to say.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm a Rebel Shock Trooper.</Boold>
<Boold>They'll upload me to a Mind Flayer.</Boold>
<Boold>Those aren't real.</Boold>
<Boold>I don't care to find out.</Boold>
<Boold>What about you, Mando?</Boold>
<Boold>I know who he is.</Boold>
<Boold>It's Moff Gideon.</Boold>
<Boold>No.</Boold>
<Boold>Moff Gideon was executed for war crimes.</Boold>
<Boold>It's him.</Boold>
<Boold>So? What does that prove?</Boold>
<Boold>I haven't heard that name</Boold>
<Boold>On Mandalore?</Boold>
<Boold>I was not born on Mandalore.</Boold>
<Boold>But you're a Mandalorian.</Boold>
<Boold>Mandalorian isn't a race.</Boold>
<Boold>It's a Creed.</Boold>
<Boold>I was a foundling.</Boold>
<Boold>They raised me in the Fighting Corps.</Boold>
<Boold>I was treated as one of their own.</Boold>
<Boold>When I came of age</Boold>
<Boold>The only record of my family name</Boold>
<Boold>Moff Gideon was an ISB Officer</Boold>
<Boold>That's how I know it's him.</Boold>
<Boold>That's how he knows who we all are.</Boold>
<Boold>He says he needs us</Boold>
<Boold>I was worried when the Ugnaught</Boold>
<Boold>but if they'd captured the kid</Boold>
<Boold>Hail them again.</Boold>
<Boold>Come in, Kuiil.</Boold>
<Boold>Kuiil?</Boold>
<Boold>- Nothing.</Boold>
<Boold>Kuiil has been terminated.</Boold>
<Boold>What did you do?</Boold>
<Boold><i>I am fulfilling my base function.</i></Boold>
<Boold>Which is?</Boold>
<Boold>To nurse and protect.</Boold>
<Boold>What was that?</Boold>
<Boold>Look alive.</Boold>
<Boold>Look!</Boold>
<Boold>Cover me.</Boold>
<Boold>Burn them out.</Boold>
<Boold>Stay with me, buddy.</Boold>
<Boold>This is our only path out.</Boold>
<Boold>Stay with me.</Boold>
<Boold>If you go near this child</Boold>
<Boold>I understand.</Boold>
<Boold>Yes, of course.</Boold>
<Boold>Oh, I love IG units.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm not gonna make it. Go.</Boold>
<Boold>Shut up. You just got your bell rung.</Boold>
<Boold>Leave me.</Boold>
<Boold>- I'm gonna need to take this thing off.</Boold>
<Boold>You make sure the child is safe.</Boold>
<Boold>Here.</Boold>
<Boold>When you get to the Mandalorian covert</Boold>
<Boold>You tell them it's from Din Djarin.</Boold>
<Boold>You tell them the foundling was</Boold>
<Boold>We can make it.</Boold>
<Boold>Come on! Let's go!</Boold>
<Boold>I'm not gonna make it and you know it.</Boold>
<Boold>You protect the child.</Boold>
<Boold>I can hold them back long enough</Boold>
<Boold>Let me have a warrior's death.</Boold>
<Boold>I won't leave you.</Boold>
<Boold>This is the Way.</Boold>
<Boold>Come on! It's open, let's go!</Boold>
<Boold>Go. Go.</Boold>
<Boold>We have to move! Now!</Boold>
<Boold>Go.</Boold>
<Boold>Escape and protect this child.</Boold>
<Boold>I will stay with the Mandalorian.</Boold>
<Boold>Promise me you'll bring him.</Boold>
<Boold>You have my word.</Boold>
<Boold>Do it.</Boold>
<Boold>Do what?</Boold>
<Boold>Just get it over with.</Boold>
<Boold>I'd rather you kill me than some Imp.</Boold>
<Boold>I told you.</Boold>
<Boold>I am a nurse droid.</Boold>
<Boold>IGs are all hunters.</Boold>
<Boold>Not this one. I was reprogrammed.</Boold>
<Boold>I need to remove your helmet</Boold>
<Boold>Try it and I'll kill you.</Boold>
<Boold>It is forbidden.</Boold>
<Boold>No living thing has seen me</Boold>
<Boold>I am not a living thing.</Boold>
<Boold>This is a bacta spray.</Boold>
<Boold>You have suffered damage</Boold>
<Boold>You mean my brain?</Boold>
<Boold>That was a joke.</Boold>
<Boold>I got you.</Boold>
<Boold>Do you know which way to go?</Boold>
<Boold>No. I don't know these tunnels.</Boold>
<Boold>I've only entered from the bazaar.</Boold>
<Boold>Well, if we get the smell</Boold>
<Boold>it'll lead us up to the plains</Boold>
<Boold>And the Imps will</Boold>
<Boold>We need the Mandalorians</Boold>
<Boold>Ugh, this place is a maze.</Boold>
<Boold>Stop.</Boold>
<Boold>I can stand.</Boold>
<Boold>The bacta infusion is working.</Boold>
<Boold>I'll try to find tracks.</Boold>
<Boold>We're close.</Boold>
<Boold>Turn here.</Boold>
<Boold>We should go.</Boold>
<Boold>You go. Take the ship.</Boold>
<Boold>Did you know about this?</Boold>
<Boold>Is this the work of your bounty hunters?</Boold>
<Boold>No.</Boold>
<Boold>When you left the system</Boold>
<Boold>and the hunters just melted away.</Boold>
<Boold>You know how it is.</Boold>
<Boold>They're mercenaries. They're not zealots.</Boold>
<Boold>Did you do this? Did you?</Boold>
<Boold>- No!</Boold>
<Boold>We revealed ourselves.</Boold>
<Boold>We knew what could happen</Boold>
<Boold>The Imperials arrived shortly thereafter.</Boold>
<Boold>This is what resulted.</Boold>
<Boold>Did any survive?</Boold>
<Boold>I hope so.</Boold>
<Boold>Come with us.</Boold>
<Boold>No.</Boold>
<Boold>I will not abandon this place</Boold>
<Boold>Show me the one</Boold>
<Boold>This is the one.</Boold>
<Boold>This is the one that you hunted</Boold>
<Boold>Yes. The one that saved me as well.</Boold>
<Boold>- From the mudhorn?</Boold>
<Boold>It looks helpless.</Boold>
<Boold>It's injured, but it is not helpless.</Boold>
<Boold>Its species can move objects</Boold>
<Boold>I know of such things.</Boold>
<Boold>The songs of eons past tell of battles</Boold>
<Boold>and an order of sorcerers called Jedi</Boold>
<Boold>It is an enemy?</Boold>
<Boold>No. Its kind were enemies</Boold>
<Boold>What is it?</Boold>
<Boold>It is a foundling.</Boold>
<Boold>By Creed, it is in your care.</Boold>
<Boold>You wish me to train this thing?</Boold>
<Boold>It is too weak. It would die.</Boold>
<Boold>You have no choice.</Boold>
<Boold>Where?</Boold>
<Boold>This, you must determine.</Boold>
<Boold>You expect me to search the galaxy</Boold>
<Boold>for the home of this creature</Boold>
<Boold>and deliver it to a race</Boold>
<Boold>This is the Way.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey.</Boold>
<Boold>These tunnels will be lousy with Imps</Boold>
<Boold>We should at least discuss an escape plan.</Boold>
<Boold>If you follow</Boold>
<Boold>it will lead you to the underground river.</Boold>
<Boold>It flows downstream toward the lava flats.</Boold>
<Boold>I think we should go.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm staying.</Boold>
<Boold>I need to help her and I need to heal.</Boold>
<Boold>You must go.</Boold>
<Boold>A foundling is in your care.</Boold>
<Boold>By Creed, until it is of age or reunited</Boold>
<Boold>you are as its father.</Boold>
<Boold>This is the Way.</Boold>
<Boold>You have earned your Signet.</Boold>
<Boold>You are a clan of two.</Boold>
<Boold>Thank you.</Boold>
<Boold>I will wear this with honor.</Boold>
<Boold>We should go.</Boold>
<Boold>IG, please guard</Boold>
<Boold>A scouting party draws near.</Boold>
<Boold>Hang on.</Boold>
<Boold>I have one more gift</Boold>
<Boold>Have you trained in the Rising Phoenix?</Boold>
<Boold>When I was a boy. Yes.</Boold>
<Boold>Then this will make you complete.</Boold>
<Boold>Thank you.</Boold>
<Boold>ARMORER When you have healed</Boold>
<Boold>Until you know it</Boold>
<Boold>I understand.</Boold>
<Boold>WEBVTT</Boold>
<Boold>You are protected.</Boold>
<Boold>More will come. You must go.</Boold>
<Boold>Come with us.</Boold>
<Boold>My place is here.</Boold>
<Boold>Restock your munitions.</Boold>
<Boold>IG, carry this for Din Djarin</Boold>
<Boold>Now, go.</Boold>
<Boold>Down to the river and across the plains.</Boold>
<Boold>Be safe on your journey.</Boold>
<Boold>Thank you.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey, Mando.</Boold>
<Boold>Where are they?</Boold>
<Boold>I said, where are they?</Boold>
<Boold>This is the lava river.</Boold>
<Boold>The ferry droid is fried.</Boold>
<Boold>Yeah, but if we push the boat out</Boold>
<Boold>Come on.</Boold>
<Boold>Looks old. Will it take the heat?</Boold>
<Boold>You got a better idea?</Boold>
<Boold>Guess not.</Boold>
<Boold>Push!</Boold>
<Boold>Come on! What're you doing?</Boold>
<Boold>- Let's try this.</Boold>
<Boold>You guys mind getting out of the way?</Boold>
<Boold>Oh!</Boold>
<Boold>Good job.</Boold>
<Boold>Watch your feet. It's molten lava.</Boold>
<Boold>No kidding.</Boold>
<Boold>I don't suppose anybody here speaks droid?</Boold>
<Boold>I believe he is asking</Boold>
<Boold>Down river. To the lava flat.</Boold>
<Boold>That's it. We're free!</Boold>
<Boold>No.</Boold>
<Boold>No, we're not.</Boold>
<Boold>Stormtroopers.</Boold>
<Boold>It looks like an entire platoon.</Boold>
<Boold>Stop the boat.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey, Droid, I said stop the boat.</Boold>
<Boold>Hey! I'm talking to you.</Boold>
<Boold>I said stop!</Boold>
<Boold>We're still moving.</Boold>
<Boold>Looks like we fight.</Boold>
<Boold>- There are too many.</Boold>
<Boold>'Cause I can't surrender.</Boold>
<Boold>They will not be satisfied</Boold>
<Boold>This is unacceptable.</Boold>
<Boold>I will eliminate the enemy</Boold>
<Boold>You don't have</Boold>
<Boold>You wouldn't even get to daylight.</Boold>
<Boold>That is not my objective.</Boold>
<Boold>We're getting close. Saddle up.</Boold>
<Boold>I still have the security protocols</Boold>
<Boold>If my designs are compromised</Boold>
<Boold>What're you talking about?</Boold>
<Boold>I am not permitted to be captured.</Boold>
<Boold>Are we gonna keep talking</Boold>
<Boold>I can no longer carry this for you.</Boold>
<Boold>Nor can I watch over the child.</Boold>
<Boold>Wait. You can't self-destruct.</Boold>
<Boold>Your base command is to watch the child.</Boold>
<Boold>That supersedes</Boold>
<Boold>- Right?</Boold>
<Boold>Good. Now, grab a blaster</Boold>
<Boold>Victory through combat</Boold>
<Boold>We will be captured.</Boold>
<Boold>Sadly, there is no scenario where</Boold>
<Boold>Listen, you're not going anywhere.</Boold>
<Boold>We need you. Let's just come up with a...</Boold>
<Boold>Please tell me the child</Boold>
<Boold>If you do so</Boold>
<Boold>But you'll be destroyed.</Boold>
<Boold>And you will live</Boold>
<Boold>No. We need you.</Boold>
<Boold>There is nothing to be sad about.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm not sad.</Boold>
<Boold>Yes, you are. I'm a nurse droid.</Boold>
<Boold>IG?</Boold>
<Boold>What're you doing?</Boold>
<Boold>Manufacturer's protocol dictates</Boold>
<Boold>I must be destroyed.</Boold>
<Boold>Moff Gideon!</Boold>
<Boold>- He missed!</Boold>
<Boold>Our blasters are useless against him.</Boold>
<Boold>Let's make the baby do</Boold>
<Boold>Come on, baby! Do the magic hand thing.</Boold>
<Boold>- I'm out of ideas.</Boold>
<Boold>Here he comes!</Boold>
<Boold>No!</Boold>
<Boold>That was impressive, Mando.</Boold>
<Boold>It looks like your Guild rates</Boold>
<Boold>Any more stormtroopers?</Boold>
<Boold>I think we cleaned up the town.</Boold>
<Boold>I'm thinking of staying around</Boold>
<Boold>- You're staying here?</Boold>
<Boold>Nevarro is a very fine planet.</Boold>
<Boold>And now that the scum and villainy</Boold>
<Boold>it's very respectable again.</Boold>
<Boold>As a bounty hunter hive?</Boold>
<Boold>Some of my favorite people</Boold>
<Boold>And perhaps, this specimen of soldier</Boold>
<Boold>Yeah. I've got some clerical</Boold>
<Boold>And if you would agree</Boold>
<Boold>clerical concerns would be</Boold>
<Boold>But you, my friend, you will be welcome</Boold>
<Boold>So, go off, enjoy yourself.</Boold>
<Boold>And when you're ready to return</Boold>
<Boold>I'm afraid I have</Boold>
<Boold>Take care of this little one.</Boold>
<Boold>Or maybe, it'll take care of you.</Boold>
<Boold>What do you got there?</Boold>
<Boold>I didn't think I'd see this again.</Boold>
<Boold>Why don't you hang onto that?</Boold>